Chapter 654: The War Begins

The Seoul Star Cluster, which was controlled by Klent, was separated from the Colton Star Cluster by a barren cosmic belt. After the war between the Star Clusters broke out, the stargates to both Star Clusters were temporarily shut, and troops could only cross the border illegally through the barren cosmic belt.

A large fleet of troops passed through the barren cosmic belt and entered the borders of Colton, the West Wind Star System.

This was a vanguard force with the intention of probing the enemy. There were fifteen Expedition Level flagships, thousands of frigates and assault battleships, and a total of over ten thousand spaceships.

There were twenty-six Calamity Grade Supers, including Tyrant's Eight Vanguard Official.

The commander of the expedition fleet was Jorde, the individual in charge of Bloodshed Land's Military Strategy Department. He was a Grade A Super and one of Tyrant's old subordinates.

"According to the intelligence, Purple Crystal has mobilized their forces to intercept our vanguard forces. Your first mission is to occupy a planet without inhabitants and make use of the Crimson Dynasty's Fortress Expansion Package to construct a base.

"This is a secret war that a civilization cannot openly participate in. The West Wind Star System Civilization will not dare stop you from constructing a base on a planet without inhabitants."

Right at this moment, the Military Strategy Department was holding a remote meeting, and the commanders of the various fleets, as well as seven Vanguard Officials, were listening to Jorde's instructions.

Only the chief Vanguard Official was not present, but no one found it strange at all. With the Military Strategy Department taking up the role of command, the Vanguard Officials only needed to listen to orders and fight. The status of the chief Vanguard Official was special, and others revered his strength. Compared to being part of a meeting, he was more willing to spend his time in his cultivation chamber. He had the privilege to do so.

Jorde briefly went through the strategy before saying, "Not all the Star Systems within the Colton Star Cluster have submitted to the Purple Crystal Civilization. A portion of the Star Systems aren't concerned about who rules over the Star Cluster and will choose to remain neutral. They will not obstruct us in anyway. Unless necessary, do not start a conflict with the local civilizations. Let them understand Klent's intentions and try to befriend them..."

With the restriction of the peace treaty, all the Star Cluster Civilizations had a protective talisman. Furthermore, Klent's objective wasn't to destroy Purple Crystal. Klent only wanted to expand their territory and snatch a few Star Systems from the Colton Star Cluster. They wanted to make use of the Bloodshed Land as their proxy and contain the war between both parties at the level of a secret war.

As long as Bloodshed Land could gain a foothold in a few Star Systems, Klent would be able to spread their influence through Bloodshed Land and weaken Purple Crystal's control over the region. They would then be able to completely block out Purple Crystal's control over the region.

Their objective would not be in conflict with the various Star System Civilizations. Bloodshed Land would not take over the control of those Star Systems and would even build diplomatic ties with them. The only party suffering a loss would be Purple Crystal.

Using an analogy, it was like two gangs fighting over collecting protection fees.

Since they wanted to snatch territory, there would only be a future if they could protect it. Bloodshed Land's invasion was not the same as that of DarkStar, harassing different locations without claiming any territory. This also meant that the following war would be extremely intense and last for a long time.

The target of this vanguard force was to establish a bridgehead in the West Wind Star System and test the strength of the Purple Crystal Civilization's retaliation.

Everyone nodded in response. They had already been briefed thoroughly on the mission and were hearing it from Jorde again.

The second Vanguard Official, Hunting Blade, growled in a deep voice, "Section Zero has many members with at least a hundred Calamity Grade Supers. This time, our vanguard force has less than thirty Calamity Grade Supers. Even if the Vanguard Officials can fight three, I can fight five, and chief can fight ten, we will still be on the losing end. The main force had better catch up soon."

Jorde nodded in response. "Purple Crystal won't be able to mobilize such a large force within a short period of time. Furthermore, the first exchange is only a probing one, so the opponent won't send too many troops. The other vanguard forces invading the other Star Systems will help tie down Purple Crystal's forces."

The West Wind Star System was only one of Bloodshed Land's targets. Bloodshed Land had the ability and resources to stretch out the battle lines.

As a condition for Bloodshed Land participating in the secret war, Klent had helped Bloodshed Land rope in almost half of the armed organizations within their Star Cluster. Bloodshed Land had already expanded to a whole new level, and they were definitely capable of taking out a hundred Calamity Grade Supers.

Right at that moment, a holographic projection suddenly entered the meeting.

Everyone looked over, and the seven Vanguard Officials bowed.

"Chief."

He had dark red skin with a square jaw and sharp gaze. His aura was extremely tyrannical with thin dragon scales around his eyes, lips, and temples. He looked like he had a mixed dragon bloodline, but the species of the dragon could not be seen from his appearance. He was wearing a set of heavy armor, but his burly figure could not be covered, and he was at least a head taller than Malekith.

Fosters-Slott was the chief Vanguard Official under the Tyrant and had the nicknames of 'War Dragon' and 'the Tyrant's Left-Hand Man'. He was a capable assistant of the Tyrant.

"Do you have anything to add?" Jorde asked with doubt.

Fosters remained expressionless, and he replied with a baleful aura, "I don't care about the others, but Black Star must be mine."

His aura was tyrannical, and the shadow of Heber could be seen in him.

Bloodshed Land had long known that Han Xiao was in Purple Crystal's camp. Black Star was an important officer of Floating Dragon, and both their factions were in conflict. There were many individuals in Bloodshed Land looking forward to fighting Black Star.

Among them, Fosters' killing intent was the greatest.

During the Tyrant's gathering, Han Xiao had trashed Carroll and caused the Tyrant to lose face. Heber would not bother about such a matter, but Fosters worshiped the Tyrant to the point he would never allow anyone to ruin his reputation.

Heber would not pursue the matter, but Fosters would not let the matter rest. Black Star had already entered his kill list, and this secret war would be the best chance.

Of course, the big picture was the most important, and Fosters would not defy orders just because of Black Star.

"As long as I meet Black Star, he will definitely die on the spot!" Fosters said with a resolute tone.

To dare fight in the main camp of Bloodshed Land and beat one of our officers, you are seeking death!

[Magus] Austin was floating within the palace of Hidden Red Robe Abbey and teaching a group of Forbidden Sorcerers theories of magic.

Despite the Star Field being thrown into chaos, his life was still extremely carefree. Since he chose to remain neutral, no one would come and bother him.

After lecturing for a while, Austin suddenly paused and felt his heart skip a beat. He then turned around and looked at the sky outside the palace as though his gaze could see through the boundless galaxy.

Right at that instant, Austin was distracted for a moment, and the image of the Colton Star Cluster and Black Star appeared in his mind.

For a Mage like him who had grasped a secret technique, premonitions would appear in his mind from time to time.

"Colton... Hmm, Klent and Purple Crystal have begun to fight. However, since this matter has nothing to do with me, why would I receive a premonition?" Austin muttered under his breath.

He was uninterested in the secret war between the two Star Cluster Civilizations. The way he saw it, both parties were only trying to snatch territories and weaken the private armed organizations within their own territory. Even if both Klent and Purple Crystal were enemies, they should have a tacit understanding regarding this matter.

Thus, Austin was not willing to work with either of the Star Clusters.

"My premonition should have nothing to do with my war. If that's the case, the reason should be because of Black Star..."

Austin chanted an incantation for a moment and unleashed his mysterious secret technique. After performing a short divination, Austin broke out with a smile of enlightenment.

"I see. It turns out he has my Forbidden Sorcerer under him..."

After thinking for a while, Austin raised his finger and pointed at a few Forbidden Sorcerers present.

"You lot, bring him back. If Black Star stops you, say that it is my intention. He will show me some face."

The few Forbidden Sorcerers who were called upon nodded and walked out of the palace.

Han Xiao gathered all his forces and responded to Section Zero's emergency mobilization. He arrived at the West Wind Star System and met up with the main force of Section Zero.

He brought three hundred modified battleships, Lagi, Herlous, Aroshia, and over ten more Grade B officers. Reynold was in charge of guarding the base, and Sylvia, who was too weak, did not follow them.

He was only participating in the war to farm faction Contribution Points to accumulate his strength. He would not sell his life loyally and sacrifice all the forces that he had spent a great amount of effort to accumulate.

He would just do what he could.

The other members of Section Zero also thought the same. None of them would mobilize all their forces. All of them had their own selfish thoughts, and this was the biggest flaw of an allied organization.

On the contrary, Bloodshed Land did not face such a problem as Heber controlled all the troops.

"This is the benefit of having a beyond Grade A Super." Han Xiao sighed.

A large force was already gathered at the gathering point with almost ten thousand battleships. The Arc Light Organization sent out eight hundred battleships, the most among all the organizations present.

As the leader of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao was also invited to join the conference before the war.

The commander was a member of Purple Crystal. Purple Crystal also knew the cons of having such an allied force and thus sent out a member to command the forces.

In the meeting, Han Xiao understood the situation that they were facing.

Bloodshed Land's vanguard forces had established a bridgehead on an uninhabited planet and set up various defensive measures. The objective of their expedition was to launch a probing attack and attempt to destroy the base of the vanguard force.

Every organization had their own responsibility, and Han Xiao also received his own mission.

[Local Campaign: Pin Down the Enemy Wing]

Mission Introduction: This is the order given to you by your faction. Complete it.

Mission Requirements: Pin down or destroy the battleships of the enemy's wing.

Note: After the battle is over, reward will be given based on the level of completion.

This is a small mission that was a part of the Grade S Main Storyline Mission. In the different battles of the secret war, an elementary objective would first be given such as pinning down the enemy wing in this current mission. During the battle, the mission objective would then change according to the situation on the battlefield, and a new mission would be given.

A war could not be fought by an individual, and the most basic requirement was for him to complete his own mission. As long as he stuck closely to the strategic objectives assigned, a high completion rate would be achieved even if the battle was lost. Farming for faction Contribution Points relied mainly on such tactical missions.

Completing such tactical missions would also increase the mission rating of the Grade S Main Storyline Mission [Secret War: Section Zero].

Han Xiao had only brought three hundred battleships and was not suitable to attack the enemy head on. Thus, he had been assigned to cover the wing. He was not the only party assigned to this mission, and there were a couple others who had the same mission.

After the meeting, Han Xiao walked out of the camp, and someone called out from behind.

The one who had called out for him was Sevitt, a Grade A officer of the Arc Light Organization, the commander of their expedition force.

Sevitt sped up his footsteps and said with a respectful tone, "Black Star, I have something to ask of you."

Han Xiao had the backing of Floating Dragon, and everyone was courteous to him. The majority of them were individuals who had been through many things and would not earn another enemy for themselves for no good reason.

"Go on." Han Xiao only nodded.

"I know that you are a powerful Virtual Mechanic. When you are pinning down the wing of the enemy, I hope that you can interfere to deal with the main force of Bloodshed Land using Virtual Intrusion to reduce our pressure," Sevitt said in an earnest tone.

The Arc Light Organization was in charge of the frontal assault. Sevitt had heard of Han Xiao's abilities and thus went over to request some help.

"This isn't a problem. I will help you if the pressure isn't too great on my side." Han Xiao patted Sevitt on the shoulder.

"Alright. Thanks." Sevitt's eyes lit up.

After both of them parted, Han Xiao returned to his own base and gathered his men to give instructions.

A large-scale war like this was extremely dangerous, and no one would be able to ensure that they could survive. Thus, he got all his subordinates to pay attention to their own safety.

One day later, Section Zero set off for Bloodshed Land's vanguard force.

Chapter 655: The First Battle

The fleet of the Black Star Army was mixed within the combined armed forces, marching forward vigorously. From outside, one could only see the light streaks as a result of the hyperdrive jump, resembling a meteor shower.

"The frontal force is to attack and open up the defensive formations in outer space. Attack the enemy base from space, providing firepower to cover for the other formations. As for us, we will be responsible for flanking, restraining the enemy from their reinforcements."

Within the cockpit, Han Xiao was communicating to the other fleet commanders.

The command structure of the Black Star Army had already been fixed. Out of the three hundred battleships they had, they were divided into multiple fleets, with an Officer in charge of each fleet. This would allow for more flexible tactical adjustments.

"Lagi, I'll pass the mission of charging forward to you. In addition, we have several allies who are sending out Calamity Grade Supers alongside you. Your mission is to kill as many in the opposing fleet as possible. Of course, the priority is to first guarantee your safety."

Han Xiao's tone was stern. During an interstellar war, the Calamity Grades would mainly work to behead the commander of the opposing fleet, usually by assassination. However, they could also enter the main battlefield. Their strong individual fighting capability meant that there would be high flexibility. If there were no other Calamity Grades from the enemy side to restrict them, the Calamity Grade would be able to cause great damage to the fleet, even having the opportunity to influence the situation of a battlefield.

For example, Shana's ability would be a great weapon in such interstellar conditions.

On an interstellar battlefield, Grade A Supers had always been the source of headaches for fleet commanders. This was because their uncertainty was too great, making them hard to handle. A Calamity Grade protected by their fleet was undoubtedly even more dangerous.

However, it was still a dangerous matter for a Calamity Grade to go head on against a fleet. If one was careless, they would be hit by tens of hundreds of warship cannons, and their life would likely be forfeit. However, Han Xiao was reassured by Lagi—he knew how to protect himself, so there should not be a problem.

"Sigh." Lagi only sighed, not speaking out.

Dong dong!

The spaceships trembled slightly and exited hyperdrive. Han Xiao's brows furrowed, and he immediately activated the radar. A red area was marked out in front of them on the radar.

"We're here. In front of us should be the stronghold for the vanguard force of Bloodshed Land."

Han Xiao took a deep breath.

A period of two or three years had passed, but they had still come to war with Bloodshed Land.

In the communication channel, many of the commanders practically held their breath at this sight.

It was not surprising that the members of Section Zero were nervous. The fame of people inevitably cast shadows, and Bloodshed Land had a large reputation, so no one dared look down on this tyrant.

Through the long-range vision, Han Xiao discovered that the Bloodshed Land's fleets had assembled outside, grouping into several formations, each with a flagship as the core.

"Warning, warning, high-energy response detected. Please take precautions, hum!"

At this moment, Han Xiao received the warning from Phillip. Shouting to the others, his fleet dove to evade.

The next moment, Bloodshed Land's fleet suddenly lit up with countless light spots. This was followed by countless beams of high energy particle cannons shooting toward the combined forces. They grazed the shields of the various spaceships before disappearing into the distance. A few of the spaceships that did not have time to escape were hit, their shields flickering intermittently.

"How decisive, firing the moment we meet." Han Xiao's eyes flashed.

Ding.

At this point, Phillip spoke up. "The tactical instructions have been accepted. Do you wish to execute it immediately?"

Within the virtual screen, the formations of both fleets had turned into 3D shapes. The situation was clear at a glance. The tactical movements of his own fleet were marked, with the division of labor clear. Within Han Xiao's troops, each one also had their own tactical targets, and the enemy fleet to be contained had been marked in red. This was their mission. At the top left of his screen were various parameters as well as the timings to meet.

The rear commander would adjust the tactics and reissue new instructions any time according to how the situation developed. This method of command allowed each team to perform its duties without confusion.

Glancing at the tactical board, Han Xiao found it to be acceptable and nodded.

"Execute it immediately!"

The Black Star Army fleet followed the rest of the fleet to move with the troops. After circling once, they dove straight into the fray, heading toward their own targets.

At the same time, the entire Section Zero fleet also moved. They spread out and attacked the planetary stronghold in the battlefield from all directions.

Because the alliance fleet was originally in a state of disunity, in order to prevent any infighting, the commander had organized the alliance fleet into more than ten different squadrons. Han Xiao's fleet belonged to Team Seven, whose main purpose was to restrain and restrict.

The flames of war broke out!

The combined forces of Section Zero approached the planet's fortress from various routes, while the particle cannons of both sides opposed each other. The spaceships navigated their way through the dense net of particle rays, and fireworks bombarded the area from time to time. As the combined forces attacked from multiple fronts, the formation of Bloodshed Land also changed to protect every position instead.

When both sides warred against each other, they opened fire at full blast. Team Seven charged bravely against the fire, and the pressure they faced increased sharply the closer they got.

Boom boom boom!

The vanguard troops of Bloodshed Land had transformed their fortress planet using the foundations of the Crimson Dynasty. The ground had a large base, and anti-aircraft guns fired physical missiles that could hit even spaceships in outer space. The firepower within them was fierce, and they almost hit Han Xiao's fleet more than once.

"A large-scale battlefield is really dangerous."

Han Xiao had long switched over to manual piloting, placing his full concentration on this matter. He performed thrilling aerial moves one after another to avoid any the tens of cannons fired toward them.

With such a large-scale battlefield, he did not dare act too casually. He followed the actions of the main troops, avoiding the various attacks by constantly fluttering up and down like a butterfly.

Looking at the tactical screen, he found out that the assault troops had already begun to clash in close combat with those from Bloodshed Land. Looking out of the window, he saw that the entire outer space area had turned into a fierce battlefield, with the inky black color of the universe as well as the edge of the fortress planet as a backdrop. Both sides were heavily engaged with each other, and all sorts of lights from the weapons dazzled one's eyes.

The battlefield was too vast. Even casting one's eyes out into the horizon would not allow them to see the entire situation. They could only understand the whole battle through the feedback from the tactical screen. At present, both sides had just confronted each other and were evenly matched.

The allied forces offensive had restrained the enemy's firepower, indirectly helping Han Xiao's Team Seven approach the enemy and find their restraining targets.

Han Xiao's current position quickly turned into a small-scale battlefield.

The moment they fought, Han Xiao felt tremendous pressure.

This fleet, with an expedition-class battleship as its core, seemed to be about to go support the frontal battlefield. Team Seven restrained and harassed them continuously and were immediately violently counterattacked.

Team Seven had about a thousand battleships, of which three hundred were Han Xiao's. The death toll was increasing rapidly.

"Not good!" Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

While the Purple Crystal Civilization had mentioned that there would be compensation, Han Xiao could not bear to see the battleships exploding one after another. They were his assets that he had spent much time accumulating.

He activated the Virtual Intrusion skill but immediately encountered resistance. The fleet opposing them had also deployed Virtual Mechanics to protect their fleet. In addition, they also planned to invade the Alliance fleet's spaceships.

Left without a choice, Han Xiao could only tussle with the Virtual Mechanics from the enemy side, attacking and defending. Both sides started a tug-of-war.

At the same time, within the command room of the fortress planet, two Grade A Virtual Mechanics were intercepted by Han Xiao on the virtual level, and their looks changed.

"The enemy's Virtual Mechanic has also appeared!"

"Sh*t, this guy's Virtual Technology is really strong. The infiltration speed is too fast!"

"Luckily, we still can keep the internal firewall. Did you manage to trace the source?"

"Yeah, I've locked down on his position."

"I see it, eh, turns out its Black Star. No wonder, he's so strong!"

"Cooperate with me. Fight and seize his spaceship!"

The cooperation of the two was tacit. They immediately locked onto Han Xiao, infiltrating his Blacklight Stealth.

Within the Virtual Plane, the torrent of data manipulated by the duo found the artificial intelligence core of the Blacklight Stealth. Just as they were about to launch an attack, a glowing figure materialized. It was Risda.

Looking at the two torrents of data surging toward him, Risda merely raised a hand, scattering the offensive of both men. The data torrents turned into tiny sparkles of light, becoming redundant pieces of data, and were quickly shattered.

The moment the duo saw this, their hearts chilled.

"This Artificial intelligence is too high level. There's no way to break through it."

"Dammit, now we can't shake him off."

Both sides had undergone a round of confrontation, with Han Xiao gaining a slight advantage. However, his expression remained grave.

He had long expected the Bloodshed Land to employ Virtual Mechanics, as there was no way they would leave out such an obvious shortcoming. However, the enemy had actually sent two Grade A Virtual Mechanics, which gave Han Xiao some pressure. If he was not present, the opponent would have been free to do whatever they wished.

At this point, both sides were restraining each other. Although he could not utilize Virtual Intrusion to hack into the other party, it was the same for them.

The two sides finally met each other in close combat, and a furious battle erupted. Team Seven and the enemy fleet both used their charge cabins, allowing their respective Supers to land on the enemy's spaceships.

Han Xiao pulled up a surveillance video. Any battleship on his side that got boarded would face a one-sided slaughter, as the elite Thousand Beast Soldier troops from the Bloodshed Land were extremely strong.

"My spaceship has been boarded!"

At this point, the frantic voice of Herlous sounded from his communicator.

Han Xiao hurriedly switched screens, only to see three charge cabins firmly latching onto Herlous' spaceship. Herlous brought out his troops and was currently engaging with the enemy Thousand Beast Soldiers.

Luckily, Lagi's spaceship passed by at this juncture and provided assistance. They killed off the bunch of enemies with ease, resolving the danger in Herlous' spaceship.

Han Xiao suddenly felt his emotions surge. Within the chaos, he had accidentally discovered a breakthrough point.

"Attention to all, cover the Calamity Grade assault team. Try and allow them to land on the enemy's flagship!"

Within this small-scale battlefield, the core would be the flagship of both parties. Compared to the enemy, Team Seven had the advantage with their Calamity Grade Supers, so their commander beheading operation had a higher chance of success.

Although their tactical goal was to restrain this fleet, the main commander would only give the target, and the specific actions were adjusted according to circumstances. It would definitely be more useful to destroy the opponent's flagship rather than simply restraining them.

If one could obtain stellar results, the reward would naturally be higher.

Team Seven's Calamity Grade assault teams, including Lagi, consisted of four teams. Han Xiao was not included.

When the order was issued, Team Seven immediately changed positions and began to cover the Calamity Grade assault team. They shuttled through the artillery bombing, quickly approaching the enemy's flagship.

The enemy naturally spotted the tactical objective of Han Xiao and worked on intercepting the teams as well as covering their flagship to allow it to retreat.

While the distance between both sides was shrinking, it was too slow. Instead, the battlefield was slowly moving toward the frontlines. God only knew when they would reach the enemy flagship if that continued. So, making up his mind, he issued a new order.

"All Calamity Grade teams, board my Giant Soldier. I'll take you there!"

The next instant, Han Xiao popped out of his spaceship, summoning his destroyer and sitting within the cockpit. Lagi and the others quickly got into the body of the Giant Soldier.

"Sit tight."

Han Xiao operated the destroyer, pouring all its power into the thruster as it rushed toward the enemy's flagship at a high speed.

The Giant Soldiers had more mobility and flexibility. Coupled with Han Xiao's high operating level, he moved and penetrated deep into the enemy's lines, attracting a lot of retaliatory fire. However, most of the attacks shot at him harmlessly, and some almost caused friendly fire.

Their distance was reduced at a speed visible to the naked eye!

It was a taboo in battle to operate independently, but Han Xiao was a Calamity Grade himself, and he was accompanied by four other Calamity Grade Supers. This turned them into a sharp sword with frightening power, causing the enemies to focus fire on them. Team Seven, which remained outside, immediately reacted, further restraining this fleet.

The destroyer finally arrived at the flagship and activated the shield neutralizer. They opened the hatch, allowing the four teams to successfully infiltrate the flagship. With only a single Calamity Grade Super within, they were bound to die.

Han Xiao did not sit idle, instead controlling his Giant Soldier to slice up the spaceships around him into pieces.

It was not long before the flagship could not withstand the impact and exploded!

However, the four teams had already evacuated, boarding Han Xiao's Giant Soldier once again, and they broke out of the enemy lines.

While Han Xiao had succeeded in destroying the flagship, the armor value of his destroyer had almost reached zero. If not for his team that remained outside harassing and restraining, he would probably have lost his destroyer to the sheer firepower.

However, this small setback had reversed the situation on this minor battlefield. Under the continuous attacks of the team, the enemy troops began to retreat.

Han Xiao was just about to give pursuit, but at this time, he suddenly received a new mission notification.

[Partial Campaign: Retreat]

Mission Requirements: Retreat immediately, and conserve as much of team as possible

"Why are we retreating now‽"

Han Xiao jumped in shock, casting his eyes out on the tactical screen. His pupils shrank.

On all the minor battlefields, only his one had gained an advantage!

The situation on the frontal battlefield had deteriorated rapidly. The large force of Section Zero was penetrated by Bloodshed Land, and more than two thousand warships had been destroyed. The main force of fifteen Calamity Grade Supers had suffered eight deaths, with seven injured.

All eight Vanguard Officials of the Bloodshed Land had entered the fray!

"No wonder I didn't even encounter any of them!"

Han Xiao's heart sank.

With the main force being destroyed, even if he had an advantage on his side, it would not help.

Section Zero had battled Bloodshed Land for the first time and lost!

On the main battlefield, a burning arc flew through the flagship of the organization. There were corpses everywhere, and blood flowed like a river.

Puchi.

Hunting Blade pulled out his war blade, and Sevitt's body fell heavily. There was a huge hole in his side, with his internal organs already gone, and his blood had almost dried out. He was deader than dead at this point.

"This should be the last one. Let's go. The battleship is about to explode."

Hunting Blade wiped his blade and spoke through the communicator at the side of his armor toward Fosters, who was near the hole at the hull of the ship.

Fosters was looking through a hole to the distant battlefields. The horrible vacuum suction did not affect his body one bit.

"Black Star is not on the frontal battlefield. He should count his blessings."

Fosters' eyes gleamed coldly.

Chapter 656: Danger Is Equal to Opportunity

After retreating based on the command and moving far away from the fortress planet of Bloodshed Land, Han Xiao then learned of the number of casualties on the frontal battlefield.

"Such heavy casualties‽"

After Bloodshed Land defeated the Alliance Fleet in the frontal battle, they had returned to their bridgehead and symbolically pursued the defeated frontal units of Section Zero for a while. However, because Han Xiao had been victorious on his minor battlefield, he had easily led his people to retreat, and the enemy did not pursue them.

Han Xiao had won a small victory, but it was a pity that this would not affect the overall war.

Despite the defeat in their war, Han Xiao's tactical mission was considered completed, awarding him with millions of experience and more than two hundred Contribution Points from Section Zero as well as the Purple Crystal Civilization.

The defeated Alliance fleet stopped on a barren planet to rest. The atmosphere within was sorrowful and solemn, with many of the allies pulling long faces at the deaths of their comrades.

The dead Grade A Supers had practically exploded together with their flagship. The Arc Light Organization had lost Sevitt, and the surviving members had grieving expressions.

Just two days prior, Sevitt had still been smiling as he requested them to help out, but now, even his bones could not be found. Thinking of this, Han Xiao could not help but sigh. However, he did not disturb the surviving members. Instead, he assembled his Officers to count the losses of his own fleet. Very quickly, the result came.

"We only lost 34 battleships, and there were no casualties from the high-levelled combatants. The situation is still good."

Han Xiao sighed in relief.

The Purple Crystal Civilization would compensate the various forces for their losses, or else there would be no one willing to cooperate with them. The battleships that Han Xiao had lost would also be replaced. In addition, he would also receive an additional reward from the department.

With some lingering fear, Herlous said, "I just went around to ask, and we actually have some of the lowest casualties within Section Zero. Our allies even lost a few of their Calamity Grades... I didn't know it would be this dangerous."

"Indeed, this was out of our expectations." Han Xiao nodded. He was experiencing the situation before it had taken shape in Version 3.0, and this secret war was where the game versions were moving toward. However, he had currently only seen the background of the plot and was not clear on the specific details.

As for the victory of Bloodshed Land, Han Xiao was not surprised. If the Purple Crystal Civilization could topple them so easily, there would have been no need for Version 3.0.

During Version 3.0, Bloodshed Land had already built many bases across multiple planets, and a game of tug-of-war had been established between them and Section Zero. Han Xiao could guess that during the version update, Section Zero would definitely be at a disadvantage.

What he was surprised about was that, for the first battle, to have a death count of ten Grade As on their side was a little unbelievable.

If so many people would die in every war, it would not take a few months for all the Supers in Section Zero to die off. Bloodshed Land would also have heavy casualties, so both sides would lose out.

Beep beep!

Han Xiao suddenly received a communication request from Ralph.

After connecting, Ralph's voice came through, sounding hoarse and full of static. "Black Star, how bad is the situation?"

After receiving the news of the failure in the war, Ralph could not help but contact Han Xiao to ask about the details.

"Extremely bad..."

Han Xiao recounted everything he knew and conveniently emphasized that his battlefield had an advantage.

Hearing this, Ralph got worried. "This is the only good news I've heard in the last hour. However, you cannot determine the outcome just by yourself."

Han Xiao shrugged in response. He did not care; in any case, he would still receive his due compensation, so he did not lose out in any way.

"The objective of Bloodshed Land is to kill all our Grade A Supers. They're trying to showcase their strength," Ralph said.

Han Xiao's eyes shone, and he immediately understood the intentions of Heber, secretly exclaiming to himself how ingenious this idea was.

Bloodshed Land had seized the greatest weakness of Section Zero—a lack of unity. This was a common problem among allied forces. Because each Grade A Super was the core of their own respective organizations, the eight vanguard officials had rushed out to kill all those top tier combatants so as to make the people within Section Zero fear the repercussions of their actions.

Every collaborator of Section Zero did not really care whether Purple Crystal held onto their territory. They had no territorial fondness, unlike the Purple Crystal Civilization, and were only there because of the benefits. Winning or losing the war was irrelevant to them, and the only thing they cared about was whether the benefits outweighed the losses.

If they battleships received damage, the Purple Crystal Civilization could compensate them and even reward them, allowing them to receive the resources of the Star Cluster Civilization. However, if their Calamity Grades were killed, there was nothing they could do about it. The Purple Crystal Civilization was unable to replace the loss of their high-level combatants.

This was the difference between Section Zero, which was in a state of disunity, and the cohesive Bloodshed Land, and it was a weakness that they could not change.

No wonder Bloodshed Land fought so fiercely.

Han Xiao groaned secretly. He did not care if the secret war was successful. In his previous life, the Purple Crystal Civilization had been destroyed, and only when the Crimson Dynasty had come to an agreement with the Federation of Light did they finally put a stop to all the wars that they had incited.

Before both Universal Civilizations completed their benefits exchange, no one would bother about the secret war between Klent and Purple Crystal. The Crimson Dynasty was Klent's backer, so as long as Klent was not driven away, the Crimson Dynasty would split off a part of the land belonging to Purple Crystal and give it to them. This was Klent's strategy and the result of his past life.

Han Xiao's motive for joining Section Zero was not to help Purple Crystal win the war but rather to exchange his contributions for Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

If his losses were kept to the minimum, he did not mind keeping strictly to his designated tasks to complete the missions, slowly increasing his favorability to [Reverence].

Even if the broader picture was affected, as long as his 'stocks' in Purple Crystal continued to rise, he would still receive more attention and respect.

If people above did not die, how would he have a chance to move up?

A gleam shot through Han Xiao's eyes. It was a pity the players were not there. That way, he would not have needed to care about deaths and injuries.

Putting aside his thoughts, Han Xiao said, "Bloodshed Land is still gaining a foothold in the West Wind Star System. What do we do next?"

"We'll take a break for now. Wait for the reinforcements to arrive before we attack once more," Ralph gravely replied.

The collaborators of Section Zero were located in various sectors of the Colton Star Cluster, with some only needing a short journey to arrive, whereas others took longer. Han Xiao belonged to the first batch of the allied troops and could be considered more of a vanguard force for Section Zero. The main force was still behind, so the failure of the vanguard force did not mean that Section Zero had been completely defeated.

Ralph was more worried about the tactics utilized by Bloodshed Land. For the enemy to target their powerful combatants, this could not be defended. He was worried that Section Zero would not put in any effort to cut their losses, with the worst outcome being the disbandment of the entire Section.

Han Xiao took a few deep breaths before suddenly speaking. "I have a suggestion. The next attack, let me hold the frontal battlefield."

Ralph froze in shock. Black Star, despite knowing of the dangers, still chose to volunteer for the main battlefield‽

"You, what you mean is..."

"Maybe I can hold off the Vanguard Officials of Bloodshed Land..." Han Xiao stroked his chin.

Ralph was overjoyed to the point he wanted to cry. Just now, the forces participating in the main battlefield, such as the Arc Light Organization, had demanded that they no longer assume the task of attacking as the frontal force. They did not dare face the Bloodshed Land Officials. Only Black Star was willing to step up and handle such a risky job.

This... this was the true meaning of a reliable cooperator!

Ralph held back his tears of joy, excitedly asking, "How many can you fend off?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "All of them."

Ralph's eyes bulged wide, incredulity plastered all over his face.

Are you f*cking kidding me‽

This is no laughing matter!

"Don't be too surprised. I never said I could beat them all. I only said that I can hold them off."

Han Xiao waved his hand. He had calculated it a while ago. Against the eight Vanguard Officials, his chances of winning against them probably would only exceed Lagi's by a minute amount. However, with his meat shield like capabilities, he was more than qualified to hold off the eight of them. Furthermore, he could still utilize Aurora's Character Summon Card, so he only needed to maintain a battle.

With him stalling the Vanguard Officials, it could lower the risk that the allied combatants would face. Furthermore, showing such strength would allow him to gain a wave of reputation, which would result in more attention being paid to him by the Purple Crystal Civilization.

The most important reason was that Han Xiao planned to use this to strike a deal.

"To take such a huge risk, I won't do it for free."

"What do you want?" Ralph immediately asked.

Han Xiao's brows rose. "I want the Cutting-Edge Knowledge for the Mechanic profession."

"Deal!" Ralph immediately agreed.

At this time, he no longer hesitated. Black Star was already willing to bear the risk of death. As long as he could survive, the Purple Crystal Civilization need not be stingy with their resources.

Han Xiao's expression did not change, but he was secretly exhilarated. Although he could lie low and slowly increase his favorability, the time taken would be longer. As long as he could reach for the skies in one single leap, he would not let go of this chance to obtain the Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

The sooner he completed his Class Advancement, the faster he would be able to break through to level 170, converting all his accumulated experience into actual combat capability. Furthermore, being able to hold back eight Vanguard Officials was a matter of reputation and prestige. He would kill two birds with one stone!

Han Xiao could not help but give rise to a wicked idea. He would rather the Purple Crystal Civilization lose more and win less. If the situation was not so dire, he would not have had a chance to obtain the resources that he wanted this quickly.

"Indeed, opportunities only exist in chaotic times. The ancient sages did not lie." Han Xiao laughed to himself.

Standing by the side, Lagi heard the conversation and could not help but interject. "Do you need me to collect your corpse?"

Han Xiao was not angry but rather happy instead. It seemed like this would work. Lagi's counterproductive comments had never failed before.

"Continue commenting, don't stop."

"No wonder you really want to commit suicide. You're really mad." Lagi sighed to himself. It seemed like he needed to change employers once more.

Chapter 657: Gloat When Winning, Hide When Losing

At the same time, the vanguard force of Bloodshed Land had summarized the outcome of the battle.

"We fought back a wave of attacks. All of you did well and got rid of quite a few Calamity Grade Supers. Purple Crystal's allied force will definitely be wary after this."

Jorde praised the result of the battle.

Hunting Blade nodded. "The enemy only launched a hasty attack and didn't send out too many high-level troops. Your prediction was right."

The vanguard force had prepared many different war strategies. Their original strategy had been to focus on defense, but upon observing that Section Zero did not send out an overwhelming force in their first attack, Jorde had switched strategies and gotten the eight Vanguard Officials to take action together. They had managed to take out a large number of Section Zero's high-level combatants and achieve the effect of frightening the others.

"We should have about ten days until the enemy's next attack. All of you should continue to deal with the high-level combatants of the enemy. This is the weakness of an allied army," Jorde said with confidence.

Hunting Blade frowned in response. "With their first failure, the enemy will not underestimate us anymore and may not even be willing to fight us head on. We may not have such a chance again in the future."

"Then we will have to create the chance," Fosters, who was by the side, suddenly said. "If the enemy doesn't send their high-level combatants to fight us, we will dismantle their entire fleet."

Jorde nodded in agreement. "In any case, try to find the opportunity to kill as many high-level combatants as possible. The more terrified our enemy is, the lower the difficulty of our expansion."

"Black Star should be participating in the next attack as well. I have a request," Fosters suddenly said. "Everyone must send me the coordinates of Black Star's location. If the frontal assault team doesn't need me, I will go and get rid of Black Star."

"Alright," Jorde replied, "but don't let your private grudge affect the overall situation."

"Humph, I don't need you to remind me about that. Furthermore, this isn't my private grudge," Fosters said coldly. "Black Star is Dragon Emperor's subordinate. Getting rid of him will also force Dragon Emperor out. Only then can His Excellency Heber participate in the war openly."

The presence of a beyond Grade A Super served as a deterrent, and they would rarely take action. Even if the Tyrant was the leader of Bloodshed Land, he did not personally participate in the war. However, if Ames took action, he would have an excuse to participate.

In their eyes, the Tyrant was obviously stronger than the Dragon Emperor.

Everyone's eyes lit up.

Jorde nodded and said, "That makes sense. I shall hand him to you."

"Don't worry, I will be able to find him no matter where he hides." Fosters nodded with satisfaction.

...

As the allied army was waiting for their reinforcements, a couple of riots broke out. With the Arc Light Organization at the helm, the various members of the frontal assault party requested to have a change of mission with the reason being their heavy losses.

Sevitt's death had shocked the entire Arc Light Organization with their leader being filled with regret. Sevitt had been his capable assistant, and he had trusted Sevitt greatly. However, he had never imagined that Sevitt would perish in the very first battle, and the leader had immediately suggested backing out. All the other organizations who were part of the frontal assault group had experienced varying degrees of loss to their high-level combatants.

Such an intense battle was completely out of their expectations, and the eight Vanguard Officials had truly scared them out of their wits.

Perhaps they might have been able to defeat the Vanguard Officials if they worked together, but none of them were willing to lose their Calamity Grade Supers. As such, they had all tacitly agreed to avoid the battle.

This was a problem without a solution. The commander of Section Zero could only reorganize the battle formation and change the members in charge of frontal assault, hoping that the reinforcements would be willing to take up the responsibility.

However, the reinforcements also heard of the death count on the frontline and were not willing to take up the role. None of them were willing to sacrifice their high-level combatants.

The Purple Crystal Civilization was extremely helpless and only managed to get a few organizations to grudgingly accept the job after some private negotiations.

The strategy of Bloodshed Land was extremely effective, exposing the weakness of Section Zero in a single battle. Even if the members of Section Zero were famous armed organizations from the Colton Star Cluster, they were no more than a mob when gathered together.

However, Han Xiao was not disappointed that he would only have the opportunity to display his abilities when his faction was at a disadvantage.

Just when everyone was trying to avoid taking up the assault role, Han Xiao was the only one who volunteered for the job.

This piece of news quickly spread throughout the entire camp and set off a huge wave of commotion. Everyone looked at Han Xiao with strange looks filled with doubt, shock, and many other emotions.

Despite knowing that he would face a huge risk, Black Star still volunteered for the job. Did he lose his mind?

The few organizations that had already lost their comrades all watched from the side coldly. They all misunderstood Black Star's intentions and felt that he was trying to step on their heads to display his brilliance so that Purple Crystal would think highly of him.

While this in itself was not a problem, the problem was that Black Star did not have the corresponding strength to perform such a feat. It was no different from seeking his own death. Did he not have any brains at all?

Many organizations in the allied army immediately came to a common understanding. In order to raise his status, Black Star did not want to live anymore.

However, not a single organization bothered to advise Black Star about anything. They needed someone to serve as cannon fodder at the front, and since Black Star was willing to die, they would not stop him.

Since Han Xiao had volunteered for such a dangerous mission, Ralph tried to fulfil almost every request of his. Han Xiao did not allow his subordinates to join the assault and got Lagi to lead Herlous and the others to participate in other less intense battles.

A few days later, the second batch of reinforcements finally arrived, and Section Zero's allied army attacked the few bases that Bloodshed Land had in the West Wind Star System again.

Han Xiao got Herlous to command their forces temporarily while he formed the spearhead of the assault force with the Blacklight Stealth.

The objective of his mission this time was to pin down the eight Vanguard Official and the reward was Cutting-Edge Knowledge and a large amount of faction contribution points. The reward from this single mission was comparable to more than ten ordinary missions.

Because of their previous failure, Section Zero's second assault attempt was being watched by the entire Star Field.

The other five Star Cluster Civilization of the Shattered Star Ring as well as some large organizations within the Star Field all focused their attention on the West Wind Star System. The outcome of the second exchange between both parties would be extremely indicative of the outcome of the secret war.

...

This was the second time that they had fought, and both Bloodshed Land and Section Zero were fully prepared. The battle between both parties had immediately shot to the peak without any foreplay.

Bright balls of flames lit up the pitch-black universe. The burning battleships, exploding cannons, and blinding laser cannons filled the entire battlefield.

The eight Vanguard Official with Fosters in the lead destroyed one battleship after another and swept through the battlefield with unstoppable momentum.

Rather than send out their high-level combatants to stop the Vanguard Officials, the Calamity Grade Supers from Section Zero all chose to avoid the battle and watch as the Vanguard Officials destroyed their battleships.

"Why are all of you in a daze! Stop them!" the commander roared.

"Roger, we will take action soon."

"This isn't the time yet. Wait for them to expend some energy first."

The Grade A Supers all gave perfunctory replies.

Despite the commander being thoroughly enraged, he was also utterly helpless. He was helpless if these high-level combatants chose to go against his orders. Furthermore, knowing that Purple Crystal would compensate them for their lost battleships, they would rather watch their own fleet get destroyed than take action.

Ralph could no longer sit still. Despite knowing that the situation was bad, he did not expect it to be so terrible. Thus, he could not help but contact Han Xiao.

"Black Star, we can't rely on the others. When will you take action? We will be defeated for sure if this continues."

In the cockpit, Han Xiao looked at the coordinates of the eight Vanguard Officials and replied, "Give me a battlefield."

"I understand!" Ralph was overjoyed.

He still doubted the fact that Black Star would be able to hold all eight Vanguard Officials back alone but had no choice but to believe Black Star.

...

At the center of the battlefield, the Vanguard Officials were having the time of their lives as they destroyed one battleship after another and disrupted the formation of Section Zero.

The eight Vanguard Officials were like leopards and the battleships like sheep. Without the high-level combatants pinning down the Vanguard Officials, the battleships were reduced to sitting ducks.

"Haha, the enemy Calamity Grade Supers still aren't taking action. Do they truly not care about their fleet at all?"

Malekith burst into laughter in the communication channel.

"What a bunch of cowards. They don't even have the guts to fight," Hunting Blade sneered with disdain.

Boom!

In the interior of a battleship, Fosters crushed half the spaceship with his fists and boarded an assault spaceship before the battleship exploded. Upon hearing the conversation, he could not help but ask, "Why hasn't anyone reported Black Star's location to me yet? Where exactly is he?"

"I don't know. No one has reported Black Star's location yet. We managed to find the Black Star Army fleet, but Black Star isn't part of the fleet. There is only a Grade A mage controlling the situation."

Fosters glanced at the battlefield and coldly said, "Since the enemy's high-level combatants are a bunch of cowards, I am not needed for the time being. I will go to the Black Star Army. He will definitely be hiding in the vicinity."

"Okay, go ahead and leave matters here to us." Hunting Blade nodded in response.

Just as Fosters wanted to leave the area, the battleship formation suddenly spread out to reveal a passage, and the Blacklight Stealth flew out from deep within the formation.

"That is... Black Star‽"

Fosters stopped abruptly with his gaze being fixed on the Blacklight Stealth. The other seven Vanguard Officials could not help but look over as well.

Han Xiao then left his spaceship wearing his Berserk Ape suit and floated in space. He looked at the eight Vanguard Officials and raised his hand to beckon for them in provocation.

A single individual in the vast battlefield was far too tiny, but not a single person in the surroundings could ignore Han Xiao's presence. He unleashed his energy, and the high energy reading being given off from him was sufficient to set off the radar of any battleship around him.

Despite being far away from Han Xiao, Fosters and the others could clearly see Han Xiao's actions.

"He is provoking us?"

Hunting Blade was dumbfounded. He truly did not know who gave Black Star the courage to provoke them.

Fosters could not help but be surprised. He had thought that Black Star was hiding like the other Calamity Grade Supers and had never expected him to step out on his own.

"Not bad. At least he is more courageous than the others. Saves me some time."

Fosters' eyes narrowed, and he instructed the assault spaceship to charge for Han Xiao. He then jumped out from the spaceship and shot toward Han Xiao with his entire body burning with flames like a dark red meteor.

Han Xiao raised his arm, and the parts on his mechanical suit expanded out to form a gigantic mechanical fist that was a hundred meters in size. Bolts of Mechanical Force covered the fist ,and his fist hammered down on the meteor.

Sound would not be produced in the vacuum of space, and everyone could only visualize the sound of the collision in their heads.

Bang!

The gigantic fist was penetrated by the meteor to reveal a human sized hole, and Fosters' fist arrived at Han Xiao's chest.

Han Xiao was forced to retreat, and his body flew backward a short distance before he could stabilize himself. He then waved his arm to unequip the destroyed mechanical hand.

"Show me everything you have and let me have a good time." Fosters sent Han Xiao a voice message to the mechanical suit's communication system.

Leaving a voice message in a fight... This fellow is truly annoying.

Han Xiao then waved his arm, and the hatch to the Blacklight Stealth opened up. His Mechanical Army then swarmed out of the spaceship like a swarm of locusts.

Very quickly, his army revealed itself, and tens of thousands of machines floated beside him.

Such an army was not to be underestimated!

Because Purple Crystal would compensate him for his losses, Han Xiao did not hold anything back and sent out all his machines.

"The eight of you can come together. You won't be able to deal with me alone." Han Xiao returned the favor and sent Fosters a voice message, too.

Fosters sneered coldly and could not be bothered to reply. Black Star was already a dead man in his eyes, and he alone was enough to get rid of this pest.

The Calamity Grade Supers of Section Zero were skiving off at the side, and not a single person seems to have any intention of helping Black Star.

Up until now, Han Xiao was the only Calamity Grade Super from Section Zero who had stepped out onto the main battlefield!

Chapter 658: Fighting Eight People Alone!

Let's end this fast, thought Fosters, and intense flames immediately spread out from him, akin to the surface of a small star. Pushing forward with both of his palms at the tens of thousands of mechanical soldiers, a dark red beam struck toward Han Xiao and the Mechanical Army that surrounded him.

The outer layer of mechanical soldiers was directly blasted away, shattering into metal pieces. The debris was blown away like sand particles being washed away by the tide.

The cannon fodder machines could not stop the assault of the Grade A+ Fosters. Only the Oathkeepers beside Han Xiao stepped forward, deploying their shields to withstand the shockwave blast from Fosters.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and his Mechanical Force rolled outward. Under the influence of [Mechanical Force Field], he covered all his mechanical soldiers. The next moment, he waved his hands, and the hundreds of thousands of mechanical soldiers opened fire at the same time, attacking Fosters with different formations and different tactical modes.

A fierce battle unfolded!

The vast Mechanical Army drowned Fosters. Right in the middle of the main battlefield, a smaller scale battlefield was formed. The fleets were still engaged with each other all around them, and Bloodshed Land did not care about a one on one battle, constantly firing toward Black Star's Mechanical Army. However, Section Zero was not a group to be trifled.

While the rest of the Calamity Grades were watching the show, they still had the courage to command the fleet to provide enough cover for Han Xiao.

Moreover, surrounding the machinery were numerous floating shields, which blocked the attacks from time to time.

This was the all-out attack of a Mechanic at the Calamity Grade. A person could rival an entire fleet!

However, Han Xiao had placed all his attention on Fosters.

Millions of ion cannon rays crisscrossed, like a large airtight net, which continuously struck at Fosters. He dodged continuously and rammed through when he could not, relying on the sheer power of his Pugilist flames to also wreak havoc in the mechanical soldier army.

The armor of conventional mechanical soldiers was akin to paper in front of Fosters' strength. In a battle between the Grade As, the role of the basic mechanical soldiers was just to provide firepower and tactical containment, as well as to continuously sap at the opponents' health and strength. Under the bonus given by Han Xiao's Mechanical Force, Fosters could only try to evade most of the time. Being bombarded by tens of thousands of concentrated firepower was nothing to scoff at.

While he might have been confident to endure it with his current strength, should he not treat himself better if possible?

As for the main combat force, it would be the small number of Grade A Elite Machinery, such as the improved versions of the Oathkeeper, Phantoms, and so on. The strength of a single unit naturally could not exceed that of the Calamity Grade itself, but their mutual cooperation would be able to threaten them. Even with their famed reputation within the Star Field, the Tyrant's Vanguard Officials would not be able to blast away an Oathkeeper that was equipped with sufficient shields, energy, and thick armor in just two or three punches.

Han Xiao strolled leisurely among his Mechanical Army, but his walking speed was extremely fast. Coupled with his sudden change in direction, it caused Fosters to be unable to lock onto him.

However, Fosters did not dare pause, constantly maintaining his high evasion speed as he avoided the various attacks while analyzing the situation quickly in his heart.

Got to look for a chance to behead him in one fell swoop, or else I'll be drowned by this human wave tactic.

It was not as if Fosters had not come into contact with any Mechanics specializing in the Army Style. He understood that once he was completely surrounded, he would be tortured to death sooner or later. One could not look down on the damage ten thousand soldiers could deal.

As for the weakness of the Army Style... if the commander was beheaded, the rest of the soldiers would easily be broken through.

Black Star has the moniker of Indestructible Body... however, he cannot be more difficult to deal with than the Mechanical Army itself.

Fosters stared closely before drastically increasing his speed using a skill. Flames blazed around him, and like a dark red bolt, he bashed through layers of mechanical soldiers to arrive beside Han Xiao, swinging a mighty fist filled with endless power toward Han Xiao's neck.

The split second that the fist was supposed to connect, Han Xiao's figure suddenly flickered, and the next instant, he was at another location within his Mechanical Army. This was his Advanced Void Travel.

It continued the same way. Every time Fosters launched an attack on Han Xiao, it would end up being easily neutralized by the latter. With Void Travel, [Chaos Entity—Release] as well as the Short Distance Teleporter Module on his Berserk Ape on continuous cycle, Fosters had no way to touch even his clothes. The shockwave blasts were avoided even more easily.

Fosters' face got uglier as time passed. According to the intelligence received, he had thought that Han Xiao would choose to fight with him given his sturdy body, but he did not expect the latter to be as slippery as an eel.

As for Han Xiao, his thoughts were clear. Since I'm a Mechanic, before my Mechanical Army is depleted, there's no need for me to rush up and get beaten up like an idiot.

His fleshly body was his trump card, and of course, he had to use it only as the last resort. His mission was to restrain the eight Vanguard Officials. By trapping Fosters within the Mechanical Army, he would make the guy feel unbearable, allowing him to call the rest over for him to restrain.

If not, just based off his fleshy body, while Fosters might not be able to kill him, he would be completely suppressed and beaten down without any chance to retaliate. In that case, he could not appear as carefree as he was now.

Han Xiao's was considering this in the long term. As long as he completed this mission successfully, he would obtain the Cutting-Edge Knowledge needed for his Class Advancement. Destroying his entire Mechanical Army would give him an excuse to withdraw from the war for the current period of time, allowing him to go back and create a brand-new Mechanical Army with new and improved capabilities.

The Purple Crystal Civilization would naturally overcompensate him for his loss.

Since he knew that the expansion of Bloodshed Land was inevitable, with the current performance of Section Zero, they would be constantly defeated for the time being. There was no need for him to participate in a losing battle. It was better for him to go home and recuperate.

When the situation became bad and Purple Crystal started to panic, they would think of his performance before automatically asking him to participate. Only then would he take the opportunity to extort them.

While Han Xiao liked to utilize the Army Style, he also loved to personally enter the scene. However, this time, he had chosen to utilize conventional tactics, revealing his frightening evasion abilities to foil Fosters' sudden advancement. The power of his Army Style was revealed to the fullest!

Although the losses of the Mechanical Army were constantly rising, Fosters' energy consumption was also becoming severe. When facing hundreds of thousands of Mechanical soldiers, it caused a qualitative change as a result of the quantity. Unless one had a special tank-like ability, no one would be able to endure the entire group.

The damaged machinery was revived again and again by Han Xiao using both [Waste Modification] and [Machinery Continuation], and the soldiers appeared endless.

Both sides could see that Fosters appeared like a bug trapped within a spider's web, completely falling into Black Star's tempo. The Mechanical Army blessed by Han Xiao's Mechanical Force as well as the [Superhuman] buff provided a 142% increase in damage at Level 170. This had greatly offset Fosters' strength advantage.

"He's managed to restrain the Chief Vanguard Official!"

There were quite a few Grade A Supers in Section Zero, and they all obtained a boost in their spirits.

To have Black Star's capabilities rival the Chief Vanguard Official, this was good news.

However, no one was too surprised. With Black Star's fame, many of his deeds had already spread among the people in the galaxy. He was also recognized to be one of the strongest members under the Dragon Emperor Ames. Thus, it was not surprising that he was able to match the Chief Vanguard Official of the Tyrant in power.

However, Ralph was a little worried. Black Star had promised him that he would restrain all eight of them, but currently, only Fosters was being trapped. The other Vanguard Officials were still moving around and destroying the warships. If not for the fact that Black Star was wrapped up in an intense battle, he would have urged a retreat.

After dodging yet another round of cannon fire, Fosters' gaze wandered toward Han Xiao, feeling extremely stifled.

The difficulty in killing Black Star proved to be far out of his expectations.

Fosters still felt that Black Star was not a match for him. In his opinion, as long as he managed to snatch a chance, he would definitely obtain victory. However, the two of them had been fighting for so long that it had run counter to his original intention of ending the battle quickly. Unable to resist getting angry, his patience had long been worn thin.

"Hunting Blade, Malekith... all of you come over and help me to destroy Black Star's Mechanical Army. I'll see where he can still hide!" Fosters shouted out.

The other seven Vanguard Officials who were dealing with the fleet around received the new instructions and were surprised. Fosters had mentioned that Black Star was an opponent whom he would deal with alone, but now he needed help!

However, they naturally gave him some face, not to mention that Black Star had provoked them as well. Thus, all of them turned around and killed their way toward the tiny battlefield that Fosters and Black Star were at. They were akin to seven meteors, crashing into the Mechanical Army.

The moment the eight Vanguard Officials joined forces, the situation deteriorated instantly. The Mechanical Army was destroyed wantonly.

"Black Star cannot hold on much longer."

The Grade A Supers in Section Zero felt shock in their hearts, but to face off against eight of the Vanguard Officials, none of them had the courage to risk it and support him. Before the Mechanical Army was completely destroyed, Black Star still had hope.

Fosters eyed Han Xiao like a hawk the whole time. The moment Black Star intended to escape, he would immediately rush forward to disrupt him, not allowing him to escape.

Contrary to his expectations, even though the situation was clearly not on his side, Han Xiao continued to shift and dodge, without any intention of escaping. This resulted in Fosters' vigilance being useless.

"What is Black Star doing? Why is he not retreating‽"

"Does he not know that fighting on will only lead to his death‽"

The surrounding Calamity Grades were all frightened, carrying expressions of incredulity. Was he really going to fight all eight by himself‽

The entire area was filled with shards from his Mechanical Army, with none of them in one complete piece. Fosters and the other seven finally stopped, gazing over at Han Xiao like a tiger eyeing its prey.

Shooting a glance at the nonexistent Mechanical Army, Han Xiao remained passive. His opponents were the famed Vanguard Officials. This result was still within his expectations. Just based off the Mechanical Army alone, it would be difficult for him to face the assault of eight people.

However, with his insurance covering his losses, Han Xiao did not feel any heartache. Instead, he smiled before addressing the eight of them. "Hehe, seems like it's still eight against one in the end."

Fosters' face sank, and he growled, "Hurry up and deal with him. Let's see if he still can laugh."

"Really? All of us?" Malekith was surprised.

"Since we've already done so, let's just finish this."

The others were reluctant. In the first place, they had given Fosters face, allowing him to single out Han Xiao to fight. However, now that Fosters had gotten tired, he wanted them to help—they could not stop halfway. Bloodshed Land never emphasized fighting single battles—they only focused on getting the job done as fast as possible.

The eight of them rushed forward, and Han Xiao too breathed out once before rushing forth to meet them. In the eyes of the Calamity Grades around, Black Star's back seemed to have an impression that he had seen past death itself.

Everyone was touched!

They did not understand why Black Star would be so desperate to give up his life!

It was as though eight shooting stars continuously hit Han Xiao's body. Their explosive fists burst forth with numerous afterimages, bombarding every inch of his body.

Was Black Star hit with thousands of punches or tens of thousands? Nobody could tell for sure.

Everyone around had the cold sense of desolation, akin to foxes grieving when all the rabbits died. They could not bear to watch. Black Star's ending would definitely be grisly.

However, the next moment, everyone rubbed their eyes, not daring to believe this scenario!

When facing the barrage of blows like a heavy thunderstorm, while Han Xiao was beaten black and blue, to the point even his Mechanical suit shattered, his body was still perfectly sturdy, and he remained so lively even when facing such heavy punches!

Fosters and the rest suddenly stopped, staring at Han Xiao with uncertain gazes.

The strength that they released just now would be enough to destroy half the surface of a medium planet. How was Black Star still alive?

The MP and HP are indeed reliable, and the Steel Body ability does negate a lot of damage. However, these fellows are really frightening. I nearly had to use Aurora's Character Summon Card.

While he was being beaten up, Han Xiao's had been calmly analyzing the situation.

Seeing that the eight had stopped, Han Xiao exhaled, rubbing his shoulders and neck whilst revealing a careless smile. This, however, worked better than any form of provocation. Fosters' face turned steely as he felt that this smile was full of ridicule toward him, as though it was Han Xiao saying, Why did you stop?

At this moment, everybody's expression seemed to freeze up.

Ralph had a crazed expression of joy on his face. Black Star was indeed able to restrain all eight of them—he was serious about that!

The Grade As from Section Zero revealed various expressions of shock. Those eight were no ordinary Calamity Grade Supers; they were all the reputed eight Vanguard Officials of Bloodshed Land! The fame of each one resounded throughout the Star Field!

Fosters and the rest were furious. The eight of them had only lost to Tyrant whenever they joined hands!

They could not believe that Han Xiao could actually withstand their offensive.

It was as though the raging waves had smashed against the cliff but ended up being scattered into sea foam!

The name Black Star popped into everyone's head, with the connection that could not be waved away.

Was this the famed... Indestructible Body‽

Chapter 659: Beyond Grade A Level Attack!

"This is 'Indestructible Body' Black Star..."

"The strength of his body is even more exaggerated than in the rumors. With such a powerful recovery ability, only a beyond Grade A Super would be able to kill him."

"Tanking the attacks of the eight Vanguard Officials under Tyrant single handedly? He lives up to the name of being the number one general under Ames. Just where did Ames find such a ferocious character?"

Han Xiao's performance truly shocked many of the Calamity Grade Supers in Section Zero.

They had all thought that Black Star was overestimating himself and would end up sacrificing himself in battle. Who would have thought that the difference between them was so big?

Fosters was extremely shocked in his heart, and he said, "His body is a little strange. A portion of our attacks were absorbed by his cells to allow him to recover quickly."

Hunting Blade's expression was solemn. "I realized that, too."

The chief Vanguard Official had plenty of experience in battle and quickly identified the logic behind Han Xiao's Indestructible Body. Fosters' eyes narrowed, and he immediately thought of a method to deal with Han Xiao.

"He isn't able to recover instantly, and there is an upper limit to his ability. As long as our attack exceeds that limit, we will definitely be able to cause true damage to him. We need to launch an explosive series of attacks and not give him the chance to breathe. That is the only way that we can kill him."

Fosters' eyesight was extremely sharp, and he came to a conclusion that was extremely near to the truth.

Hearing that it was possible to kill Black Star, the seven others heaved sighs of relief.

The endurance that Black Star had displayed truly terrified them. The combined attack of the eight of them was sufficient to cause an entire ridgeline to collapse, and they would not even dare endure such an attack with their own bodies, just like how they would not dare tank the attacks of Han Xiao's Mechanical Army but choose to avoid them.

Looking at Han Xiao, who was currently at the center of the attack, Fosters said in a deep voice, "Don't overestimate Black Star. While it is extremely difficult to kill him, as long as we can destroy his Mechanical Army, the threat that he poses will be greatly reduced. I will be able to pin him down alone."

However, Fosters' target was not just to pin Black Star down but to kill Black Star. If the eight Vanguard Officials were not able to kill a single enemy of their same level when working together, this would be a huge blow to their reputation. They would only be able to establish their dominance by killing Black Star and scaring the other members of Section Zero.

"Attack together. Change tactics and do not spread out the strength of your attacks."

The moment he finished his sentence, the eight of them charged forward together. Fosters had said that only high damage in a short period would have a chance of killing Black Star, and the joint force of the eight of them could be extremely frightening.

Han Xiao had already guessed that the eight of them would attempt a second attack. The members of Bloodshed Land all had brains made from muscle and would not give up that easily.

He did not just stand still to tank the attacks. He spread his arms, and bolts of Mechanical Force shot out in all directions. Even if the Mechanical Army was destroyed, the spare parts floating around in space were his weapons!

Countless spare parts gathered toward Han Xiao like a whirlpool, and they quickly transformed into a gigantic mechanical cannon and arm.

The metal fist knocked the flames apart, and the laser cannon lit up the dark space. Han Xiao launched his ferocious counterattack.

If the battlefield was not located in the vacuum of space, the commotion of the battle would definitely have been earth shattering.

At the same time, five multicolored light rays intersected each other with a frightening force being hidden within them!

A Grade B Super would not even be able to withstand the shockwaves from the battle between Han Xiao and the eight Vanguard Officials!

For Han Xiao to transform all the spare parts into weapons, it required the use of [Waste Modification], [Basic Machinery Construction], and [Mechanical Force Combat Technique]. It greatly exhausted his energy, but the ferocious attacks of the eight Vanguard Officials made it such that Han Xiao did not lack energy at all.

Boom boom boom!

Every time their fists came into contact with each other, bright energy rings would be emanated.

The battle was becoming more and more intense!

Because Fosters had identified the method to deal with Han Xiao, the eight Vanguard Official's chose to use attacks with high burst damage. Their coordination was seamless, and their attacks rained down on Han Xiao without end. Han Xiao had to face a thunderstorm of attacks every second.

Punches with enough force to flatten mountains hammered down on his chest, and flames that were comparable to the main canons of battleships burned his bones. In order to achieve high burst damage, the eight Vanguard Officials used all their strength and greeted Han Xiao with all their techniques.

Their fists were like shooting stars, and those shooting stars were like rain!

Boom boom boom!

The tremors in his muscles and bones were all transmitted to his brain, and Han Xiao felt like a rice cake being hammered repeatedly. The eight Vanguard Officials had extremely powerful control over their strength, and Han Xiao suffered attacks ninety percent of the time. His retaliation was only able to cause a small disturbances to the Vanguard Officials and was insufficient to interrupt their attacks.

There was a limit to the conversion of energy into health, and he was only able to regain twenty-eight percent of his health every second.

The damage he took every second reached 450,000, and it exceeded the rate of his recovery.

This damage was extremely frightening, and an ordinary Calamity Grade Super would only be able to survive for two seconds before being turned into a corpse.

Thankfully, my Strengthened Life talent was upgraded to the advanced stage and gave me 200,000 HP. If not, my recovery speed would not have been able to keep up.

Enduring the pain from the never-ending attacks, Han Xiao grit his teeth and remained calm. His eyes were locked on his health meter. If things got too dangerous, he was prepared to use the Aurora Character Summon Card or Void Travel to give him some breathing space.

If the battle continued in such a manner, he would eventually be defeated. However, Han Xiao did not panic. He had only chosen to take on such a risk after serious consideration.

The most dangerous part of this battle was only the start. As long as he could drag this battle on, he would be safe.

His [Advanced Strengthened Life] talent did not only increase his HP but also allowed him to be more valiant as he fought. Every time he lost forty percent of his HP, his attributes would be increased by ten percent, including his Endurance.

This meant that Han Xiao's HP limit would only increase as the battle went on!

While the twenty-eight percent limit would not change, the amount of HP that he could recover would still increase!

This Molding Ability had made up for the shortcoming of the conversion limit and was the perfect combination to increase his recovery rate!

As long as he could survive past the most dangerous starting phase, the threat that the eight Vanguard Officials posed to him would become smaller!

Apart from the lack of aggro attracting skills, Han Xiao was already a god-level Main Tank!

The battle continued, and the frightening shockwaves from their battle truly scared the other Calamity Grade Supers present.

Through the energy reaction on their radar, they could see Black Star's life force signal becoming stronger and stronger. This meant that the terrifying attack of the eight Vanguard Officials did not threaten his life but made him stronger instead!

Even if Han Xiao was in an extremely pathetic state right now, no one dared underestimate him!

Only a single word was able to describe how all of them felt.

Unbelievable!

Fosters could already feel that something was wrong as the feeling of his fists coming into contact with Han Xiao's body became different. He could clearly feel Han Xiao's body becoming stronger by the second.

He is becoming stronger!

This thought floated up in his head, and his heart was shocked. At the same time, an unknown sense of rage exploded in his head.

Just how many trump cards does Black Star actually have?

This is enough!

Fosters hammered himself on the chest, and the flames on his body glowed brightly. All his energy was then channeled into his arms, and his arms ballooned up.

All the muscles in his body were clenched tight!

Arteries popped out by his temples and a dark red glow could be seen emanating from his fists.

Right at this moment, the radar from the surrounding battleships all let out an alarm.

"Warning, warning, high-energy response detected!"

The next moment, a blinding red beam of light shot out from Fosters' fists.

A gigantic red ball of energy smashed into Han Xiao with a pillar of fire behind its tail.

This single fist snatched the limelight of the entire battlefield, and the terrifying energy wave of the attack made everyone fill in the sound effects in their heads.

Boom!

"This is the Star Shaking Fist!"

The other seven Vanguard Officials were startled. This was a Pugilist skill that the Tyrant had taught them personally. It expended a large amount of their energy, and they all treated it as their killing blow.

They had seen Heber personally unleash the Star Shaking Fist, and the might of the attack lived up to its name!

Fosters was Heber's favorite student, and while his strength did not reach the level of a beyond Grade A Super, the shadow of Heber could be seen behind this fist of his.

Despite the thoughts flashing through their minds, their hands did not stay idle, and they copied Fosters.

Eight Star Shaking Fists smashed down on Han Xiao from all different directions!

Sh*t! Why do all of you like energy blasts so much. Do you think that you're a Saiyan[1]‽

The instant the attacks landed on him, Han Xiao only had time for a single thought.

The next instant, a terrifying blast of energy exploded!

Eight blinding energy blasts collided with each other and exploded with Han Xiao as the center!

The ball shaped energy wave expanded rapidly until the size of it exceeded that of a flagship. It was like a small planet made from energy and instantly became the focus of everyone present.

The energy ball expanded to its maximum, and a huge explosion occurred!

The blinding light from the explosion made everyone close their eyes instinctively.

Silence filled the battlefield.

A shockwave spread out in the galaxy.

The explosion ended in silence.

Before the explosion, Fosters and the other Vanguard Officials had already retreated and witnessed the outcome of their attack from afar.

This move of theirs had expended half of their energy and stamina. Even with their powerful Pugilist bodies, they were panting heavily from the attack, with their armor surrounding their arms cracking to reveal their bare skin.

Everyone's attention was focused on the center of the explosion. However, the place was completely empty, and Han Xiao's figure could not be seen.

"Was he reduced to smithereens?" Fosters' eyes lit up with joy.

Even he did not realize that he had lost his confidence.

"Did he really die‽" The members of Section Zero could not help but worry.

At this moment, a grayish fog suddenly condensed together and rapidly transformed into Han Xiao.

After regaining his physical form, Han Xiao spat out a mouthful of blood. His appearance was pale, and his limbs were covered with injuries, with burn marks and blood all around.

Before anyone could even react, Han Xiao's wounds began to close up rapidly, and all his lost blood and flesh grew back. His pale appearance also began to regain color, and in the blink of an eye, he recovered to his peak.

Aurora's Character Summon Card, [Life Return]!

Dammit, I was almost blown to death. Han Xiao felt a lingering fear in his heart.

The eight Star Shaking Fists, when used together, formed a special reaction, and the DarkStar mothership main cannon that he had tanked before was like a little brother before this.

In order to tank this blow, Han Xiao used all his trump cards. He had first used [Repel—Thorns] to reduce thirty percent of the initial attack. He then transformed into his Chaos Body form to ignore ninety-five percent of the damage with his energy becoming his health.

When his energy was completely exhausted, he had transformed back into his physical form, and his health had begun to fall with his energy being replenished rapidly. However, the interior of the energy ball was like a furnace with damage being dealt every second. Thankfully, he had the [Steel Body] to cancel out most of the damage, allowing him to replenish his energy. He had then transformed a couple of times between his Chaos Body form and physical body to tank the damage.

After his physical body met with the last wave of the explosion, his health had immediately emptied out, and he could only transform back into his Chaos Body form to avoid the calamity. When he reappeared again, his energy had been reduced to zero, and his HP had been left with eight percent.

He was at his wits end!

Han Xiao could only make use of his final trump card, [Life Return], to return to his peak state.

It was too dangerous!

Han Xiao had almost perished.

The scene of his physical body recovering was displayed before everyone present.

Black Star was still alive!

The next moment, the entire battlefield fell silent.

All the Calamity Grade Supers only had a single thought.

That attack was definitely at the beyond Grade A standard!

However, Black Star had managed to tank it.

They were shocked to the point they fell into a daze.

Right at this moment, the commander of Section Zero issued a new order.

"Retreat!"

While Han Xiao and the eight Vanguard Officials fought to a stalemate, Section Zero had slowly been pushed back and were not able to chase Bloodshed Land out of the region.

Despite facing eight high-level combatants alone, Han Xiao still was not able to turn the situation around. His teammates did not become outstanding because of him.

Only a beyond Grade A Super would be able to determine the direction of a war single handedly!

Despite Section Zero losing, Han Xiao's objective had been met.

It could be said that he was the only winner of this battle!

Even the victor of this battle, Bloodshed Land, could only remain in the background!

Han Xiao boarded the Blacklight Stealth and returned with the main fleet. Fosters and the others did not attempt to stop him. Their stamina was running out, and it would not be appropriate for them to enter enemy lines. Furthermore, he had already lost the confidence to kill Black Star.

The eight Vanguard Officials could only watch as Section Zero retreated.

The Section Zero fleet split up to reveal a path to welcome Han Xiao as though he was victorious. Despite being the losing party, Section Zero's morale was extremely high.

Even though Bloodshed Land had won the battle, the atmosphere seemed as though they had lost.

Right at that moment, those who had witnessed the battle between Han Xiao and the eight Vanguard Officials understood one thing.

After this battle, Black Star would no longer be treated as an ordinary expert and would go up to the next level. He had truly walked onto the stage of the bigshots in the Star Field!

The Calamity Grade Supers from Section Zero could predict that Black Star would be completely different from them!

[1] This is a reference to Dragon Ball. Back

Chapter 660: Legendary Point: Indestructible Body.

The Section Zero fleet left the Bloodshed Land startled. Word of the astonishing fight earlier quickly spread throughout the entire fleet. The other allies were all shocked and could not believe it. Their doubts were only cleared when they saw the video footage.

Han Xiao met with Lagi and the others. The battlefield that his troops had been in did not have an intense fight, so the damage suffered in this battle was insignificant.

After leaving the battlefield, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

Han Xiao was not surprised. Back when he faced the attack of three DarkStar Calamity Grades before he was even a Calamity Grade himself, he had also received the [Battle of Three Calamity Grades] Legendary Point. Now that he had faced the eight Vanguard Officials who were much more famous, receiving a Legendary Point was expected.

Star Cluster Legendary Point (Colton Star Cluster): Indestructible Body. You fought eight Vanguard Officials of the Bloodshed Land at once, and with absolutely unquestionable results, you proved to the world that you deserved this title. Tales of this fight will be passed on by many, becoming an everlasting legend!

Indestructible Body...

Han Xiao was surprised. This had initially been a nickname given by many organizations, but now it had become official. He felt very excited for some reason.

He had finally earned a real title for himself!

Star Cluster Legendary Points increased his rewards by twenty percent, much higher than Star System Legendary Points. This was his first Star Cluster Legendary Point.

If I defeated the eight Vanguard Officials, the reward might totally be a Star Field Legendary Point.

Han Xiao shook his head. That was beyond his capabilities. All the Vanguard Officials were very tanky, too. Plus, they had cooperated with each other very well, controlling the tempo of the battle. Retreating alive was the limit of his current capabilities. Only Beyond Grade As could deal with this kind of situation with ease.

On the interface, the mission was shown as completed. Han Xiao was about to contact Ralph and tell him to carry out his end of the deal, but as soon as he took out the communicator, Ralph's communication request came first.

As soon as he picked up, Ralph instantly spoke. "Black Star, your combat capability has completely exceeded my expectations. You really did it! Although we did not win this time, you have put an end to the negative situation..."

Ralph did not hold back in praising him. Due to fear of Bloodshed Land's strategy, the Calamity Grade Section Zero members had all been unwilling to fight. At this crucial moment, Han Xiao had been the only one that could directly restrain those enemies. Han Xiao was a straw to clutch at in his eyes. He praised him nonstop till the point that even Han Xiao was annoyed.

Han Xiao could not help but stop him.

"Stop it. There's no need for these compliments. It's time to complete the deal. Give me the Cutting-Edge Knowledge. I want to retreat from the battlefield temporarily."

Hearing that, the excitement on Ralph's face froze. "You want to quit the secret war?"

"Just temporarily. As you have seen, in order to fight the eight Vanguard Officials, my Mechanical Army was wiped out. I'm a Mechanic. Without my machines, my combat capability will decrease tremendously. Plus, I'm actually suffering from rather serious internal injuries. I'm only forcing myself not to vomit any blood," Han Xiao said with a serious and sincere face.

"Really?" Ralph looked at Han Xiao suspiciously.

He did not look injured at all.

"What, do you want me to vomit some blood for you to see?" Han Xiao opened his mouth and looked like he was about to vomit.

"Alright, alright, I believe you." Ralph quickly stopped him. He felt that Black Star might really be heavily injured.

Thinking about it, he had fought against the eight Vanguard Officials. Plus, he had been hit by a Beyond Grade A standard attack; it was normal for him to pay a price for it.

Han Xiao paused and explained, "I need to rest for some time. Cutting-Edge Knowledge is extremely complex. I will need half a month... Hmm, a month to learn it."

Ralph nodded. Cutting-Edge Knowledge was indeed very complex.

"Also, I need time to rebuild my Mechanical Army. This will be a huge project. I won't be able to utilize my full potential if I don't rebuild it, so it would be meaningless even if I did continue to take part in the battles."

"Er... I suppose." Ralph was in a dilemma. "But if you quit, we really won't have the ability to fight back in terms of high-level combatants. As you know, the other members are not really contributing at all."

Han Xiao shrugged, as if saying, I've done what I could.

He shook his head and said, "As you've seen, I can't change the war alone, and this battle has proved that. Even though I held back the Vanguard Officials, the fleet wasn't able to penetrate into the Bloodshed Land's stronghold. Compared to Bloodshed Land, our alliance fleet looks like an amateurs. The way I see it, the Bloodshed Land will almost definitely succeed in their invasion."

After two battles, Ralph was rather pessimistic. He asked, "What thoughts do you have?"

"I think that at the start of the secret war, Bloodshed Land will gather their forces to create the first batch of strongholds," Han Xiao said in a sincere tone. "It will be exceedingly difficult for us to stop that from happening. However, Bloodshed Land will have to split their forces to build more strongholds in order to invade the several Star Systems near the borders. This will cause their forces to split up. At that time, maybe Section Zero will have a chance to counterattack."

Although he did not know the details from the version update, he still remembered what the situation of the secret war had been at the later stages during Version 3.0. From that, he could deduce Bloodshed Land's advantages during the earlier stages.

The march of Bloodshed Land was unstoppable. He wanted to retreat now because he did not want to get thrashed by the opponents in the earlier stages.

Ralph contemplated for a while. In the end, he could only admit that what Han Xiao had said made a lot of sense. That might really turn out to be how things developed. He suddenly felt powerless and asked, "You're right—do you have any suggestions?"

"I feel that the most important matter at the moment is the fact that the high-level combatants of Section Zero are avoiding battles. We shouldn't have unrealistic fantasies about chasing all the enemies away. It's best to stop when suitable to avoid larger damage. The time to counter-attack has yet to arrive. What we need to do now is strengthen our forces till that moment arrives."

Star Cluster Civilizations were not short on resources. In order to stop Bloodshed Land, Purple Crystal could use these resources to increase the strength of the Section Zero members. As for Han Xiao, who had already shown his value, if the Purple Crystal Civilization took his advice, he would receive even more benefits.

Ignoring the Great Mechanic Han's ulterior motive, this suggestion did make sense. At least, this was a feasible strategy for Ralph.

"I will pass on your suggestion to the commanding department and let them analyze it." Ralph paused before sighing. "As for your request, I will approve it... I have only one requirement. When you have recovered fully, you have to return to the battlefield immediately."

"Of course. When will you give me the Cutting-Edge Knowledge?"

"I will give you a knowledge list later. You can pick it for yourself. By the way, the resources to make up for your loss will also be handed to you as soon as possible."

Han Xiao smiled.

With the Cutting-Edge Knowledge that he was soon going to receive, he would be able to complete his Class Advancement mission. One of the bigger goals of joining the secret war had already been achieved.

Han Xiao had taken a shortcut, so he did not have to spend too much time farming Favorability. This act of holding back the eight Vanguard Officials alone was unduplicatable; the Vanguard Officials had now discovered that he was very difficult to kill, so they would not waste their energy fighting him together. This time, it brought Han Xiao fame, and the Vanguard Officials would definitely not make the same mistake next time.

Han Xiao was extremely tanky, but his actual combat capability was not that extraordinary. One or two Vanguard Officials would be able to restrain him. What had happened that day would never happen again.

In order to become stronger, he needed to continue leveling up as well as build new machines using the Cutting-Edge Knowledge as the core.

After closing the communication, Ralph sent the knowledge list over.

There was a total of sixty Mechanic knowledges, twenty from Armed, Energy, and Control Branch each. These knowledges were grouped into five levels—basic, advanced, and high-level knowledges made up forty-five of the sixty knowledges. There were only fifteen Cutting-Edge Knowledges and Ultimate Knowledges in total. The fact that there were so few of them showed how extremely valuable they were.

There were nine types of Cutting-Edge Knowledges, three from each of the branches. Even Purple Crystal did not have all the Cutting-Edge Knowledges, just some of them.

Han Xiao was a Virtual Mechanic. The Potential Point cost for learning Control Branch Cutting-Edge Knowledges was normal, but it would cost triple the Potential Points to learn Cutting-Edge Knowledges from the other two branches.

Yet, Han Xiao did not choose the Control Branch Cutting-Edge Knowledge but an Energy Branch Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

[Abnormal State Energy]!

This was a must-learn knowledge for any Mechanic after Class Advancement. It could be considered an evolutionary knowledge for Mechanics.

After learning this knowledge, only then would the Mechanics be able to harvest, extract, and use psionic and antimatter energy on a large scale!

Energy was the core of machines. The change in energy technology would bring tremendous changes!

Han Xiao had been waiting for this knowledge for a very long time. He had saved his Potential Points so that he could afford the triple cost.

Since he did not have to take part in the upcoming battle, Han Xiao took his people and left, heading back to the base in the Garton Star System.

The other Section Zero members were envious, seeing that the Black Star Army was leaving, but none of them had a problem with it.

Black Star had taken a huge risk in this battle. He did indeed have the right to go back and rest. The others could only watch as the Black Star Army departed.

The second fight between Purple Crystal and Klent had ended. The other five Star Cluster Civilization that had been paying attention to the secret war received the battlefield report very soon. Those superiors could almost not believe their own eyes.

Black Star had fought the eight Vanguard Officials alone and survived almost unharmed‽

Really‽

This news thunderously appeared on the desk of the various organization leaders and stirred up a storm in their social circle!

The seven Star Cluster Civilizations, Bloodshed Land, and the other huge organizations all reevaluated Han Xiao.

Originally, in their eyes, Black Star was most famously known as Ames' trustworthy subordinate and secondly known for his network. Black Star's position in their social circle had basically come from these two titles. However, these organizations did not consider his combat capability to be anything notable. On average, their assessment of him was—Black Star is a rather strong Calamity Grade, but he's not overwhelmingly strong among those of the same grade.

However, this news shattered all the opinions of these organizations concerning Han Xiao.

According to his performance in this battle, the seven Star Cluster Civilization and the various organizations reevaluated his strength.

"In the universe, fighting alone isn't popular. Many people have to face more than one opponent of the same grade at the same time. It's known that Mages and Mechanics are the two types of Supers that are most capable of fighting more than one enemy of the same grade.

"Black Star is a Mechanic, but his way of fighting more than one enemy is different.

"Mechanics have shared weakness—their physical body isn't strong enough. Other than some Mechanics that use single unit combat suits, most Mechanics are afraid of the enemies closing the distance. However, Black Star has an unbelievable physique. His endurance is extremely high, and he has an almost Esper ability level recovery speed. The strategy of closing the distance on him will be turned into a trap by him instead.

"He's a special Mechanic. Even if he loses his machines, he will still have a very high combat capability with his physique. Dragging out the battle is his strength—he's able to make the battles long enough to make more than ninety percent of the Calamity Grades exhausted and powerless.

"From the machines that Black Star has showcased, it's clear that he has yet to master the use of psionic energy. As soon as he starts to use psionic as the energy core, with his terrifying physique, Black Star's strength will multiply many times. He will undoubtedly become one of the very few people that stand at the top of Calamity Grades.

"According to the intelligence above, it's strongly recommended to move him into the [Shattered Star Ring Beyond Grade A Seed Observation List]...

"Black Star has the potential of reaching Beyond Grade A!"

The Beyond Grade A Seed List was on an entirely new level from the usual Calamity Grades. The Star Cluster Civilizations paid attention to everyone on this list. Every name represented someone extremely talented with the potential to become a Beyond Grade A.

This was not only determined by potential but also strength, growth speed, special talent, race, ability type, and many other factors.

This list covered the entire Shattered Star Ring.

However, there were a few dozen people on the list!

Chapter 661: A New Level

On Planet Heber, Bloodshed Land's headquarters, the intelligence of the frontline was transmitted back to the command post. Jorde requested to see Heber—he felt that he had to report Black Star's performance.

Heber sat on the enormous throne inside the palace. After hearing Jorde's report, not only was he not angry, he showed an interesting expression instead. He slowly spoke with a thunderous voice.

"I was not wrong. Black Star is wasting his talent under Ames. He should've come to be my subordinate."

Heber shook his head. He had always thought Han Xiao was very capable, but Han Xiao had rejected him twice. He definitely would not invite him a third time.

"Klent isn't very happy. They think that Black Star is an unstable factor and should be eliminated as soon as possible," Jorde said.

"I don't need them to teach me how to fight a war," Heber said. "What do my eight Vanguard Officials think?"

"Er, Fosters said that he has brought shame to Bloodshed Land's name and is very embarrassed. He will use a hundred victories to wash away today's shame."

Jorde chose his words carefully. The truth was, Fosters was not as emotionally stable as Jorde said he was—he was almost depressed.

"The Bloodshed Land's position won't decrease because of just one battle," Heber replied. "He's a winner, so he shouldn't act like a loser. In the entire Shattered Star Ring, there are dozens of Calamity Grades that have the potential to become a Beyond Grade A. However, after so many years, there are still only four Beyond Grade As..."

After a pause, a fierce vibe came from Heber. Jorde felt as if his neck had been grabbed by someone, and his breath stopped for a moment.

"Potential is just potential. With me here, there's no need to fear anyone."

Jorde was instantly motivated. Heber's confidence was what made it worth following him till the end.

At the same time on the Purple Crystal Civilization's mother planet...

The two losses of Section Zero had made the Purple Crystal upper echelons very unsatisfied. Black Star's performance was the only good news among all the bad news.

The high-level government officials from the relevant departments hosted a private meeting to discuss Black Star.

"Beyond Grade A seeds are extremely rare. Although the Dragon Emperor is neutral, Black Star is on Purple Crystal's side. He has remarkably high investment value."

"That's right. Black Star's force is in the Colton Star Cluster, so he's close to us. If he can become a Beyond Grade A, this means that a Beyond Grade A force will appear in Colton. This will make up for our disadvantage compared to Klent."

The Purple Crystal Civilization was very jealous of Klent Kingdom having Bloodshed Land as an ally.

If they had a Beyond Grade A organization as an ally as well, they would not have to spend so much effort to create Section Zero, and they would not be at such a disadvantage in the secret war.

Black Star had the potential, and he was much more motivated than the Dragon Emperor. Considering his political affiliation, the Purple Crystal Civilization felt that he was worthy of investing in.

This meeting was to discuss their attitude toward Black Star in the future. They saw longer term benefits in Han Xiao beyond this war.

Star Cluster Civilizations were not afraid of Beyond Grade As, but that did not mean that they did not want one. The various Star Cluster Civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring were all very serious in cultivating Supers. They built many schools to educate students with potential, producing talented people every year as fresh blood being supplied to the various departments.

However, they could only cultivate Calamity Grades at most. There was completely no hope in raising a Beyond Grade A. This was not something that could be created through a certain procedure.

Therefore, a Beyond Grade A seed who was close to the Purple Crystal Civilization was more than enough to make those high-level officials put down whatever they were dealing with and go for a meeting to discuss it.

"If Black Star becomes a Beyond Grade A, we can help him to build his Beyond Grade A organization into an organization that can match the Bloodshed Land. This way, Klent will no longer have this advantage. Also, this will make us more influential in the Star Field."

"Cultivating our own Beyond Grade A ally... it's a good idea, but Black Star will have to fulfill his potential."

They discussed for some time and finally came to an agreement.

They would change the way they invested in Black Star, increasing the resources provided to the Black Star Army. After all, the cost of building a relationship with a Calamity Grade was incomparable to the cost of building a relationship with a Beyond Grade A. The earlier they made this investment, the smaller the cost.

Purple Crystal did not lack resources. They were willing to invest early and bet on Black Star's potential.

At the same time, they decided to promote the Black Star Army's position in Section Zero. They would heavily focus on Black Star's growth and provide him with a certain amount of protection to prevent other organizations from secretly targeting him.

A Beyond Grade A seed was a new level that exceeded normal Calamity Grades. Every one of them was the focus of various organizations.

The fame brought by this fight had completely changed the Star Cluster Civilizations' attitudes toward Han Xiao.

With people spreading the information, the news that Black Star had become a new Beyond Grade A seed quickly spread throughout the Shattered Star Ring. Countless galactic residents knew about this, and it would not be an exaggeration to say that almost everyone in the Shattered Star Ring did.

Even those Star Cluster Civilizations that had no conflict with the Purple Crystal Civilization were not willing to watch Purple Crystal obtain someone that might become a Beyond Grade A in the future. With the motive of bringing him more attention so that he would be targeted by more people, not only did they not hide their attention on Han Xiao, they deliberately leaked it.

In the process of spreading, the news was twisted again and again. In the end, it shockingly became...

"Black Star will be the fifth Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring in the future"!

This was much more shocking than him being a Beyond Grade A seed. It was basically pushing Han Xiao onto the throne in advance. Countless people were stunned.

The big organizations knew that this was bullsh*t, but most people did not know the details. Under the various exaggerated reports, many people really believed in this rumor and started to spread the news that the fifth Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring was about to appear.

This news reached Floating Dragon Island as well.

Whoosh!

The alloy gate of the training room opened, and Hila walked out while wiping the sweat on her forehead.

Over the past few years while she was training on Floating Dragon Island, she had changed out of her black battle suit and gotten herself a specially tailored red windbreaker made with a special cloth. It was engraved with a high-level shield and was also enchanted to enhance her Esper ability.

If Han Xiao was there now, he would definitely feel that it looked very familiar—the design of this windbreaker was very similar to what he had worn when he was Black Phantom.

"It's been almost three years. I'm getting more and more skilled in my ability. According to the universal standard, I've stabilized at Grade B. Based on my current growth, I should be able to become Grade B+ within three years. Ames said that I have the potential to become a Calamity Grade..."

Feeling more and more proficient in her Esper ability, Hila was joyous.

Ames was a master of the Esper class, so the experiences she taught her benefitted her hugely. In order to catch up to Han Xiao, Hila never slacked off.

She was satisfied with her progress—this was the result that she had earned with sweat and hard work.

"Sis, I have good news!"

Just as Hila was about to go back to rest, Aurora quickly ran to her with a face filled with joy.

"What good news?" Hila was in quite a good mood. She pinched Aurora's tender cheeks and smiled.

"It's about Han Xiao. Everyone is saying that he will very soon become a Beyond Grade A Super. Even the news reported this!"

Aurora raised the communicator that was playing the news right in front of Hila and could not wait to share this with Hila.

Hila was stunned.

"He's about to become a Beyond Grade A?"

Ames was a Beyond Grade A. Did that not mean that Han Xiao was going to be as strong as Ames‽

Hila clenched her teeth. She had initially been very satisfied with her progress, but now she felt like she could not catch up to Han Xiao no matter what. She felt immense pressure.

Compared to him, this progress is not worth mentioning!

I'm still not working hard enough!

Aurora was still speaking with excitement. Suddenly, she saw Hila turn around and walk into the training room, closing the door behind her. The next moment, the light showing that the training room was in use lit up.

"Sis?" Aurora was stunned.

Neither of them noticed that Ames was hovering in midair above, watching them.

"With such a strong personality, Hila will progress faster than expected." Ames smiled.

Although she was lazy, she liked how hardworking Hila was.

Every Beyond Grade A had gone through a period of time when they worked extremely hard and built their own legend before they became a Beyond Grade A. In Hila, she felt like she saw her younger self.

As for Black Star, Ames could not understand what was going on with him at all.

As Han Xiao achieved astonishing things one time after another, Ames' impression of him was shattered and reformed many times. At this time, she was not even willing to try to speculate Han Xiao's potential. She had just one word for Han Xiao—unfathomable!

Ames had never thought that a mercenary whom she casually recruited would achieve the things that he had achieved.

Her requirement for Han Xiao was now as low as it could get.

As long as Black Star stayed by her, she would be satisfied.

Half of the Star Field was talking about him, and the news was exaggerated again and again, such that even Han Xiao was embarrassed by it.

Are they really talking about me?

When did I fight Tyrant to a draw‽

When did I chase Ames‽

When did I make the announcement to challenge the Crimson Dynasty‽

When did I chat casually with Austin as if we're friends... Oh, this is actually true.

Han Xiao was completely speechless.

Don't these reporters know that they have to be responsible for these things they say?

After returning to the Garton Star System base, he finally felt the effect of this matter.

The Godoran Civilization's attitude changed visibly. They were much more respectful and actively suggested to extend their partnership, as well as open up more resource channels to provide him more rare resources.

Han Xiao even heard that Serbia the Fifth was preparing to tour the Star System and would be going to Planet Golden Gate first to visit him publicly.

The resources given by the Purple Crystal Civilization to make up for his losses had arrived at the base. Just the cash was already more than ten million Enas, much more than what the Purple Crystal Civilization had promised. The quantity of resources had also multiplied. This was a completely pleasant surprise.

Han Xiao tutted. He knew that what he had done was sensational, but he had underestimated how sensational it would be. It was crystal clear how much more serious the Purple Crystal Civilization was about him.

This sped up the plan that he had made before the war started.

He quickly told Phillip, Herlous, and Sylvia to settle the matters on replenishing the lost battleships and people before going to the training room. He took out the communicator and opened the data that the Purple Crystal sent to him on [Abnormal State Energy].

When I finish learning this knowledge, I will be many times stronger. My Mechanical Armies being wiped out is a good opportunity to renew them completely.

Excited, Han Xiao opened his interface.

Mechanic class Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Abnormal State Energy] detected. Spend 12 Potential Points to learn?

"Yes."

Learning in progress. Do not cancel.

9%... 43%... 78%...

Successfully Learned! You have learned [Abnormal State Energy]!

Complex and difficult knowledge flew into Han Xiao's head. He digested it for a while and took a deep breath.

Of course, him telling Ralph that he needed a whole month to learn was bullsh*t. The others had no way to know that he could learn things so quickly.

Finally, I have my first Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

Han Xiao was content. He achieved the Class Advancement requirement at the same time.

A notification popped up on the interface immediately.

Class Advancement requirements completed!

You have received a new class [Truth Mechanic Lv.1].

+210 Energy, +2 STR, +4 DEX, +4 END, +10 INT.

You have received 7 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

I did it!

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

[Truth Mechanic] was a high-level class in the Mechanic class, one level higher than [Galaxy Mechanic]. Its level limit was twenty-five.

The name represented the fact that the Mechanic would start to learn the truths about machines in this stage.

However, to the players in his previous life, this name had another meaning.

Within my attack range, I'm the truth!

Chapter 662: Multiplied Strength

Han Xiao calmed his mood and looked at the new abilities given by the Class Advancement.

You have received talent [Machinery Truth Knowledge]!

You have acquired ability [Extreme Energy Output]!

You have acquired ability [Logic Program Strengthening]!

You have acquired ability [Deep Data Implantation]!

Your talent [Virtual Technology Essence] has been enhanced!

Your ability [Strengthened Smart Defense] has been enhanced!

Your ability [Strengthened Hacking] has been enhanced!

Your ability [Quantum Network Matrix] has been enhanced!

Han Xiao nodded.

After choosing Virtual Technology Essence, each subsequent Class Advancement would enhance the Virtual Technology abilities and talents. Several important abilities of the Virtual Mechanic were strengthened, and there were two new virtual technology abilities.

The effect of [Logic Program Strengthening] was to carry out multiple upgrades for artificial intelligence to improve their calculation efficiency.

Artificial intelligence was an important helper in both virtual attack and defense. The higher the level of artificial intelligence, the higher the success rate.

This ability could be used to strengthen Phillip. After all, Risda was an independent life. Phillip was still the most loyal and adorable.

[Deep Data Implantation] strengthened his latent intrusion ability. This ability allowed one to not attack the firewall but spend time finding holes and gaps before quietly sending disguised data packets into the target's artificial intelligence program, not causing any alarms.

This ability was not useful in direct battles because it would take a long time. However, it was perfectly suited for covert operations. The data packets could be hiding deep inside the enemy's artificial intelligence like probes that penetrated the bottom of the ocean. They could detect the movements of 'currents', filtering out useful intelligence. They could also act as a time bomb.

At the same time, they could even dive into the bottom data layer of the target artificial intelligence, embed new logic, and secretly makes it betray its master.

In addition to the improvement of some abilities, this Class Advancement gave him two new important abilities.

Truth Mechanics were famous for their high damage. Their specialty was turning mechanical soldiers into elites and enhancing the attributes of the machines.

[Machinery Truth Knowledge] was the core talent of the Truth Mechanic. It blended the truth about machines into manufacture. This would comprehensively strengthen the machinery's armor, defense, energy core, weapon power, range, and other attributes.

The degree of increase in each attribute varied from forty percent to fifteen percent. In summary, the strength increase of a single mechanical object was considerable. His manufacturing ability was greatly increased.

[Extreme Energy Output] increased the output efficiency of the energy core. This was similar to expanding the mouth of the container to make water flow faster.

It increased the power of the weapon based on the level of energy used, and the higher the level of energy used, the higher the damage bonus.

According to Han Xiao's experience, using a cold nuclear reactor could increase the damage of a weapon by about eleven percent, while using psionic energy could increase its damage by twenty-five to thirty percent.

The power of the psionic energy itself would already increase its damage. With the addition of these two abilities, it could increase his destructive power by several notches.

The strength increase from this Class Advancement is even greater than the last. The basic attributes of mechanical structures are very important. Even if it's just increased by a little bit, my Mechanical Force bonus will amplify it. The Truth Mechanic is a significant milestone. With the increase of so many attributes as well as my Mechanical Force bonuses, this means that with the same sized Mechanical Army, my combat capability will be many times stronger now compared to before the Class Advancement!

Han Xiao was satisfied. After the Class Advancement, the threat of his Mechanical Army would be tremendously higher to Calamity Grades. Thus, his combat capability was increased as all.

At the higher stages of the main class, the benefits of Class Advancements would be increasing. The current level was twenty-five, five levels above the Promotion limit. This meant that the Class Advancement was even more difficult than Promotion.

With a large pool of experience, Han Xiao did not blink and fully leveled up his new abilities as well as leveled himself up to level 180.

[Truth Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.11.

+210 Energy, +2 STR, +4 DEX, +4 END, +10 INT.

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

As always, he used the Free Attribute Points on Intelligence.

The leveling up of himself and his abilities brought Han Xiao thirteen Potential Points. He then leveled up a few blueprints to gain a few points. Together with his original savings, Han Xiao directly leveled up the Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Abnormal State Energy] to Lv.4. Each level cost him twelve Potential Points. His Potential Points were instantly emptied.

The higher the level of the core knowledge, the better. This would affect the attributes of the Mechanical Army that he was about the rebuild. These were Potential Points that would be spent sooner or later, so Han Xiao had no hesitation. Anyway, he had a lot of Experience, so he could get Potential Points from leveling up blueprints. Even though the triple cost hurt, he could still bear it.

His total level reached 180, which was the Promotion stage, and the Promotion mission arrived on schedule.

Level 180 class advancement mission [The Ultimate Trial]: Push through one's limits during battle, ascend the hierarchy of life.

Mission Requirements: Acquire 50 Trial Points, current progress: 0/50.

The Trial Points are obtained by defeating the opponent, the opponent must be Super of the same rank. 2 Trial Points will be earned by winning. A maximum of 4 Trial Points can be obtained from one person. If the opponent is 5 levels lower than you, you will not be able to get Trial Points. If your opponent is 20 or more levels higher than you, you will get 6 Trial Points after winning. The same target cannot be repeated.

Han Xiao's face turned into delight.

When he was level 60, he had triggered a similar trial-type Promotion mission. This kind of mission was not difficult and would not cause his level to get stuck.

The mission requirement was to fight Supers of the same grade, Calamity Grade. Trial Points would be given after a victory, which meant that sparring would do. Thus, there was no need to kill the opponent.

For players, this task would be a bit tricky. They would have to look for Calamity Grade NPCs everywhere. Even if they did find one and requested to spar, it would still depend on whether that person wanted to fight the player. If the player attacked directly, it would anger the opponent's faction or organization.

Players would have to spend almost all their time looking for opponents. Sometimes, they would not even be able to win. However, to Han Xiao, this was not an issue at all.

With his network and connections in the Shattered Star Ring, it was way too easy to find someone to spar with.

The Black Star Army alone already had two Grade As. With Lagi's personality, he would most likely not use his full strength, so those six Trail Points were basically guaranteed. Sadly, Reynold's level was much lower than his, or he would be able to get four more points.

I'm now level 180, not too high in Grade A. It's easy to find an opponent...

Level 180 meant his fourth Race Evolution. He had consumed the essence potions of quite a number of void creatures, even the core of a Void Lord. He should be able to get many strong options during the Race Evolution.

Since the Promotion mission was not difficult, Han Xiao was in no hurry. He had to at least rebuild his Mechanical Army before finding people to spar with. The Mechanical Army was his main source of combat capability.

After looking at the new abilities for a while, Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at his attributes.

Level: 180

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Chaos Observer (Human Form)

Attributes: 306 STR, 674 DEX, 670 END, 2126 INT, 263 MYS, 105 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Point: 0

Health: 125,390

Stamina: 101,620

Energy: 19,680 [Lv.11]

Lv.11 Energy bonus stats: +111 STR, +158 DEX, +174 END, +204 INT, +129 MYS, +21,220 Stamina Limit, +142% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 17,810

Grade: A

Grade A Ranked Bonus: Additional Bonus to END +10, All Resistances +8. Highest Stat(s) +10%, Other Stats +5%, Additional 30 Free Attribute Points, Additional 5 Potential Points

Remark: You're not far from the Grade A+ threshold. Although, your actual strength is already not weaker than some Grade A+ Supers

Due to the Advanced Strengthened Life talent, Han Xiao's energy level was already around 16,000. With the new abilities and ten more levels, his energy rank increased again.

By the time I complete the Promotion mission, my Experience will be more than enough to level up Truth Mechanic to its highest, which will make me level 195. Plus, with the bonus from Race Evolution, I should be able to reach Grade A+.

He told Herlous and the rest to take care of the Black Star Army businesses while he started to rebuild the Mechanical Army. He was eager to see how strong his Mechanical Army would be after his Class Advancement.

The first step of rebuilding was extracting new energy and building a psionic reactor.

The psionic energy was a highly unstable high-level energy. Usually, only Star Cluster Civilizations would study psionic energy because it was very risky. If a civilization studied it without advanced enough technology, if the psionic energy went out of control, an entire planet surface civilization might be destroyed.

The earliest civilization to discover psionic energy was the Federation of Light. In the field of research and development, the Federation of Light had always been ahead. Long before the appearance of Beyond Grade As, psionic energy had been used in the war between the three civilizations.

The earliest discovery of psionic energy was when the Federation of Light was studying a certain spacetime project. During an experiment that involved collapsing secondary spaces, they happened to find out that a huge amount of matter shattered during the collapse turned into a special type of energy, thus the discovery of psionic energy.

After a long period of study, the three civilizations gradually gained a clearer understanding of psionic energy.

This was very high-level energy. It came from secondary spatial collapse. It could assimilate most of the forms of energy around it, such as heat, electricity, and so on, all of which would be turned into psionic energy. That energy would all be condensed together with a very low loss of energy during the assimilation. This reaction was called 'Psionic Inflation'.

As the cost of the spatial collapse was too high to be popularized, based on this trait, the three civilizations extracted primordial psionic particles from space collapse experiments and developed a storage technology that put the primordial psionic particles to sleep. This inhibited natural Psionic Inflation, they then began to try mass applications.

There were failures during their experiments. Once the psionic energy went out of control and was exposed to the outside world, it became a black hole like energy, constantly absorbing all forms of energy around it. The converted energy all became psionic energy, which caused the Psionic Inflation to keep occurring and creating a radioactive reaction called Psionic Pollution. When the primordial psionic particles decayed to the critical point, the huge explosion happened. A tiny bit of the primordial pyloric particle could almost flatten a small half of a planet, destroying the surface civilization.

After a long period of research into psionic energy, the three civilizations finally worked out a highly efficient and controllable psionic reaction furnace that was far more efficient than nuclear fusion. However, due to fear of psionic energy's power when it lost control, it was not widely used in the early period.

After extensive studies, the three civilizations discovered another feature of the psionic energy—it could not only assimilate but also be inverted into various forms of energy. As psionic was created from spatial collapse, some thought that the psionic was the initial or final form of energy, that it was the so-called 'universal energy'.

The research on the psionic energy was still underway, and there were thousands of hypotheses and studies. The three civilizations had improved the collection methods and refining formulas many times. Psionic energy had become an efficient and controllable higher-level energy source, also a necessary technology for the Mechanic class.

As a Calamity Grade Mechanic, after learning [Abnormal State Energy], Han Xiao was able to extract primordial psionic particles safely.

Chapter 663: Psionic Core, War Situation

Four thin mechanical poles formed an 'X' shape and secured the mini sphere-shaped reactor in the middle.

The sphere-shaped reactor was the size of a fist. It was completely silver with the surface of the ball being smooth and shiny, reflecting Han Xiao's suave appearance.

"The small psionic reactor is of light purple grade, and its efficiency is many times that of the cold nuclear fission reactor."

Han Xiao looked at the psionic reactor and heaved a sigh of relief.

He had used [Abnormal State Energy] to roll blueprints and received the blueprint for a large number of psionic machines. He first constructed a complete set of psionic extraction apparatus and tested it many times before carefully refining a psionic particle. Following which, the particles were melded together, and he used a few days of testing before finally being able to construct a psionic energy furnace.

Because psionic energy had some risk, Han Xiao only dared speed up the production process after ensuring the stability of every step.

After observing the results of the test, Han Xiao plucked off a compressed orb from his necklace and threw it to the side.

A bolt of Mechanical Force shot toward the compressed orb and activated it. In the blink of an eye, the compressed orb transformed into the Berserk Ape mechanical suit. This was the backup suit in the warehouse. His original one had already been destroyed by the eight Vanguard Officials.

"Phillip, maintain standby mode and eject the energy core."

"Orders confirmed, hum..."

The Berserk Ape mechanical suit raised its head and stood up straight. The chest piece of the mechanical suit then opened to reveal the interior construction of the mechanical suit.

Kacha!

A dense energy reactor was ejected from the chest of the mechanical suit. It was glowing red as though it was the heart of the mechanical suit.

Han Xiao removed the nuclear reactor and placed it to the side. He then took the psionic reactor and stuffed it back into the empty slot.

Hum!

A humming sound could be heard, and the psionic reactor lit up. A bright blue glow could be seen from the reactor, and the glow spread through the entire suit. The mechanical suit then automatically retracted the reactor and began adapting to the new reactor.

The energy furnace got to work and provided an endless stream of psionic energy. With the energy furnace as the core, blue veins spread out in all directions on the surface of the Berserk Ape suit and covered the entire suit. These blue veins lit up for a short while before becoming dull and flashing for more than ten seconds before coming to a stop.

"The update of the energy reactor is complete. The mechanical suit is functioning perfectly, hum..." Phillip said in a merry tone as though he was a little child.

While he was constructing the psionic energy furnace, Han Xiao had also upgraded Phillip's program with his newly acquired Logic Program Strengthening. Apart from increasing Phillip's processing efficiency, Phillip had also downloaded an emotion module and now seemed more energetic. Not only that, he had even chosen to replace his voice with the voice of a little boy.

Looking at the equipment introduction on the interface, the Power Output of the Berserk Ape was three times that of the original figure, and more modules could be installed. The mechanical suit's original energy level of just over 20,000 had increased to 57,000, more than two times the original!

With such a large jump in attributes, it could be seen just how important Cutting-Edge Knowledge was.

Han Xiao released Mechanical Force from his palms and connected to the Berserk Ape suit. The next moment, the Berserk Ape suit rapidly covered his entire body, and the equipping process only took an instant.

With a single thought, the arm of the mechanical suit transformed into an exquisite cannon barrel, and Han Xiao aimed at an alloy wall used to test weapons.

After the energy furnace was replaced with a psionic energy reactor, the weapons of the Berserk Ape suit had also been upgraded to become psionic weapons. After adjusting the canon to burst mode, Han Xiao fired without hesitation.

Bang!

A crisp sound could be heard, and a blue light pulse was shot out from the canon. The light pulse rapidly expanded as it traveled through the air and exploded when it came into contact with the target.

A blinding light flashed by.

Boom!

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, and when he took a look at the wall again, the entire alloy wall had been reduced to rubble with dust floating in the air.

"Not bad." Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Psionic energy truly lived up to its reputation. Just changing a single energy furnace had resulted in such a huge increase in strength. Of course, there was also the effect of the [Extreme Energy Output].

Because primal psionic energy was not stable, an ordinary psionic weapon would only be able to use the 'dormant' psionic energy being produced from a psionic reactor. Before the psionic energy was activated, it would not expand.

Only the strategic class weapons between civilizations would pursue the pure destructive force of primal psionic energy. However, psionic weapons that were extremely destructive were heavily restricted. If a civilization made use of such a weapon, Star Cluster civilizations or the three great civilizations would investigate the matter. After all, no one wanted to see a planet within their territory getting flattened by a weapon.

All civilizations were extremely wary of Mechanics who had grasped psionic energy. It did not matter if they wanted to be a litterbug. However, they could not choose to freely throw psionic energy around.

Han Xiao still was not able to refine something like a Planetary Destroyer. His level, Intelligence, and knowledge were not sufficient at the moment. He would only be able to do so after reaching the level of Manison from the [Mechanic Empire]. This was also a specialty of a beyond Grade A Super.

Han Xiao then tested the piercing, fully automatic, and other modes of the psionic canon before testing the shield module of the Berserk Ape suit.

Because of the new energy furnace, the shield had also transformed into a psionic shield. The original appearance of the nuclear shield was a half-transparent mirror-like shield glowing either yellow or blue.

As for the psionic shield, its exterior was like a bubble with two thirds of it being transparent and colorless. Outside the colorless region, the shield was blue in color, gradually turning darker toward the outside. The entire shield was more circular and not as angular as before, with the durability of the shield being greatly enhanced.

At the same time, because of the assimilation property of psionic energy, the psionic shield would absorb a small amount of damage when being struck to replenish the durability of the shield, allowing it to last longer.

The psionic shield also came with the ability to perform a short-ranged charge. Han Xiao activated his psionic shield and charged straight at the alloy wall. The alloy wall caved in immediately like soft soil, leaving behind a circular dent.

At the instant of the collision, the durability of the shield fell slightly and transformed into kinetic force to increase the damage.

Even if an ordinary individual covered his fist with the psionic shield and punched normally, they would easily be able to bend a metal pole. This was an important method for a Mechanic to deal with close combat fights.

"Right, I think the psionic reactor has an Additional Ability."

Han Xiao then raised his palm and controlled the energy supplied by the furnace to his palm. With a shake of his wrist, a psionic energy ball floated on top of his palm. It was currently in a dormant state and was extremely stable.

He then pressed the psionic energy ball onto the alloy wall, and the next moment, the entire alloy wall shook, and cracks could be seen spreading out from the surface of the wall.

"Indeed, a psionic mechanical suit can directly release psionic energy."

Han Xiao was extremely satisfied with the results of his test. Directly releasing energy was a very handy skill. Not only would it increase his close combat abilities, it would also allow him to use it in various complicated ways.

After testing the various skills, Han Xiao began to upgrade his machines. The first one that he upgraded with his Berserk Ape suit.

The Berserk Ape suit had been constructed when he was around level 140, and now that his skills had been upgraded, it was time to improve the suit. Han Xiao was prepared to perform an all-round upgrade for the Berserk Ape suit so that it could keep up to his current level and become his core weapon.

The reconstruction of his Mechanical Army was also taking place at the same time. Han Xiao refined a large number of psionic energy particles as the core material and invested a large amount of experience to form a mini psionic energy furnace assembly line.

Apart from that, as Han Xiao's level increased, more high-level blueprints were also unlocked. Han Xiao gambled for some new machines and weapons before constructing their new assembly lines. Very quickly, new batches of high-grade machines came out fresh from the oven.

The Black Star Army's military factory was clearly demarcated into two different sections. The purpose of the logistics factory that Reynold oversaw was mainly to provide for the entire army, and it produced common equipment. Han Xiao's military factory was for his personal use, and all the equipment produced was top quality. Regardless of production speed or quality, it far exceeded the logistics factory.

To date, Han Xiao had only lent the factory to Reynold. It could be said that only a Calamity Grade Super would be allowed to use his personal factory.

The assembly line that Han Xiao had personally constructed enjoyed his personal stat boost. His new talent, [Machinery Truth Knowledge], greatly increased the attributes of the products in his factory. Currently, the cannon fodder mechanical soldiers had attributes no lower than the elite soldiers of his army before his Class Advancement.

At his level, he had almost maxed out the production speed of his assembly line. As long as he was willing to spend money, he would be able to construct a new army within a short time!

Han Xiao spent money like water, and in a short month's time, he completed the reconstruction of his Mechanical Army. Its size was even greater than before his Class Advancement, and the number of soldiers that he had was over a million!

The serial number of his ordinary army reached '016', and he had six elite army units that were numbered from '101' to '106', making a total of twenty-two Army Boxes.

He truly could do as he wished if he was rich!

In the past month, Bloodshed Land had steadily advanced, and the other two vanguard forces had also revealed themselves and invaded two other Star Systems on the border.

By this point, Bloodshed Land's target was extremely clear. They wanted to occupy West Wind, Kaya, and Chaida, the three Star Systems on the border.

Bloodshed Land intentionally fragmented the battlefield up into many different regions, and Section Zero invested all their members into the war to launch a counterattack in the three Star Systems. However, under the ferocious assault of Bloodshed Land, Section Zero was on the losing end.

The situation in Kaya and Chaida was slightly better than the battlefield in West Wind, which was the most dangerous. The eight Vanguard Officials had gathered together, resulting in the high-level combatants of Section Zero choosing to avoid battle. They were not able to stop Bloodshed Land's advancement, and the enemy had already set up bases on six different planets.

As they captured more planets, Bloodshed Land began to gradually reduce the speed of their advancement. The military forces of the vanguard army were limited. After leaving behind soldiers to guard the captured planets, the number of soldiers that they could mobilize greatly decreased. After the many battles, the vanguard army also suffered considerable losses. However, the vanguard army brought along their own logistics factory and began constructing battleships on the spot to replenish their losses.

The mission of the vanguard army was only to set up a bridgehead for their main army. They took just a month to complete the mission, and after that, they stopped their advancement and waited for the arrival of the main army.

The main army naturally would not cross the barren cosmic belt slowly like the vanguard army did. Klent had already made preparations before the battle to stealthily set up a transit station in the barren cosmic belt. They used their Star Cluster level skills to construct a stable stargate so that the transportation of reinforcements and resources would take considerably less time.

Klent's transit station was hidden within the barren cosmic belt. While the Purple Crystal Civilization did not know of its exact location, they were aware of its existence.

On the base that they had set up, the vanguard army had also brought the spare parts and Klent's technological staff to set up a stargate. The moment the construction was complete, their logistical issue would not be a problem, and they would be able to receive a never-ending supply of reinforcements.

Even if the Purple Crystal Civilization understood what Klent's strategy was, they did not have the strength to stop it. After the vanguard army constructed a few strongholds, they immediately set up a Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station to connect all their strongholds to reinforce each other.

The moment one of their strongholds was under attack, the other strongholds would be able to send reinforcements.

In order to deal with the Mutation Disaster, Godora had once used the Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station. This was Star Cluster level strategic equipment that was commonly used in galactic wars. Godora had also bought it from a Star Cluster level civilization.

Section Zero had tried to destroy the stargate multiple times with all their attempts ending in failure. Only then did they change their strategy so as to not waste their soldiers. They had changed their strategy with the main focus being to harass their enemy.

Purple Crystal invested a large amount of resources to allow the members of Section Zero to expand their fleets and replenish their troops.

Despite Ralph not mentioning it, it was obvious that Section Zero had decided to take his advice.

With the resources and production capabilities of a Star Cluster Civilization, as long as Bloodshed Land completed the construction of the stargate, this war would end up becoming a long war. Both parties would be able to replenish their armies without end and dump a never-ending supply of resources into the war.

While soldiers would die, the battleships would never be used up.

Both parties' ability to fight the war for ten years was because they had a hefty accumulation of resources. Fighting a war required money, and both parties were competing in production capabilities.

After not participating in the war for a month, the current situation of the secret war did not have much to do with Han Xiao. He reconstructed his Mechanical Army and continued to expand his army. The first batch of resources that the Purple Crystal Civilization had given him had been used up. A full 10,000,000 Enas had been used up, and he even had to take out some money from his own savings.

After spending such a large sum of money, the Black Star Army had constructed more than a hundred new battleships and hired a new batch of mercenaries.

Fighting a war burnt a lot of money. If he did not participate in the secret war, Han Xiao would not have received the support from a Star Cluster Civilization.

After skiving and preparing for a month, Han Xiao was prepared to complete his Promotion mission before returning to the battlefield.

Farming faction contribution was still useful as Purple Crystal still had a few Cutting-Edge Knowledges that he had not learned.

Han Xiao wanted to fight Lagi to exchange pointers, but a few uninvited guests showed up at his base.

Chapter 664: Lagi's Past, Creeping Evil

After the start of the secret war, the Black Star Army had conducted several additional recruitments. The seedlings of the training camp had matured, and many freelance mercenaries had also been recruited. The Black Star Army had supplemented its new blood, with the number of official mercenaries exceeding 200,000. The number of personnel stationed at Base No.1 was ample.

Three masked Mages in dark hooded robes walked into the hall of Base No.1, drawing the eyes of many mercenaries along the way. The Hidden Red Robe Abbey was known by the entire Star Field. 'Magus' Austin's Forbidden Sorcerers were very famous and instantly recognizable.

Why are Austin's people visiting the captain?

Quite a few people knew that the captain was the Dragon Emperor's officer. Upon seeing that Han Xiao was in contact with another Beyond Grade A, they could not help but wonder.

The three Forbidden Sorcerers arrived in the reception room, where they saw Han Xiao and nodded politely.

Han Xiao waved his hand and asked Sylvia to get the hell back to studying. He then looked at the three people and asked, "Austin's Forbidden Sorcerers, what is this about?"

The short Forbidden Sorcerer in the middle, Desoro, was the leader of the three. He gave a simple self-introduction and then cut to the chase.

"The Magus ordered us to find someone, one of your subordinates. We're here to bring him back."

Han Xiao was dumbfounded. This surprised him. "Are you talking about Lagi?"

Of all the officers, only Lagi had an unknown origin. Plus, he was a Grade A+ Mage, so he had the highest chance of being the target of these three people.

"Yes, his full name is called Lagi Schwer. He worked under the Magus before." Desoro's tone was calm. His statement was ambiguous, and it seemed like he did not want to give the details.

Han Xiao was secretly surprised. Lagi had been imprisoned for ten years, and no one had rescued him. Now that he had escaped, Austin's people had come looking for him right away.

Although he clearly knew that Austin would not be so despicable, it did feel a little annoying.

He thought about it and realized that it was odd. If Lagi was Austin's subordinate, how could he have been caught so easily? Lagi seemed like a lone ranger before getting caught, and if it was true, it meant that he had been removed from Austin's forces. So, why would Austin send people to get Lagi back?

"Why are you bringing him back?" Han Xiao asked.

Shaking his head, Desoro refused to answer, saying, "This is the order of the Magus. We just execute it."

Han narrowed his eyes and asked, "What if I refuse?"

Desoro's voice was calm and unshaken. "The Magus said that you owe him a favor and will give him face."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He was one to give in to the soft approach instead of the hard approach. During the Tyrant's party, Austin had given him the core of a Void Lord without any reason, so he did indeed owe him a favor. There were indeed no free lunches in the world.

Now, Han Xiao would be out of his mind to fall out with Austin, who had a good relationship with him. Moreover, he had once received a gift from him, so he really could not refuse. After all, relationships were mutual—A helped B, so B should help A in the future within the range of B's ability. Otherwise, it would be easy to bury the relationship that took effort to establish.

Only, Han Xiao was still a bit reluctant. Lagi was the second strongest combatant in the Black Star Army, second only to Han Xiao himself. If he left, the high-level combatant standard would fall drastically.

After a moment of consideration, Han Xiao came up with an excuse and said, "Us discussing where he will be going is actually meaningless. I think it is necessary to ask him for his opinion. If he wishes to go back with you, I will, of course, not force him to stay. If he does not want to go, I won't be able to do anything about it."

"Okay." Desoro nodded and had no objection.

In fact, on the way, Desoro had envisaged many situations. If Black Star used all sorts of excuses to obstruct him and not even give face to Austin, he would not exclude the possibility of having to take Lagi away by force.

He did not expect that Black Star would suddenly become a Beyond Grade A seed with a history of fighting eight Calamity Grades at once. This had shocked him.

Clearly knowing that he was miles away from being able to do something like that, Desoro feared Black Star. Black Star had shown that he had the potential to become a Beyond Grade A. Although Austin had Desoro's back, it would not be a good idea for him to establish a bad relationship with Black Star, hence his rather friendly behavior.

Han Xiao sent Lagi a message. After a while, Lagi pushed open the door and walked in while complaining.

"Is there another dangerous mission? I'm telling you, I will die sooner or later if you keep sending me to these... hmm?"

Lagi walked in and saw the three Forbidden Sorcerers. His complaining stopped, and his expression collapsed. He muttered, "No wonder I kept getting distracted during yesterday's meditation. Something bad is indeed happening today. Sigh..."

A tint of coldness flashed across Desoro's eyes as he said in an indifferent tone, "It's been a long time, Lagi."

"Can you pretend you didn't see me?" Lagi's face was bitter.

"What do you think?" Desoro replied.

With no alternative, Lagi looked at Han Xiao with grief and sorrow.

Han Xiao's eyes twitched. "Don't look at me like this. They came to me and said that they're going to take you back. So, you used to be Austin's subordinate. Why didn't you tell me? Him and I are quite close."

"How would I know that you knew Austin?" Lagi asked with an aggrieved expression.

Being Austin's subordinate before was an amazing record and would get him a very high position in the majority of organizations. Lagi did not tell Han Xiao because he wanted to remain low key. Moreover, he felt that Black Star and Austin should have nothing to do with each other. He never expected that Han Xiao and Austin had talked and laughed together before.

"You don't seem to want to see Austin's people." Han Xiao frowned slightly. "There's no need to hide your past now. Tell me."

Desoro glanced and Han Xiao and did not say anything to stop him.

Lagi sighed and had a sad expression on his face as if he did not want to get into it. Han Xiao almost wanted to give him a cigarette so that it would match his expression and the atmosphere.

"Alright, I'll tell you. Decades ago, I was the Hidden Red Robe Abbey's Forbidden Sorcerer commander, the fourth disciple of Magus Austin."

Han Xiao's eyes immediately widened.

Holy... you're quite someone, aren't you?

The position of the Forbidden Sorcerer commander was roughly equivalent to the chief Vanguard Official under the Tyrant. The fourth disciple meant that he was one of Austin's protégés. These two titles added together, and Lagi's position in the past was basically Austin's right-hand man.

Lagi waved his hands with that same sad, reluctant expression. "However, afterward, I made a mistake, and Austin kicked me out of the Hidden Red Robe Abbey. I left Austin, became a Lone Ranger, and then I was caught. You saved me, and then you know the rest."

Han Xiao was shocked. With Lagi's position, what big mistake could he have made to cause Austin to chase him away?

At this point, Desoro coughed and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, it's better if you don't know."

Han Xiao's eyes moved but became more curious. He then turned his head and saw that Lagi's expression had become incredibly forlorn, as if he suddenly had stubble on his face.

"Alas, everyone has been young and wild before. Magus really is a good man. It's a miracle that I could live till now," Lagi said with a nostalgic tone.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. It was very difficult for him to imagine Lagi being young and wild. It felt like a man with this name was born with a languid aura. He could not associate him with the adjectives 'young' and 'wild' at all.

"Alright, let's get back to the point. I respect your opinion. If you want to go back with him, I won't stop you, but if you want to stay, I'll help you refuse them."

Desoro's brows furrowed. He thought for a moment and did not speak.

He rubbed his face and sighed. "I'll go back with you."

Desoro heaved a sigh of relief. Luckily, Lagi read the room, so he did not have to fall out with Black Star.

He turned to Han Xiao and said, "Your Excellency Black Star, he's willing to come with us. Please abide by our agreement."

"Alright then."

Han Xiao sighed in his mind. Lagi was a great aid who had been difficult to acquire, and now he was leaving him. It felt like a neighbor reaching out to his vegetable field and pulling a high quality, emerald-like leek.

This time, Lagi suddenly opened his mouth and spoke with a very serious tone.

"Black Star, you saved me. Don't doubt my belief of doing things for you. I'm going back to make it clear to Austin. Otherwise, they won't give up, and I don't want to cause you trouble..."

After hearing this, Han Xiao immediately felt that he was wrong about Lagi. The little discontentment in his heart disappeared instantly. He was even a little touched.

Wow, you're actually quite reliable. Saving you definitely wasn't meaningless.

Then, Lagi returned to his original tone and became indolent, muttering, "You can't beat Austin anyway. There's no use even if I do refuse. Me going back with them is good for everyone. Sigh..."

What? That's not false at all!

Han Xiao could not help but ask Desoro, "What was Austin thinking, appointing him as the commander of the Forbidden Sorcerers? Is he not worried that all the Forbidden Sorcerers will become depression patients under his lead?"

"Er... he wasn't like this in the past." Desoro's tone was awkward.

They exchanged a few more polite lines. Then, Desoro stood up and said, "My mission is complete. I shall bring him back now."

Han Xiao was just about to nod but suddenly remembered something and hurriedly stopped the bunch of them who were about to walk out.

"Wait a minute. I need your help with something."

Desoro looked back and wondered, "Please, do tell."

"Er... I would like to spar with you guys," Han Xiao said.

Including Lagi, there were four strong people in front of him, who should all be twenty or more levels higher than him. This was a good opportunity to do the Promotion mission. If he beat all of them, it would give him twenty-four Trial Points, directly completing half of the mission progress. An opportunity like this would not come again once it was gone, so even though it was sudden, Han Xiao still asked for it.

As expected, Desoro and others all felt bewildered and confused.

Why is Black Star suddenly making this request?

Desoro was dumbfounded for a few seconds before he remembered to answer.

"Er... why is that?"

"When I see a formidable opponent, I can't help but want to fight with him. The Forbidden Sorcerers are very famous, so I want to experience your strength and test my new weapon while doing so." Han Xiao quickly made up a reason.

"Er..." Desoro was still hesitant.

Han Xiao clenched his teeth and took out the most promising trump card.

"Play a little bit. You're here anyway..."

It was indeed the most promising trump card. Once used, Desoro did not know how to refuse.

Originally, he just wanted to take Lagi back and finish the mission early.

However, now that he had been invited to a fight, he suddenly became interested in a contest!

People had been saying that Black Star was a Beyond Grade A seed. Only a few dozen people in the entire Star Field had that honor.

Although Desoro was just an officer of a Beyond Grade A Super, he too dreamed of becoming a Beyond Grade A.

Desoro wanted to measure what made a Beyond Grade A seed so exceptional and see how big the difference in their strength was.

Thinking about that, Desoro stopped hesitating and became eager. He stared at Han Xiao and said, "Okay, you pick the place."

Hearing Desoro's response, Han Xiao had a humble smile of a farmer on his face. The way he looked at Desoro and the others was like looking at a few walking leeks.

"By the way, I want to spar with you too." Han Xiao pointed to Lagi, who thought he had nothing to do with it.

Lagi's face turned bitter, and he muttered, "I see, so this is where I get 'accidentally' killed during a spar..."

Meanwhile, on Planet Aquamarine...

"So, this is Black Star's home..."

A spacecraft in stealth mode was suspended in outer space. Through the porthole, Stephanie looked over at the azure star, smiling.

"Albert was such a fool. There's a glaring weakness, but he didn't know how to exploit it..."

Chapter 665: Thrashed

Three years ago, when the Mutation Disaster ended, all sorts of galactic financial groups followed Black Star and invested in Planet Aquamarine, which was nominally a Floating Dragon territory. The long-standing technological bottleneck had easily been broken as interstellar knowledge poured in, and the stalled progress of the civilization began to grow rapidly.

No one had forgotten the significance of Han Xiao's actions. In commemoration of the person that changed the fate of this planet, Bennett had led the effort to build a city named after Han Xiao based on Black Phantom Sanctuary.

That was Black Star City.

The survivors in the sanctuary became the residents, and countless people from the Six Nations moved to this city. Now, the budding Black Star City was the most popular city on Planet Aquamarine. The center of the city was the base of the Black Star Army. The tall, square-point tower pointed directly to the sky, with a huge Black Star Army sign carved on the tower's body. The height of the buildings decreased from the center of the city to the edge. The overhead electric rail bridges crisscrossed, where the magnetically suspended trains shuttled continuously. The lights were bright both in the day and at night.

The galactic financial groups had come for Black Star and Floating Dragon, so Black Star City received the most investments. The technological level of this city was the highest on Planet Aquamarine. The capitals of the Six Nations were like the countryside in comparison. Black Star City was the 'city of the future' on Planet Aquamarine.

Although the treaties laid down by the three major civilizations contained rules that forbade interfering with the progress of low-level civilizations, these were primarily aimed at protecting the low-level civilization from being violated. If they were supporting their development, as long as the region's governing civilization did not mind, no one would make any trouble. Of course, Godora would not prevent Han Xiao from rebuilding his homeland.

Under the protection of Han Xiao, the Six Nations were thriving, developing technology, supporting people's livelihoods, and restoring the environment. Compared to three years prior, Planet Aquamarine had changed dramatically. With Han Xiao's approval, Bennett had also changed the purpose of the organization and formed a new political system with Black Star City as the capital, forming the seventh nation in the world. They were gradually developing toward a Galactic Civilization.

The ten people including Stephanie landed in the wilderness outside Black Star City, looking out at the distant city.

"This is the home of Black Star. Based on the intelligence we gathered, his mother planet is of great importance to him, and he's devoted a lot of energy to it," one member said.

Stephanie slowly nodded.

After arriving in the Shattered Star Ring, she had not rushed into action but instead collected information for a while, learning about this mess that Albert had left behind.

The people that Albert caught had all been rescued by Black Star and were now connected to each other. If she acted carelessly, once she caught one of the freed men, the others would be alerted and become aware that someone else was hunting them again. Albert's failure had made Stephanie's job very difficult.

Stephanie was not planning to build a base like Albert did. She decided to stay in the dark, sending one target away right after she caught them, never staying in the same place for an extended time.

It was less efficient but less risky.

She was also not planning to seek cooperation from Klent. Klent had taken the blame for them, so it was highly likely that they would sell her out to clear their name. Furthermore, she did not build a base, so intelligence channels were less important to her.

In this case, the most difficult-to-deal-with target, Black Star, became the best first target. He had killed six people, including Albert, saved everyone captured, and made Albert's years of accumulation go to waste. Plus, he had become a Beyond Grade A seed. He had a lot of potential and was the best prey. His Excellency Thousand Shadows would love it very much.

"Black Star is in a war, so we won't have a very good chance of getting to him. However, as long as an enemy appears on his mother planet who only he can handle, he'll definitely come back and deal with it. I'm not as reckless as Albert, not taking advantage of things like this."

Instead of attacking Black Star's territory or taking the risk of messing with the secret war, Stephanie chose to set a trap to lure Black Star into an ambush. The battlefield was set on Planet Aquamarine, which seemed like the dominant battleground for Black Star, but would actually make him cautious and careful.

Including herself, ten Calamity Grade 'shadows' might not be able to kill the nicknamed 'Indestructible Body' Black Star, but capturing him would not pose an issue.

"Even if he has the potential to be a Beyond Grade A Super, he isn't Beyond Grade A now." Stephanie's expression was cold and calm.

Looking out into the azure sky, Stephanie took a deep breath and felt the coldness in her lungs. She narrowed her eyes with pleasure, smiled faintly, and said, "Hehe, I never thought that I would miss the whole war era after sleeping. This place is like my hometown, a prosperous planet... I really want to smash it."

The other nine people glanced at each other and did not speak.

They were not familiar with Stephanie, but they knew that this captain was not a 'shadow' of their time.

...

Whoosh!

The Blacklight Stealth landed on an unpopulated planet, and Han Xiao, Desoro, and the others walked out of the hatch.

"Here will do. The space is big enough, and there's no need to worry about the damage caused." Han Xiao smiled.

He did not choose the base as the sparring venue. With just one accidental impact released during a fight between Calamity Grades, the base would vanish. Besides, the walls of the training room were not necessarily strong enough, and he did not want to incur unnecessary losses.

Desoro was silent and expressed his attitude with actions. His hands were reached out sideways, bright golden magic patterns appeared on his black robe, and magic forces surged. The robe was flapping as if it had rolled up a typhoon. His pupils under the hood were flashing with lightning, and anticipation for battle filled the air.

Lagi and the other two Forbidden Sorcerers retreated from the battlefield.

Feeling the immense fighting spirit, Han Xiao pulled on his necklace with his Mechanical Force. A brand-new mechanical suit model instantly covered his whole body. It was more beautiful than the Berserk Ape. It had a streamlined, silver-black shell with glowing blue patterns.

Despite being more aesthetic than Berserk Ape, it was much more violent.

This was an updated version of the Berserk Ape, also a Nano Transforming Mechanical Suit of the Ape series. Its name was [Mountain Ape]!

While the level requirement for Berserk Ape was 135, for Mountain Ape it was 165, a whole 30 levels higher. Han Xiao had used a great deal of rare raw materials and integrated new technology, which greatly increased the attributes of this mechanical suit.

Its armor value was over 110,000, and its Power Level was close to 5,000. Its performance was extremely strong.

While the Berserk Ape specialized in having strong power, Mountain Ape specialized in having strong energy. This was due to the superiority of the psionic reaction furnace. While the Berserk Ape was more focused on close-range combat, Mountain Ape used psionic energy to battle and could excel in both close and long-range battles; it was more versatile.

"Come on!" Desoro yelled. A magic jewel on his collar sparkled brightly. The next moment, a dazzling magic array appeared under his feet, turning into a giant black vortex that seemed to connect to another dimension.

A giant twelve-fingers palm emerged from the vortex. Its texture was like obsidian, full of glowing golden cracks. The hand alone was close to a hundred meters long. It slammed violently on the ground.

Bang!

The ground trembled!

"Summoner Mage? Superior Magic Colossus?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

The Summoner class was as unreasonable as the Army Style. All the Forbidden Sorcerers were magic masters and knew spells of many styles. It seemed like Desoro was mainly a Summoner.

Using a large summoner spell right in front of me? Do you think I don't exist?

Han Xiao curled his lips and crossed his hands, forming an oval shape and aiming at Desoro. A blue, azure light particle appeared between his palms. It then expanded rapidly with a blinding light, shooting out a huge blue beam!

As Desoro maintained the Summoning spell, the pattern on his robe lit up. A high-energy magic shield appeared in front of him, and the blue beam crashed into it. At that moment, Desoro felt an immense sense of danger. His pupils constricted, and he immediately withdrew the Summoning spell, teleporting a few hundred meters away.

Boom!

The blue light beam instantly swallowed up the magic shield and then went into the ground. The ground cracked rapidly, and blue light emitted from the cracks and shot up into the sky.

Rumble!

A blue pillar, dozens of times larger than the beam, shot out from the ground, rising up like a fountain.

Psionic Impact—Whale!

One of the Mountain Ape's abilities!

The energy beam vanished into the sky, and the ground turned into a circular crater hundreds of meters in diameter. As the summoning spell had ended early, only one arm of the Magic Colossus was summoned, which was nearly shattered by the explosion.

"You can use psionic energy‽"

Desoro's tone became extremely grave.

A Mechanic that could use the psionic and a Mechanic that could not were two completely different concepts!

"Wouldn't that happen..."

Before Han Xiao finished his sentence, his body suddenly became blurry. Powerful impetus infused with psionic energy turned him into a lightning bolt, leaving a blue shadow behind. Han Xiao flashed in front of Desoro in an instant. His fist wrapped in psionic shield crashed down on Desoro's magic shield with the second half of the sentence!

"... sooner or later?"

Bang!

The two of them crashed into each other!

An enormous amount of energy came from the psionic shield. The magic shield was shattering piece by piece!

Desoro was heavily hit, and he flew out like a shooting star. Leaving a blue trail, Han Xiao caught up with Desoro midway and caught him by the back of his head. His hands gripped Desoro's neck and threw him up into the sky.

Mountain Ape Throw!

Compared to Berserk Ape's [Berserk Throw], the Mountain Ape version gave fifty more Strength but a lower damage count. Also, it had an extra 0.5-second stun time. Generally, it was more of a disabling ability now.

Squeak!

Han Xiao stopped instantly. The mechanical suit on his arms turned into joint energy cannons. The dozens of barrels aimed at Desoro in the sky.

Bang bang bang!

In the blink of an eye, psionic beams rushed out of the barrel one after another, catching up with Desoro. The light illuminated his fearsome eyes.

Boom!

Continuous blue explosions appeared in the sky!

The bright light lit up the Mountain Ape's helmet, and the scorching hot air was swirling.

Under the mask, Han Xiao smiled.

A Mage's weakness was also close-range combat!

Whoosh!

With a flash of light, Desoro teleported out of attack range once again. He was injured and rather flustered. Then, he started casting a spell without a word. After all, he was an elite Mage under Austin's command. Although the situation was not looking good, he would not be so easily defeated.

However, Desoro had to admit that, although he did not look down on Black Star, Black Star's combat capability was still beyond his expectations.

Zoom!

With the light of summoning spells, strange and weird creatures were summoned one after another. Desoro even cast dozens of instant enhancing spells on himself to guard against Han Xiao from closing the distance again, only to find that Han Xiao had no intention of stopping his summoning.

Han Xiao smirked. As he clapped, the space around him suddenly started to ripple and buzz.

"Channeling spell? I can, too!"

Hum!

A beam of light flashed around him, and twenty-two Army Boxes appeared out of thin air.

In order to improve the efficiency of the army, Han Xiao did not care about the cost and equipped the Army Boxes with energy stoves and hyperdrive engines. This way, the support range and speed of the mechanical army increased greatly. He did not need the Blacklight Stealth to airdrop them anymore.

Most importantly... it looked so much cooler!

The purpose of sparring with these people was not only for the Promotion mission but also to test the combat ability of the new mechanical army. Thus, of course, he was going to use everything he had.

As Han Xiao pulled with his fist, a Mechanical Force lightning chain grabbed onto every Army Box.

Boom boom boom!

The Army Boxes vibrated, and they were opened. Countless compressed orbs were sprayed out, turning them into a mechanical army.

In front of the large mechanical army, Desoro's summoned creatures were like lambs surrounded by wolves, weak and helpless.

"Get him!" Han Xiao pointed at Desoro, who was panicking.

Boom!

The Mechanical Army swallowed Desoro's summoned creature army.

The scene became chaotic instantly.

As soon as the two armies clashed, the strength difference became crystal clear—Desoro's army could only hold on for a few seconds. The situation turned into a one-sided thrashing!

Chapter 666: Round Three

Both the Army Style and the Summoning Style relied on numbers. The summoning class used mana, so it did not cost a lot of money. Even if the summoned creatures were destroyed, they could still be summoned the next time. However, it took a lot of time to summon those creatures during battle.

As for the Army Style, it required a lot of money. The army would be built before the battle and could all be used immediately. Once destroyed, money would be needed to rebuild them. The good thing was that the time to get the army ready was very short.

The rebuilt mechanical army used psionic energy as the main energy source. Most machines were modified to be psionic powered. The electromagnetic cannons had all been swapped out for psionic cannons that were many times stronger. Even the mechanical soldiers were equipped with psionic shields and small-caliber psionic lasers among other things.

The psionic energy technology was extremely useful. The cost of building machines did not increase by a lot, but their combat capabilities rocketed.

Under Phillip's control, the mechanical army quickly defeated Desoro's summoned creatures. With the [Machinery Truth Knowledge] bonus, Han Xiao was satisfied with the individual combat capabilities of the mechanical soldiers. He estimated that one mechanical soldier could defeat five of the same model mechanical soldier before his Class Advancement.

Bang bang bang!

The explosions continued in the sky. The battle was one-sided. The creatures summoned by Desoro were already wiped out, leaving him to face the mechanical army alone. Even without the summoning spells. Desoro was still a very strong Mage. He cast powerful spells very quickly and smoothly.

The battlefield was an unpopulated planet, so both sides were not restrained at all. They unleashed destructive forces freely. Desoro constantly teleported, and the mechanical army surrounded and intercepted him. The battlefield constantly shifted and extended over thousands of miles. The powerful forbidden spells and psionic cannons bombarded the surface. The earth was completely disorganized and filled with deep craters from explosions. If this was a planet with a civilization on it, the buildings would have been flattened long ago.

Being surrounded, Desoro was having a tough time like he had fallen into a swamp—every movement was difficult to make.

If this was the mechanical army before Han Xiao's Class Advancement, Calamity Grades would not have felt too threatened even if they were surrounded. For the stronger Calamity Grades such as the eight Vanguard Officials under the Tyrant, they would be able to go in and out through the mechanical army easily. All it could do was slowly reduce the enemy's health and energy.

However, the mechanical army after his Class Advancement had much more destructive and restraining power. The psionic cannons and shields caused the army's overall attack and defense ability to go up by many levels.

Even a strong Calamity Grade like Desoro was in a pickle. The Psionic Cannons had much stronger individual power, which meant that the attacks did not have to be too concentrated in one place. Thus, the attacks from the Psionic Cannons seemed to have built a blue spider web, with danger at its every corner.

In terms of defense, the guarding team connected their Psionic Shields into a large shield a few hundred meters in size, like an enormous bubble. Even Grade 6 to Grade 7 spells were unable to penetrate it. Desoro had no choice but to use very powerful and high mana cost forbidden spells to barely cause any damage.

"He's being overwhelmed completely. His loss is inevitable." At the edge of the battlefield, the other two Forbidden Sorcerers' tone changed slightly.

Before the battle, the two of them had also thought of observing how strong Black Star was, but this scene right before their eyes dumbfounded them. They knew very well how strong Desoro was. They had thought that even if Black Star would be able to defeat Desoro, it would happen after a rather tough fight. However, the battle turned out to be one-sided.

"He's even stronger..." Lagi felt complicated.

The time for which he had known Han Xiao was still very short, so this was the first time that he had witnessed Han Xiao's growth speed. When they met for the first time, despite Lagi underestimating his strength as usual, he had still felt that he had a fifty percent chance of beating Black Star. One month ago, when Han Xiao was given the title of Indestructible Body, he had felt that he only had a thirty percent chance of winning.

Now, he felt that he was nothing.

"Such unbelievable growth speed, this is truly Beyond Grade A potential." Lagi's negativity exploded, and he suddenly felt that there was no point in him studying magic anymore. He might as well go home and start a farm or something...

On the battlefield, Desoro held on for a while longer before being so disgusted by the mechanical army that he almost vomited. Not having the will to fight anymore, he yelled, "I admit defeat!"

Han Xiao lifted his finger and stopped the mechanical army, making them retreat to the side.

With the pressure gone, Desoro instantly felt more alive. He took a deep breath, slowly turned toward Han Xiao, and said with a regretful tone, "You've won the spar. I'm no match for you."

If he continued, he could still have fought for a long time, but he felt it was futile. Black Star's mechanical army was so strong and did not give him any chance. Furthermore, Black Star was basically just watching from the side, yet he still had such a tough fight. Even if he continued, he would most likely have had no chance of winning.

"You're very strong, too." Han Xiao smiled. "You should've tried approaching me. Maybe you would've beaten me."

Desoro's face turned back. He wanted to ask if Han Xiao even felt shame but decided not to say it after thinking for a moment.

Black Star's Indestructible Body title was known across the Star Field. Everyone knew that Black Star's strength was his body. Desoro did not live under a rock—it would have been crazy of him to go close to Han Xiao in a battle thinking that he would be able to defeat him that way.

This was also one of the reasons that Desoro had admitted his defeat—he could not see any opportunity to turn the tables.

Luckily, I did not start a conflict with him. Desoro was glad of how sensible he was to give up the thought of using force on Han Xiao. From his perspective, even the first three disciples of Austin would not be able to defeat Han Xiao easily, if at all, so Desoro himself would only be completely thrashed by him.

Desoro was convinced that he was indeed still very far from a Beyond Grade A seed.

Han Xiao gave Desoro a few patronizing compliments. As the victor, he had the right to speak this way, and Desoro saw no problem with it at all. Calamity Grades would not be unable to accept a defeat. The loss only upset him for a while before letting it go, at the same time throwing away his sense of superiority as a Beyond Grade A's subordinate and giving Han Xiao more respect.

Respecting someone stronger was a rule that never changed and never would change, which was even more deeply understood by a Beyond Grade A's subordinate.

You have received 6 Trial Points.

Current Progress: 6/50

While chatting, a notification popped up on the interface.

He's at least twenty levels higher than me. I see, so the definition of winning is to have the opponent admit defeat... Hmm, one person can only give points one time. There are three more people.

Han Xiao was delighted. He turned around and asked Lagi and the other two for a spar as well.

Since Han Xiao personally requested to spar with them, even though the other two Forbidden Sorcerer knew that they would not be able to win, they were not so cowardly as to not even take the fight. After all, it was just a spar.

Desoro felt strange. The way he saw it, Han Xiao wanting to spar with his two colleagues even after he had defeated him was clearly an act of showcasing his strength.

"Apparently, although Black Star did not express it, he's actually very unhappy about us taking Lagi away. Therefore, he requested to spar with us, to showcase his power and beat us up." Desoro felt that this was the truth, but there was nothing he could do.

Those two Forbidden Sorcerers were not summoners, but they were just as strong as Desoro. One of them specialized in psychic spells, which ignored Han Xiao's health-energy cycle and caused him a little bit of trouble. This was one of the few weaknesses that he had at the moment, but he did not let it show.

He had the [Advanced Mental Toughness] talent, so he was not completely defenseless against psychic attacks. Despite not being able to absorb the psychic attacks, he was still very tanky, so he did not panic at all.

Furthermore, if he gave it his all, he could even damage himself to recover energy, which was completely unnecessary for a spar. This Forbidden Sorcerer also admitted defeat very soon.

Lagi was basically a walking pile of negativity. He admitted defeat just one minute into the fight.

After sparring with all four of them, Han Xiao had a rough idea of his combat capability.

I now have two trump cards—my tankiness and the Army Style. As long as it's not against those strongest Grade A+ who are only a tiny bit away from Beyond Grade A, I will be able to maintain a more than 50% win rate. When facing more than one enemy, I can pose a threat to about three Calamity Grades at the same time. If the goal is just to hold the enemies back, ignoring the fact that the enemies will want to escape, I should be able to hold back six to seven Calamity Grades...

As for those who are a threat to me, psychic attacks and Virtual Mechanics are notable. Army Style Mechanics who also have a psionic energy mechanical army are threatening, too, as it will turn into a battle of resources since the style is the same, but I do have the advantage of being very tanky. Also, those Espers with strange abilities are always dangerous.

While summarizing all that in his mind, Han Xiao was chatting with Desoro and the others.

The spar had ended. Desoro expressed his intention to leave, and Han Xiao did not stop him this time.

Before leaving, Lagi made a serious promise. "Austin is a good man. Although I was chased away by him, we still have a connection, and he won't make things difficult for me. Black Star, I will definitely return."

"Alright." Han Xiao smiled. "When you return, you'll be my vice-captain."

Lagi had only joined the Black Star Army for a short time, so he was still on probation. He was currently just a high-level combatant and had not taken on a position yet. With his ability, he was undoubtedly qualified to be the vice-captain. No one would have a problem with a Grade A+ being the vice-captain. Furthermore, he had an amazing resume. Despite being a little negative, he was indeed a talent.

Having developed into a veritable behemoth, the Black Star Army did indeed need one more person that matched up to its fame.

Lagi was stunned for a moment before turning hesitant. "Does that mean I will have more things to do?"

"... I'll just give you the title without the work, how about that?"

Only then did Lagi smile again.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we shall take our leave."

Desoro and the other two nodded before taking Lagi to the spaceship. Han Xiao thought for a moment before giving Lagi an Observer's Mark.

His Promotion was close. His Racial Talents would change by then, so he did not have many chances to use Observer's Marks left. Although Austin would be able to notice the Observer's Mark, it was not a problem. His intention was not to peek at Austin—how could a child looking old Mage be as nice to look at as Ames?

He did not stop Lagi from going back. Putting an Observer's Mark on him was to express his attitude toward Austin, that Lagi was important to him. Unlike the Tyrant, he had no conflict with Austin. In fact, they had quite a good relationship, and Austin had quite high hopes for him.

The spaceship took off and left.

After watching Desoro and the rest leave, Han Xiao looked at the interface.

The Promotion mission progress was now 24/50. It was almost half done.

Nice, that was very efficient. I'm only twenty-six points away. If my opponents are all twenty or more levels higher, I just need five more to complete the mission. If they are less than twenty levels higher or the same level as me, it will take at least seven opponents...

At this time, an unexpected notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the round three mission of [Prey]!

"Huh?" Han Xiao was shocked, and his expression changed drastically.

Chapter 667: Sudden Situation

[Round Three: New Hunters]

Mission Introduction: You have defeated the first group of hunters and seen the tip of the iceberg of this enormous force. Now, a new group of hunters has arrived. They're stronger and more dangerous, staring at you in the shadows, ready to move.

Mission Requirements: Resolve the attack from the new hunter team.

Reward: 78,500,000 Experience. One random ability from one of the members of the hunter team.

The mastermind behind Albert and his gang has sent a new team here, starting the hunt again?

Han Xiao's expression became serious. The high experience reward indicated the difficulty of the third round of this mission.

The mission introduction was ambiguous. All he knew was that there was a group of enemies of unknown strength creeping in the shadows. He knew nothing about what their plan was.

This was like a time bomb, and he did not know when it would explode. The only good news was that the interface notification at least alerted him of this time bomb.

According to the clues in the past, the master of these hunters should be a member of The Ancient Ones from another Star Field. That person still has not given up and has now sent another team that is definitely stronger than Albert's team. This will be quite difficult.

Han Xiao was troubled. Another group of strong enemies appearing during the secret war added uncertainties to the secret war, which was definitely not a good thing.

After pondering for a while, he felt that the most important thing at the moment was to find where the enemies were. Once the enemies showed themselves, it would mean that they had enough confidence to deal with him.

Since the mission notification had alerted him, he wanted to make preparations.

Since the third round has appeared, this means that the new hunter team has already targeted me. In order to capture me, there are a few possibilities...

Han Xiao contemplated but came to no conclusion. He had no idea when and where the enemies would suddenly appear.

Looks like I have to borrow the power of superstition...

He boarded the spaceship and set the destination. The Blacklight Stealth lifted off, turned into a stream of light, and disappeared.

...

A few days later, a spaceship landed on Floating Dragon Island. Han Xiao ignored the cowardly and fearsome looks of the galactic pirates and headed straight to old man Aesop's house.

In the past, old man Aesop's life had been full of excitement and the lack of fear for death. However, for some reason, maybe because he was old now, he had retired on Floating Dragon peacefully, so it was very easy to find him.

"You're saying that a new group of hunters appeared, and they're planning to come for you?"

In the room, Aesop yawned and rubbed his eyes in a flecked nightgown and a crooked nightcap, expressing his doubts about what Han Xiao had said. He had originally been sleeping like an old man but had been woken up by Han Xiao's nonstop calls.

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded.

"Therefore, you came to me because you want me to help you by foreseeing what the enemies will do, right?" Aesop brushed his beard and squinted.

"Yes, the enemies are hiding in the shadows, I need your help."

Aesop suddenly sized Han Xiao up and changed the topic. "I heard you became a Beyond Grade A seed recently?"

Han Xiao was stunned and did not know why he had suddenly brought this matter up, so he could only nod.

"Hmm, I did not expect that to happen." Aesop tutted. "However, don't trust that title too much. It's not that easy to reach Beyond Grade A. It's not just the increase in strength but more of the ascension of life form. Every Beyond Grade A is actually a new race..."

Aesop had come into contact and communicated with many Beyond Grade As before, so he did not mind telling Han Xiao some of what he knew.

Han Xiao listened patiently. Despite having the interface, there were only pros and no cons in listening to experience. As the saying went, having an elderly at home was just like having a treasure.

After speaking for a while, Aesop suddenly shook his head.

"If you do hit the one in ten thousand chance and manage to become a Beyond Grade A, the Ancient One behind the hunters will immediately stop chasing you. The secret war that has been attracting a lot of attention recently will also end because of you alone. As a new Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring, you will be able to immediately sit on the highest dinner table, and those Star Cluster Civilizations will actively bring their cake to share with you. As long as you express your intent, you will be able to easily receive an enormous amount of support. Everything that has been troubling you will be solved instantly..."

Aesop paused momentarily and sighed. "If that day really comes, you will definitely leave Floating Dragon. It's impossible for a Beyond Grade A to be the subordinate of another Beyond Grade A."

Han Xiao did not reply.

Indeed, if he reached Beyond Grade A, he would definitely leave Floating Dragon.

From the beginning, Floating Dragon has always been a stepping stone for him. He had helped Floating Dragon achieve many things throughout the years, so he did contribute as a member. Even if he left Floating Dragon, he would not become Ames' enemy.

Ames might not be happy, but Jenny definitely wanted him to get the hell away as soon as possible.

Aesop rubbed his forehead and said, "Don't mind me. Old people are always talkative. Back to the topic, you gave me too few clues. I won't be able to guarantee how accurate the prophecy is. It can only be used as a reference."

Then, Aesop closed his eyes and started his prophecy.

Not long after, he opened his eyes.

Seeing that Han Xiao was still waiting patiently, Aesop said, "I only saw a few blurry images. A large shadow shrouds you. You dash left and right but aren't able to escape the shadow no matter what. In the end, the shadow consumes you completely."

Han Xiao frowned and asked, "What does this mean?"

"What I saw might not be the reality; it might just be a symbol. I think this prophecy means that the people behind this will keep chasing you, and you won't be able to escape him. In conclusion, it means you're in danger."

"That's it?" Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Are you pulling my leg?

"As I said, there are too few clues. The prophecy is very blurry and might not be right." Aesop shrugged. "If I was all-knowing, do you think you would've caught me back then?"

Han Xiao was speechless.

Is that not the same as saying nothing at all? Why do I feel like even the Destiny's Child Character Summon Card is more useful than you? If not because there's only one last usage left, I would have used it long ago. You're not very reliable, old man Aesop.

Aesop was not of any help, so Han Xiao turned and went to see Ames. Since he was already there, of course, he had to see her.

Ames was alone in the palace, and she was rather happy to see Han Xiao. The two of them chatted for a while. Han Xiao did not see Hila and Aurora, so he asked Ames about it. He then came to know that Hila had been extremely motivated recently for some reason, so she had been dragging Aurora along and training extra hard.

Han Xiao did not tell anyone else about this visit, so he did not plan on disturbing Hila and Aurora. He chatted with Ames for a while longer before bringing up his request for Ames' help.

He instinctively felt that the third round of the mission would be very dangerous. If he could get Ames to help, he would have nothing to worry about.

Unexpectedly, Ames smiled elegantly and exquisitely before rejecting him.

"Black Star, I can't this time. I have something else to do. Plus, you can't keep asking for my help. Maybe this is very dangerous, but you have the potential to become Beyond Grade A in the future, so if you really want to do that, you have to rely on yourself to conquer one obstacle after another."

From the rumors recently, Ames saw the possibility of Han Xiao becoming a Beyond Grade A in the future. Hence, she decided to help Han Xiao less. The way she saw it, danger was a fertilizer. Only through danger would the seed be able to sprout and grow out of the soil.

When Aesop was her mentor, he had used the eagle style of education, too, letting her grow and become independent. Ames had learned from this and used the same thing on Hila and Aurora. The only difference was that these sisters had yet to reach the standard of going out on adventures and battles alone.

As for Han Xiao, Ames had a lot of trust in his strength. She felt that giving too much protection to Black Star was not a good thing—it would reduce Black Star's opportunities to hone himself. She sincerely wanted to see Black Star become stronger, and she would feel happy for him as a friend.

There was nothing Han Xiao could do. After all, Ames was the faction leader—she would not be willing to help him every single time, not to mention the fact that the enemies had yet to even appear this time.

Requesting Ames' help was just to make things easier. If the Dragon Emperor was not going to help, he would do it himself. In the past few years, he had met countless dangers, so he was not going to be afraid, not ever.

After bidding farewell to Ames, Han Xiao left Floating Dragon Island in his spaceship, coming quickly and leaving just as quickly.

He did not receive much from this trip to Floating Dragon Island, so he was unavoidably a little upset. In the end, relying on himself was still the best choice.

As he became stronger and his organization developed quicker, the battles he was in became larger. The help that Floating Dragon could give to him now was not as great as it used to be.

In the cockpit, Han Xiao piloted the spaceship while thinking of a plan.

Ames isn't helping, and Aesop was basically useless, so I have to complete the Promotion as soon as possible. Every little increase in my strength counts...

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao took out the communicator and was about to contact his friends to find people to spar with.

Beep beep!

The communicator suddenly vibrated. It was a sudden message from Bennett.

Han Xiao was shocked. He read through it, and his face instantly turned grave.

It was not good news.

Ever since Bennett built Black Star City, due to all the matters he had to settle every single day, it had been quite some time since he contacted Han Xiao. If there was nothing important, Bennett would not disturb him.

This novice planet had always been rather important to Han Xiao. Although the old players had basically all joined his army, there would still be many more new players in the future.

He was very sensitive at this time. There was no way for him not to connect what was suddenly happening on Planet Aquamarine with the third round of [Prey].

Han Xiao frowned and was on high alert.

"This is certainly a trap!"

...

One day earlier on Planet Aquamarine...

In the government affairs building, Bennett had just finished reviewing the files. He heaved a sigh of relief, put the pen down, and rubbed his temples, trying to ease his tiredness.

"Sigh, being a leader of a nation is more tiring than fighting a war."

Bennett sighed. He picked up the hot tea beside him, blew into it, and sipped slowly. The warm tea flew down his throat, bringing warmth to his stomach. The tiredness started to gradually disappear, and he exhaled comfortably.

He turned his chair around to face the floor-to-ceiling windows, overlooking the city outside. Trains were running along the tracks, and pedestrians were laughing. It was harmonious and lively. He smiled with relief.

Seeing that the people had peaceful and stable lives, Bennett felt that everything was worth it.

Ring ring!

Suddenly, the telephone on the desk rang hastily.

"There's really no time to rest at all."

Bennett picked up the call.

"You—Your Excellency, the Six Nations!"

A government official was on the other side of the call, stuttering with a sharp voice. Bennett could hear his panic clearly even through the call. He felt that his eardrum was hurting and held the telephone a little further away from his ear.

"What are you yelling about? What happened?"

"Th—the Six Nations have declared war on us at the same time!"

Bennett immediately became stiff. His eyes widened and stood up instantly.

"Have all of them gone insane‽"

Clank!

The teacup fell to the ground, and the hot tea spilled all over the floor.

Chapter 668: My Network Is Beyond Your Imagination

The Six Nations declared war without warning, seemingly wanting to eliminate the seventh country that Bennett had built. Bennett spent the entire day trying to prove it. He had personally dialed dozens of phone calls on private lines with the leaders of the Six Nations, which were all rejected. He had no idea why the Six Nations had suddenly gone crazy, and he had no way to find out. He could not deal with such a big matter alone, so he eventually notified Han Xiao.

If the third round of the mission did not appear, Han Xiao would most likely have thought that this was due to the technology given to the Six Nations by the galactical financial groups causing their confidence to expand, thus wanting to regain power... which was also highly unlikely. The Six Nations were not idiots. The more they came into contact with the galaxy, the more they would know how tiny they were; the difference was very clear and visible. The Six Nations would not become arrogant so easily.

The galactic financial groups only invested in Planet Aquamarine because of him and Floating Dragon. He alone was the reason that Planet Aquamarine was developing so rapidly. The Six Nations should know very well that they were depending on Han Xiao—declaring war on him basically meant that they were digging their own graves.

However, the Six Nations had all lost their sanity at the same time. This did not make sense.

"I'm almost certain that there are others behind this, and they're most likely the new group of hunters. These people are more difficult to deal with. They're using Planet Aquamarine to lure me back." Han Xiao frowned.

If he did not receive the alert from the interface, he would definitely have been shocked as soon as he heard about the Six Nations' betrayal. He would also be suspicious, but he would not be as alert as he was now, so he would go back to find out the cause of it.

Making the Six Nations betray him was bait; the real enemies were hiding in the shadows. They had the ability to destroy Planet Aquamarine directly, but that was meaningless. Their real target was Han Xiao, so if they appeared, it would alarm him.

If Planet Aquamarine was destroyed, it would mean that they had destroyed one of the very few 'weaknesses' that Black Star had. They would then have no way to trick him. Hence, they chose to use Planet Aquamarine as a trap and secretly set up an ambush on Planet Aquamarine, waiting for him, the prey, to step right into the trap.

"Luckily, the mission alerted me..."

Han Xiao secretly felt relieved. He had to admit that the enemies this time were much smarter. If he had not been alerted by the mission notification, he might have fallen into this trap. By then, he would have been in a very difficult situation.

"My current advantage is that the enemies think I do not suspect anything, but I already know about their existence."

Han Xiao pondered. The hunters had made the Six Nations betray him for some reason, which was a scheme that he had no choice but to step into. Planet Aquamarine had strategic significance to him; it was a huge leek plantation, so he could not watch the enemies mess up the situation that he had taken so long to build up to. Therefore, he definitely had to go back there and deal with the problems with the Six Nations.

The enemies definitely knew about this.

"Hiding from the enemies will only cause worse damage; only by facing them directly can I possibly resolve the issue. Fortunately, I have time to think about a solution. The enemies' strength and numbers are unknown, but there shouldn't be fewer than six Calamity Grades. It would most likely be difficult for me to fight them alone. I have to get some help."

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and was a little troubled. The Dragon Emperor had said that she would not help, Section Zero was at war, and further organizations would take too long. After thinking for a while, it seemed like the only ally that could be of help at the moment was Godora.

"The Purple Crystal Civilization might be of help, too..." Han Xiao hesitated. Purple Crystal had quite a few Calamity Grades for sure. They were officially a part of the government, so they did not take part in the secret war.

However, Han Xiao was not sure if Purple Crystal would help him. They might only be interested in the war but not this.

"I shall give it a try. It never hurts to ask anyway."

Han Xiao took out the communicator.

He was definitely going to look for help. Unless no one would be helping him, he would not return alone.

Networking was part of one's strength!

On the frontline of the secret war, the army of the Bloodshed Land had arrived at three border Star Systems and had started expanding once again. Section Zero was having an extremely tough time. They could only send small fleets to disrupt the enemies, trying to slow them down.

They were in a very passive position in the war, and countless difficulties were popping up every single day. The never-ending difficulties made Ralph extremely stressed, especially the problems with the high-level combatants.

After all kinds of persuasion and profit promises, the high-level combatants of Section Zero finally stopped avoiding fights, but they still were not willing to go all out. They saved seventy percent of their strength to protect themselves and only used thirty percent to deal with the enemies. In terms of high-level combatants, Section Zero was still completely at a disadvantage, getting beaten black and blue by those war maniacs of the Bloodshed Land. Ralph had been thinking of the reliable Black Star every day.

Although Black Star would not be able to change the situation of the war alone, Black Star was the only one that had given all he had.

Ralph was still settling the matters when his communicator suddenly received a communication request from Black Star. His exhausted mind suddenly became energized.

As soon as Ralph picked up the phone, he said, "Black Star, you've finally contacted me. Has your holiday ended? Quickly come back to the battlefield, we need you!"

Han Xiao coughed and said, "Sorry, I can't go back yet. Civil strife has occurred in my home, Planet Aquamarine. Someone wants to overthrow my representative. I have to return to settle it."

Ralph was disappointed.

"Did you call to notify me of that?"

"No no, I want the Purple Crystal Civilization's help."

Ralph was confused. "Is that necessary? It's merely civil strife of a surface civilization. Aren't you able to settle that yourself?"

"It's not that simple..."

Han Xiao did not hide and told Ralph about the new group of hunters while leaving out the source of this information and changing some of the details.

Currently, only Han Xiao, Aesop, and very few people knew that the true master behind the hunters was one of The Ancient Ones. Last time, when eliminating Albert and gang, Han Xiao did not stop Albert from pushing the blame to Klent, so many Shattered Star Ring organizations thought that Klent was the mastermind, including Purple Crystal.

Han Xiao was hinting that Klent had sent a group of hunters to eliminate him.

After Ralph heard Han Xiao's explanation, he connected the dots and speculated Klent's 'motive'.

Black Star fought the eight Vanguard Officials alone, showcasing his Beyond Grade A potential. Klent planned ahead. They can't let a new Beyond Grade A appear in the Colton Star Cluster even if the possibility of that is just one in a billion. They don't want Purple Crystal to have the opportunity to invest in Black Star, so they sent a group of people to secretly infiltrate the Garton Star System, wanting to eliminate Black Star, the Beyond Grade A seed!

Ralph was shocked and felt that he had discovered the truth. The Klent Kingdom's motive made perfect sense. He could not find anything wrong with his speculation. If he was in their shoes, Purple Crystal would have chosen to do the same thing.

Ralph's expression became serious immediately, and he said in a low voice, "Got it. There's a deeper reason behind this. Black Star, we have very high hopes for you. We won't let Klent threaten you easily. I will submit your request immediately, and the people above should send some high ranking government combatants to help you."

Han Xiao was delighted. It went smoother than he had thought—Ralph was rather easy to bluff.

What he did not know was that the Purple Crystal Civilization upper echelons had held a private meeting long ago and decided to heavily invest in him. Han Xiao still thought that he was just a normal Section Zero member, but in reality, as long as his requests were not too excessive, Purple Crystal would always be willing to help him. In fact, they would want to help him as much as they could.

"By the way, for insurance, I'm planning to ask for help from the Godorans too," Han Xiao added.

"Godora is the ruler of the Garton Star System, right? I remember they're your ally. Sure, they're under us. Do you need me to tell them?"

"... That would be best."

Han Xiao was secretly surprised by how Purple Crystal's people were so easy to convince.

Hanging up the communication, Han Xiao contacted Godora.

Godora was his old ally, so when Serbia the Fifth heard his request, he agreed without hesitation.

If only Black Star had requested help from them, they might have hesitated for a moment. However, Purple Crystal had confirmed that they were involved in this as well, so the Godorans had nothing to be afraid of and were even eager to agree.

In the Godorans' eyes, Black Star was giving them a chance to improve their relationship with the Star Cluster Civilization.

The detailed plan still required discussion. Han Xiao chose an unpopulated planet near Planet Aquamarine as the gathering location and headed over in his spaceship.

Chapter 669: Ambush and Counter-Ambush

In a dark cell, a man whose hands and feet were shackled by electromagnetic handcuffs was sitting on the floor. Light glimmered through the window of alloy bars and lit up his furious face.

"The world outside is in a mess. I can't stay here!"

The man's voice was husky with a very worried tone.

If Han Xiao was there, he would have recognized this man. This imprisoned man was his former boss from more than seven years ago, the ex-director of the Stardragon National Strategic Defense Department, Gu Hui.

He had survived the Mutation Disaster. In the past three years when Planet Aquamarine was rapidly growing, he had retired from Division 13 and been promoted to an upper echelon in the government.

However, a few days prior, his position had been taken away, and he had been imprisoned.

Gu Hui took a deep breath as the images from a few days ago flashed across his eyes.

He was invited to an upper echelon conference. During the meeting, the national leader had suddenly made a decision that petrified everyone—to work together with all the Six Nations and declare war on Black Star City. No matter how strongly the majority of the officials present opposed this, the leader took an extremely strong stand and refused to retract the decision. The several deputy level officials kept silent and shockingly did not oppose it too.

As both sides stood their ground firmly, this meeting ended without them coming to an agreement. However, before Gu Hui could recover from the shock, one hour after the meeting ended, he was secretly captured and thrown into prison.

"I'm definitely not the only one that's been captured. All the opposing officials are locked up, too. The upper echelons are going to declare war no matter what. This is a dictatorship!"

Gu Hui still could not figure out the reason behind this. He was rather familiar with the national leader; such extreme and arbitrary behavior felt like it was a different person.

Black Star was now the protector of Planet Aquamarine, yet they want to fight their own protector? Was that not insanity?

Gu Hui had been locked up for many days and was very worried about what was happening in the outside world. Since the people that opposed the decision had been captured, no one would stop the leader anymore. He could not imagine what the consequences of declaring a war would be. He could only pray that at least the military would still have a clear mind and not just follow orders blindly.

"This will definitely lead to Black Star's revenge!" Gu Hui did not want to imagine Black Star's reaction to this.

That man was no longer that weak Black Phantom of the past!

He could crush the entire Planet Aquamarine alone!

...

"Those Six Nations have declared war on Black Star's forces. This planet is his garden, so he has definitely received the news."

In a certain city of the Six Nations, Stephanie and the rest were walking down the crowded street, coldly observing the riots happening.

Just a few days ago, this city had still been peaceful and harmonious. Now, however, large groups of people were protesting. They were angry and agitated, strongly opposing the government's declaration of war against Black Star.

The military cooperated with the police to maintain security. Yelling, screaming, and roaring was everywhere. The messy footsteps almost trembled the ground. Some people even threw Molotov cocktails at the buildings, igniting flames and fighting with the police.

Chaos reigned!

This scene was happening in many cities of the Six Nations at the same time.

Stephanie looked at the chaotic scene and smiled in satisfaction.

"Good. Black Star will definitely come back here to investigate, but he won't know that we are behind this. He won't know that we are targeting him, so he won't be very alert. We just have to wait in the dark for an appropriate opportunity to give him a 'surprise'!"

As she was speaking, the nine of them turned and walked away before disappearing in a flash of light.

This team had ten members, but only nine appeared there.

...

Ten days later, a stream of light approached an unpopulated planet. This was the gathering location that Han Xiao had set. It was not far from Planet Aquamarine.

The Blacklight Stealth circled around the planet for a while. It then received a signal from the surface and came to the location where the signal was sent. Purple Crystal and Godora's people had all reached there before him, waiting for his arrival.

The spaceship landed, and Han Xiao walked out the hatch. The helpers approached him. Han Xiao looked around—there were six of them.

"Hello Black Star, we're here to assist you. You can call me Wilton. I'm a Purple Crystal Calamity Grade combat officer. These are my two team members..."

Wilton seemed to be their leader. Han Xiao nodded and shook hands with the six of them one by one. All six of them were Calamity Grades. Purple Crystal and Godora had each sent three. The leader of the team on Godora's side was a familiar face—Nagakin.

Even to Star Cluster Civilizations, Calamity Grades were rare high-level combatants, yet Purple Crystal had still sent three to help him, showing their sincerity.

"As per the order from the superiors, you're the commander and can give us orders. Tell me, what do you want us to do?" Wilton said with an expressionless face.

Han Xiao sharply noticed Wilton's impatience. He thought about it for a second and figured out why.

Wilton was a high-level combatant of a Star Cluster Civilization, so he had a sense of superiority and was rather arrogant. However, he had no choice but to follow the orders of a same grade Super who was not even a part of his government. Although he would definitely not disobey the superiors' orders, he would still probably be unwilling.

Han Xiao did not mind it at all. He did not need them to be willing or whatnot—he only needed them to obey his orders and be useful.

"I suspect that the civil strife on Planet Aquamarine is a plot, and there are people behind it. Their goal might be to assassinate me..." Han Xiao repeated what he had said to trick Ralph.

"What do you want us to do?" Wilton asked.

Han Xiao thought about it and said, "Since the enemies are trying to attract my attention by starting a civil strife, they will most likely be hiding till I appear. Let's not alarm them. I will go back alone first as the bait. You guys wait near Planet Aquamarine. When the hidden enemies show themselves, you guys come to support me."

"Okay."

Wilton had no problem with the plan. Although he did not like Black Star, this did not mean that he doubted Han Xiao's body. After all, it was a strong body that had withstood the attacks of the eight Vanguard Officials, so Black Star would definitely be able to last till they arrived.

After discussing it for a while, Han Xiao settled on the plan. The enemies had set a trap for him to step into, but he could use the same method to lure them out. This was the contest between an ambush and a counter-ambush.

After confirming the plan, Han Xiao looked at the few of them. Suddenly, he had an idea and said, "I have a small request. I hope to spar with each of you to test your combat capabilities. Only then will I be able to know the overall strength of our team."

There were six Calamity Grades there; it was definitely a good opportunity to earn Trial Points. His Promotion mission progress was currently at 24/50. If these six teammates were strong enough, he might be able to even complete his Promotion right there.

Wilton frowned.

Han Xiao's request was not nonsensical, but it was too straight forward. It was as if he was doubting their strength. This made him feel like he was being underestimated. Wilton was expressionless but could not help but feel rather annoyed in his heart.

However, he did not even consider fighting Han Xiao seriously during the spar. To him, the mission was the priority. He suppressed his anger and sparred with Han Xiao. This time, the sparring was even shorter than when Han Xiao sparred with the Forbidden Sorcerers. Both of them stopped at a suitable time and did not go all out.

Han Xiao sparred with his six teammates one after another. It went smoothly and did not waste too much time. After all, the six of them were temporarily under his command, so they did not have any objections.

Among the six Calamity Grade helpers, only Wilton was twenty or more levels higher than him and gave him 6 Trial Points. Four of them were less than twenty levels away from him. Han Xiao found an excuse to spar with each of them twice and obtained 4 Trial Points each. In total, he gained 22 Trial Points.

The progress of the Promotion mission was now 46/50, four points away from completion. Sadly, one of the Godoran Calamity Grades was three levels lower than him, so he did not give any Trial Points.

Only four points away. I need one more opponent... Han Xiao hesitated. He kind of wanted to find another person to spar and complete the Promotion before returning to Planet Aquamarine.

However, finding a new opponent would take quite some time. Over the past few days, Bennett had sent him reports every day. The situation was getting worse very quickly. Bennett was hurrying him back all the time, so Han Xiao did not really want to delay it much longer.

Furthermore, as soon as he completed the Promotion, he would go through Race Evolution, and the Observer's Mark ability might disappear. This was a very useful special ability, especially against these elusive hunters.

After pondering, Han Xiao came to a decision. The enemies are ambushing me, so we will fight sooner or later. I have helpers now, so it won't be easy for the enemies to succeed. It won't be too late to complete the Promotion mission during the battle. It's better to keep the Chaos Observer's abilities—they might be useful.

Han Xiao sorted his thoughts and left Phillip's sub-programs to deal with the rest. In case the enemies had ways to cut communication, Phillip could call for reinforcements for him.

As the preparations were completed, Han Xiao did not stay on this planet. He boarded his spaceship and headed to Planet Aquamarine.

...

At the central helipad in Black Star City, the mercenaries stationed there and some of the officials under Bennett received the news and waited for Black Star's return.

Bennett was walking back and forth at the front and glancing at the sky occasionally, appearing rather anxious.

Hu!

As the sound of spaceship approached, the crowd hastily looked up and saw Black Star's signature spaceship slowly landing. Everyone felt relieved as if they had finally found someone to rely on.

The Blacklight Stealth stopped, and Han Xiao stepped onto Planet Aquamarine once again. He saw Bennett and the others immediately and walked over.

"You're finally back!"

Bennett felt as if his shoulders were lighter, like the weight above them had been removed. Recently, he had been very stressed, but as soon as Black Star returned, he suddenly felt no stress at all. Black Star was the protector of the entire Planet Aquamarine; he would be able to solve any problem they had.

Han Xiao nodded and walked toward the base. Bennett and the others followed beside him.

"What's the situation now?"

"The Six Nations have publicly declared war. Both their people and our people are flustered. The intelligence personnel I planted in the Six Nations told me that the Six Nations have already started preparing missiles to attack Black Star City. I don't even dare turn off the protective shields these few days for fear of a sudden attack by the Six Nations. They've gone insane. I cannot judge their actions with logic at all!" Bennett spoke hastily.

Han Xiao curled his lips. "Do all the government officials of the Six Nations agree with the war declaration? I don't believe that everyone has lost their mind. Do you have any information regarding this?"

With a grave tone, Bennett said, "You're right. The Six Nations' decision to declare war was very sudden. Many government officials did not even know about this before it happened. Many opposed it, but a few hours later, all the opposing government officials were captured. The Six Nations are basically under a dictatorship now."

"Collective dictatorship? Ha, that's new." Han Xiao acted as if he was curious and asked, "Have you talked to the Six Nations' leaders?"

"No, they refuse to communicate with me. I have no idea why they're doing this."

Han Xiao squinted. "Then I will have to go to them personally to talk."

He wanted to see what these hunters had done to the Six Nations to make them go insane together.

With a worried expression, Bennett said, "Six Nations won't allow you to get close to them. You have to be careful. They might launch missiles at you."

"Let them try." Han Xiao's tone turned cold. "I've had enough of internal fights. The civilization has been split by too long. It's time to unite it."

Since he was acting as a bait, he had to look real. Han Xiao secretly looked at the government officials following behind him.

The enemies might even be looking at him right now.

Chapter 670: Child's Play

Since the enemies' goal was him, Han Xiao felt that they should have measures to confirm his return. The most likely one would be to have someone watching him in Black Star City, as the Planet Aquamarine people would have no way to discover the enemies. As a Calamity Grade, toying with a surface civilization was as easy as eating and drinking.

With the investment from galactic financial groups, Planet Aquamarine was developing rapidly toward the interstellar era. In just a few years' time, they might be able to build stable interstellar carriers, colonize other unpopulated planets, and other things. However, Planet Aquamarine was still considered a surface civilization at the moment; they had no chance against a Calamity Grade Super.

All the officials that came to welcome him had green names and no red names, but Han Xiao did not completely rely on the interface. In his previous life, there had been some special abilities that could trick the identification of the interface. In fact, his Observer's Mark was one of them.

Han Xiao looked normal but stayed alert. Starting from the moment he landed, the enemy might attack any time.

After chatting for a while, Han Xiao roughly understood the situation from Bennett. He smiled and said, "I understand the situation. There's no need to give the Six Nations time to prepare. I'll go and chat with them right now."

Then, without waiting for the others to reply, mechanical parts covered his body in the blink of an eye and formed into the Mountain Ape mechanical suit. With a blue flame shooting out from his back, Han Xiao took off from the helipad, breaking through the sound barrier, turning into a little black dot, and quickly disappearing.

Bennett's relaxed. With Black Star there, he felt so much more assured.

...

With the efficiency of its galactic engine, Han Xiao flew within the planetary atmosphere. The wastelands, mountain range, and the rest of the landscape receded under him rapidly. Han Xiao left a blue trail behind him and traveled using the planet as the axis. His tracks were very visible even in the daylight. Everywhere he went, many residents on the surface of the planet looked up and discovered this long-standing blue route he took.

Not long after, Han Xiao arrived above the Stardragon capital.

Looking at the familiar city, Han Xiao saw images flashing past in his mind that felt like only yesterday. Without noticing it, almost ten years had passed. This city was where he started.

Thinking for a while, Han Xiao did not hide and landed on the streets. Not far away, a group of people were protesting. The moment they saw Black Star, their faces turned into excitement, and they started to cheer at Han Xiao.

"Look, it's Black Star!"

"Please stop our government!"

"Black Star, those government officials do not represent us. We all support you. No one wants to be your enemy!"

The crowd squeezed over and yelled in a mess, but Han Xiao still managed to understand what those civilians meant.

As he had solved the Mutation Disaster, Han Xiao's reputation in Planet Aquamarine was much higher than that of the Six Nations' governments. He was admired by every Planet Aquamarine resident.

I'm sort of popular.

Han Xiao felt strange. He did not feel troubled, but he did not enjoy this feeling of being loved by so many people either. After all, his target was not just resolving the trap that the hunters had set up but also using this opportunity to overthrow the Six Nations and uniting Planet Aquamarine.

Since my reputation is so high, things should be much easier.

Han Xiao nodded internally. Without greeting the civilians, he quickly left and flew across half of the city, landing in an alley.

Since he had returned, Han Xiao wanted to see the maintenance workshop that he had once worked at.

During the Mutation Disaster, the city had been in a mess. For safety, many people had decided to leave the city. Lu Qian had disappeared and become uncontactable as well. This store had been closed for a very long time, and there had been evidence of it falling apart everywhere.

Now that three more years had passed, this maintenance store had become even more run-down. Still, no one had come back.

Han Xiao shook his head. With Old Man Lu's protection, Lu Qian would not have died in the Mutation Disaster. They might have already settled down in another city and would not be coming back. Since she had not gone to look for him, he did not want to disturb them.

After taking a look at a place of the past, Han Xiao flew toward Dragonhorn Tower where the Stardragon government was, heading right toward the Stardragon leader.

Dragonhorn Tower was very conspicuous. Han Xiao quickly arrived at the destination. Suspended in midair, Han Xiao looked down and smirked.

The ground around the tower cracked open, showing many deep tunnels leading underground. Armored armies appeared from within, and all kinds of firearms and artilleries aimed at Han Xiao.

The basement of Dragonhorn Tower was a military base. When Han Xiao first appeared within the crowd, the Stardragon military received the news. As Han Xiao had come so suddenly, Stardragon did not have enough time to get the missiles ready and could only make some hasty preparations.

With Han Xiao's strength, those armored armies could not even tickle him. Their rather refined gunpowder weapons seemed primitive to him.

Han Xiao shook his head and extended his arm. Several bolts of Mechanical Force lightning launched from his hand.

Clank!

The tanks and artilleries on the ground were sucked up immediately and quickly dismantled into pieces, all turning into waste. This army was eliminated in an instant, leaving the lost and helpless soldiers on the ground.

"The welcome ceremony isn't enthusiastic enough."

Han Xiao felt like he was bullying children... but it did feel good.

With his strength, eliminating the entire Six Nations was a piece of cake.

...

Under Dragonhorn Tower, the Stardragon leader entered the safehouse while being accompanied by the troops. After closing the thick alloy gate, he finally breathed a sigh of relief.

This specially-made safehouse was like a safe. It was extremely thick and would never be penetrated by missiles.

"How're the armored troops?" the Stardragon leader quickly asked the military personnel beside.

"They were wiped out. Black Star only raised his hand a little."

"How could he be so strong‽" The Stardragon leader inhaled deeply.

Suddenly, a loud sound came from the gate of the safehouse.

Boom!

With a flash of psionic energy, the safehouse that could stop missiles now had a hole in it. Han Xiao walked right in. Through the hole, the people inside the room saw countless soldiers behind Han Xiao who were lying on the ground, whining in agony.

Han Xiao really did not want to start a slaughter, so he controlled his strength as much as he could and was barely able to injure them without killing them.

"We meet again." Han Xiao looked at the Stardragon leader.

"Ho—How are you able to come in‽" The Stardragon leader was horrified.

"Hmm?" Han Xiao frowned and noticed the strangeness.

The leaders of the Six Nations should know very clearly how strong he was. It was impossible for them to doubt that he would not be able to even break into this fragile safehouse. However, the shocked expression on the Stardragon leader's face did not seem like an act.

Han Xiao squinted before punching the safehouse wall beside him.

Boom!

The entire safehouse shook. Everyone else could not maintain balance anymore and fell onto the ground, taking slight damage.

The interface immediately received a lot of combat information. Han Xiao instantly opened and read through it.

The level of everyone there was significantly lower than his, so their attributes were all crystal clear.

Including the Stardragon leader, the status bar of everyone in the room had a special status on it.

[Memory Modification]: The memories of this person are modified.

Remaining time: 2 days 13 hours.

"No wonder..."

All his doubts were cleared—this was the reason that the Six Nations had turned on him.

This was undoubtedly an act of those hunters. He did not know what kind of memories the enemies had given the Six Nations' leaders, but they seemed to have forgotten how strong he was. No wonder they were resisting so meaninglessly, even dreaming of taking back power from his hands and overthrowing Bennett's forces.

A person's personality was decided by their experiences. Once their memories changed, their personality would shift, too. Some Psychics who knew special techniques or Espers with those kinds of abilities were able to do things like this, so there was definitely someone like that among the enemies.

Such things were useless to stronger people. Stronger Supers had higher mental resistance. However, Planet Aquamarine only had a few decades' history of Supers. The strongest among them was just Grade C. In front of a Calamity Grade, they were still weaklings that could be toyed with as they liked.

Changing one's memory was a rather subtle and hidden measure, other than Supers with psychic abilities, the other class Supers would not be able to discover what happened to these people instantly.

But Han Xiao was an exception.

The enemies most likely think I won't be able to discover what they did because I'm a Mechanic.

Han Xiao sneered in his mind.

Since the enemies could modify memories, it was meaningless for him to do anything to these government officials as the enemies would be able to modify those people's memories again.

Suddenly, Han Xiao had an idea.

This kind of ability has to be cast at a close range. The status duration on these people is only two and a half days. By then, the hidden enemy will definitely secretly appear and modify their memories again... Hehe, I will then be able to discover their location.

Han Xiao planted an Observer's Mark on the Stardragon leader before pretending he knew nothing about the memory modification and acting like he should have acted—threatening the Stardragon leader to stop the declaration of war.

The government officials present had forgotten about Han Xiao's strength, so they were now terrified and gave in under Han Xiao's threats. They gave orders on the spot and released the captured officials at the same time.

Han Xiao saw his old friend Gu Hui, but he only glanced at him and did not intend to say hello. Since the enemies were still hidden, it was not the time.

After witnessing the Stardragon leader complete his orders, Han Xiao turned around and immediately left the Stardragon capital.

The Stardragon leader and the other officials could not believe it. Was that all? They had thought that they were going to die for sure.

The captured officials, including Gu Hui, were all very glad that Han Xiao did not kill those people. Such gentle measures clearly meant that he was giving them a chance.

Due to this mistake, Gu Hui and many officials decided that they had to impeach the current leader. They could not let this maniac continue leading the nation.

...

Afterward, Han Xiao visited the remaining five nations and convinced every one of them.

He could only plant five Observer's Marks, the mark he had planted on Lagi had already been wiped away by Austin after completing its job.

As Promotion was around the corner, Han Xiao swapped out all the Observer's Mark targets and gave them to five national leaders. He then returned to Black Star City and waited for the Observer's Marks to provide useful information. This was like fishing—it required patience.

To his surprise, the hidden enemies did not attack him during this time. What could they be waiting for? Were they observing him?

Knowing what had happened to Albert, the enemies seemed to be very cautious and were confirming if he had really fallen for the trap.

A few hours later, the Six Nations withdrew the war declarations at the same time. Countless people were cheering and overjoyed.

However, before they could even enjoy the contentment, just one day after, everyone was dumbfounded by the Six Nations' actions.

Having just withdrawn the war declaration, the Six Nations launched missiles at Black Star City the following day!

As if their compromise one day ago was just to earn the time to prepare.

Most missiles were intercepted midair, and the galactic level protective shield of Black Star City stopped the rest of the missiles. There were no casualties. However, everyone in Black Star City was furious at the completely perfidious Six Nations.

Even the people of the Six Nations could not believe it.

Has our government really gone insane‽

Are they asking to be killed? Will they only stop when Black Star kills all of them?

Han Xiao, however, was not angry at all. It was clear that this had happened because the enemies had modified the Six Nations' leaders' memories again. The political conflicts of a surface civilization were no different from children playing house to Calamity Grades.

The good news was, he did not have to wait two days to obtain useful information.

Through the Observer's Marks, an enemy finally appeared.

"These people finally showed themselves."

Han Xiao squinted his eyes.

...

Just one day later, Gu Hui was imprisoned once again before he could execute his plan.

Being imprisoned the second time, he was not even angry anymore.

What is this?

Does the leader think that matters of national importance are just like children playing house, doing whatever they want?

Of course, Gu Hui did not know that the memories of all those officials had been modified. He was completely speechless toward those people who had once been his colleagues.

Chapter 671: I Recognize You!

In Raylen's capital, Zeglin walked slowly in the government building. Everyone he passed—be it government officials, secretaries, or guards—ignored him as if he did not exist. However, if someone was about to bump into him, that person would subconsciously dodge aside.

Arriving at the door of the leader's office, Zeglin did not stop. He pushed the door open and walked in. The guard beside the door did not react at all.

In the room, the Raylen leader was in a call with the military, who also ignored Zeglin. Zeglin tapped his own forehead with his finger, and invisible psychic energy expanded and turned into more than ten tentacles, which then penetrated into the Raylen leader's brain, modifying his memories.

The Raylen leader's words suddenly paused. Confusion flashed on his face for a second before his expression returned to normal, and he continued speaking on the call. In this short pause, his memories had been modified.

Expressionless, Zeglin nodded and left the way he had entered. While walking, he used the psychic mark in his brain and communicated with Stephanie and the others across thousands of miles.

"I checked their memories. Black Star's attitude toward them is very normal. He threatened them and does not know that the memories of these national leaders have been modified. It's basically confirmed that he did not notice anything. We should act soon. He's not alert now, but he might be if we delay this for too long."

Stephanie's chuckling sounded in his mind. "Don't forget what happened to Albert. Black Star is even more cautious than Antarrians. Letting our guard down against him would be foolish. However, you're right—delaying isn't a good idea. The next time he leaves Black Star City, we will set up an ambush over there. In his own territory, he would be more hesitant to attack."

"When I'm done with my job, I will rendezvous with you guys."

Zeglin nodded and then levitated with his psychic energy, flying toward Theseus, which was also on the Northern Continent. This was his next target.

He was a member of Stephanie's team, a Grade A Psychic master who could modify memories. He deviated from the others and acted alone, giving fake memories to the Six Nations' leaders and twisting their knowledge toward Black Star, making them think that they were fighters resisting a dictator.

The political conflicts of a planet surface civilization were just tricks between weaklings, meaningless and childish. He could toy with those people any way he wanted to. If not for the sake of setting up a trap for Black Star, he would not even have been willing to waste his energy on using such delicate memory modifying methods on a group of surface civilization natives.

...

It was winter on the mountainous Northern Continent.

Zeglin quickly left Raylen's border, flying over the icy landscape.

When flying over a mountain, Zeglin's heart suddenly skipped a beat as if it was grabbed by a hand. A sense of danger appeared, and he looked up at the sky.

A mysterious blue light was burning in the sky.

"Wha—"

In the blink of an eye, many blue light beams fell from the sky!

Boom!

The ground cracked open!

The area of hundreds of miles was all within the attack range. Apart from the bright blue light, no other colors could be seen. Half of the mountain was flattening in an instant. Terrifying craters appeared on the planet's surface, like a dozen meteors hitting the planet at the same time!

At the edge of the explosion radius, Zeglin barely kept himself floating. He was covered in burn marks and was horrified. He had never expected to be attacked so suddenly by such a strong attack.

Unable to hold back, blood spilled out of Zeglin's mouth. He felt as if his organs were going to shatter. As he backed away, he looked around anxiously, wanting to find the enemy.

"Who is it? Come out!"

Just as he said that, a blue meteor flew toward him from the edge of the sky rapidly, leaving a long trail, and stopped not far away.

"Black Star!"

Zeglin's eyes opened wide with shock.

He did not expect Black Star to suddenly find him.

Han Xiao opened his helmet, stared at Zeglin, and snorted.

"There's indeed someone controlling the Six Nations, or they wouldn't have acted so strangely. Speak, why did you target Planet Aquamarine?"

Since he was already putting on an act, he might as well do the whole show. Han Xiao acted as if he did not know that he was the target of Stephanie and the others, and he acted as if he was certain that Zeglin was the last mastermind behind all this.

Since there were definitely more enemies other than Zeglin, him striking suddenly would mess up with their plan and get him the high ground. Without the Observer's Mark, he would only be able to wait for the enemies to attack him. It would be too passive that way, and there would very likely be unrelated casualties.

Now, however, he could choose the battlefield and attack the enemies first.

After confirming Zeglin's appearance, Han Xiao had locked onto Zeglin's rough coordinates with the spaceship radar before using more than ten Psionic Sky Cannons to bombard the area. There was no need to be careful when fighting in this desolate region.

The power of one Psionic Sky Cannon was higher than an Eye of God.

He did not know that Stephanie and the gang's choice of the battlefield was Black Star City. The Observer's Mark had helped Black Star City escape its fate of being destroyed, not turning it into the battlefield of more than a dozen Calamity Grades.

Psychics were even more vulnerable than Mechanics, and seeing that Zeglin was heavily injured, Han Xiao knew that his attack was very effective.

Zeglin hastily turned his mind into a server through the psychic mark in his brain and shared his vision with Stephanie and the rest.

"Sh*t, I've been discovered. Quick, come save me!"

Stephanie was surprised. "Black Star is indeed as cautious as I thought. He's very observant too... However, he's only discovered you."

Black Star had discovered Zeglin and attacked him directly. This had messed up Stephanie's plan, but she felt reassured upon seeing Han Xiao's attitude.

She connected Han Xiao's actions and realized that Black Star definitely did something to the Six Nations that led him to discover Zeglin, thinking that he was the last and only enemy. However, Black Star did not know Zeglin's motive and did not know that there were still nine more people waiting to ambush him. He only thought that his enemy's target was Planet Aquamarine. In this case, the situation was still in her control—Black Star did not discover that this was a trap for him.

"We only have one choice now. Change the plan and attack Black Star straight away. He has not discovered us yet. Zeglin, do your best to stall him. We're heading over now."

Having made the decision, Stephanie felt confident.

Black Star thought that Zeglin was the only enemy, so when the nine of them all appeared, Black Star would definitely be surprised!

Stephanie and the rest were rather far from Zeglin. It would take some time for them to arrive even with Calamity Grade speeds.

Half of Zeglin's heart froze.

He was heavily injured, and the opponent was a Mechanic that could use psionic energy, who also happened to have the Indestructible Body title. He knew clearly that he was no match for Han Xiao. Without saying a word, Zeglin turned around and started escaping.

"Want to escape? Do you think that's possible?"

Han Xiao clapped his hands. The Army Boxes arrived instantly and turned into an enormous mechanical army that shrouded Zeglin in an instant.

The Psychic class countered the Mechanic, but the Mechanic class also countered the Psychic class. After all, psychic attacks were useless against machines—only telekinesis would have an effect.

Boom!

The long-range units and the artillery units shot psionic beams one after another, penetrating Zeglin's Psychic barrier again and again. Mechanical soldiers waved their multifunctional weapons with electromagnetic, shock, high temperature, laser, and other attacks, slashing through Zeglin time and time again, leaving him with scars of all sorts.

Zeglin ran with all his might, but he was surrounded. The new generation mechanical army enhanced by the Truth Mechanic bonuses was many levels stronger than before.

Without needing Han Xiao to do anything, Zeglin was already in a dire situation. His health was steadily reducing.

Han Xiao was giving his machines Mechanical Force bonuses at the side while paying attention to the surroundings at all times. He attacked to lure the enemies out, but he still did not know how many hunters there were. Thus, he kept his guard up.

After fighting for a while, Zeglin was covered in wounds and blood.

"Argh!" Zeglin roared with rage. His psychic energy turned into an enormous spiral drill, covering him as he tried to escape the encirclement of the mechanical army.

He was at his limit, and this was his last attack—he was betting his life on escaping.

The psychic drill penetrated one layer of encirclement after another, almost penetrating the army.

However, at this moment, the shield team suddenly gathered before Zeglin. They activated their Psionic Shields at the same time, which then fused with each other and turned into colossal Psionic Barrier.

The invisible psionic drill and the thick Psionic Barrier clashed!

Energy debris shot out from the location of the impact, like the sparks from cutting through metal.

The drill's impact lasted quite a while before weakening. Zeglin's eyes opened wide with regret—he could not penetrate this Psionic Barrier.

Out of exhaustion, he felt sleepy. This was the side effect of overusing psychic energy.

Usually, he would be able to recover after a short while, but he was now under siege!

The moment that Zeglin's body stiffened, countless psionic beams landed on him.

Boom!

Blue explosions appeared continuously!

Blood and flash separated, incinerated the moment they left his body.

Mechanical soldiers slashed Zeglin's body with high temperature weapons, making him spin around in midair.

Slash!

An arm flew out.

Slash!

A leg this time!

Boom!

The next second, the dozens of mechanical soldiers attacked together. Zeglin was sliced into minced meat in an instant. His body exploded like a firework. Blood fell like rain.

Dead on the spot!

The mechanical armies all stopped moving. A cold wind blew past, bringing the only sound to the dead silent battlefield.

Han Xiao was stunned. The battle had ended quicker than he expected. If he remembered correctly, this was the first Calamity Grade to have been killed by his mechanical army.

My god, my virtuous mechanical army has killed someone.

Though, this guy was a little too vulnerable...

Han Xiao scratched the stubble on his chin.

If he did not have so many tanky talents, with his Endurance, he would only have a little more than 70,000 health. Psychics were strong in attack but weak in defense—this was a known fact. If Zeglin did not only think about escaping the encirclement but attacked him with psychic attacks, Han Xiao might have been injured a little.

Sadly, it seemed like Zeglin feared his Indestructible Body title and did not have the guts to attack him.

Killing Zeglin in a duel was a welcomed surprise. Not only did this weaken the enemies' overall strength, but the Promotion mission on his interface was also displayed as 'Completed'.

This meant that, if Han Xiao wanted to, he could go through his Promotion at any time to complete his Race Evolution!

Han Xiao felt relaxed.

Knowing that he could go through Promotion anytime, he was more confident.

The Experience that he had was more than enough for him to level up to 195 right after his Promotion, reaching the maximum level limit of Truth Mechanic.

At his current stage, being able to maintain such fast leveling speed was thanks to his savings in Version 2.0.

At this time, the sound of the sound barrier breaking appeared.

Hu!

A few people flew over from the edge of the sky and stopped in midair. It was Stephanie and the others. They all looked at what was left of Zeglin, and their expressions changed.

In the short time it had taken them to travel there, Black Star had already killed Zeglin‽

Stephanie squinted. She had no emotion toward her teammates, so she was not angry, just staring at Han Xiao.

"He really is very strong. His Excellency Thousand Shadows will definitely like him."

Not planning to explain anything to Han Xiao, Stephanie made a sign, signaling for the others to spread out and surround Han Xiao. They blocked all of Han Xiao's escape routes and looked at Han Xiao.

Stephanie stared at Han Xiao's face, looking forward to seeing his terrified and shocked expression of realizing that he had fallen into a trap.

Seeing this, Han Xiao put on his helmet and covered his face. He had already successfully lured the enemies out, so he was too lazy to continue his Oscar spirit.

Stephanie was disappointed and lost her excitement. Although she knew that Black Star was definitely shocked and was only controlling his expression to not show his enemies, she still wanted to see the panicking expression of her prey. Sadly, it did not go as she hoped it would.

Nine Calamity Grades... Hmm, this is probably all.

Han Xiao was secretly relieved. If he was alone, he would definitely have had a very tough fight. Luckily, he had planned ahead and found helpers.

Phillip had already called Wilton, Nagakin, and the others to reinforce him. He just had to hold on for a while—he was not as vulnerable as Zeglin.

Furthermore, he had discovered something huge that he did not expect.

Under the mechanical suit helmet, Han Xiao stared at the enemies' leader, Stephanie, sizing her up. He then smiled.

He recognized this woman.

Chapter 672: Suddenly Clear

The moment Han Xiao saw Stephanie, he felt that she looked familiar. As he looked at her carefully, his heart skipped a beat.

He did not recognize the other hunters, but he was familiar with this woman!

Many players in his previous life had known Stephanie. She was very active during the Calamity of the Supers version. She was a subordinate of the Beyond Grade A from the Abyss of Stars, [Thousand Shadows]. She fought for Thousand Shadows with countless Supers as pawns, including many players that teamed up to kill her. In the end, she died in a battle while being surrounded by many forces... or she was finally freed.

After that, a related Dungeon Crystal appeared. Stephanie was inside the dungeon as a hidden boss. There was a chance of obtaining an extremely rare reward by defeating her.

In the later stages of Han Xiao's previous life, with an extremely high 87.6% player repeat rate, she entered the list of top hundred hard workers and received the honorable title 'Lady Stephanie'!

At that stage, the player count of Galaxy was dozens of times greater than the player count of Version 2.0. The number of players online at the same time was more than ten million. The fact that more than eighty percent of players had repeated Stephanie's dungeon before represented its popularity!

It was a little embarrassing to mention, but Han Xiao had fought Stephanie with at least three hundred different accounts. He could not have been more familiar with her.

Han Xiao did not expect to recognize one of the enemies, so he was surprised.

Initially, he did not know who the mastermind was. Now that he had seen Stephanie, everything became clear, and he found the truth.

It was Thousand Shadows!

No wonder, no wonder, everything connects now... Han Xiao was excited. If the mastermind was indeed Thousand Shadows, he knew why the hunters were capturing Supers.

It was to provide 'shadows' for Thousand Shadows!

Thousand Shadows' ability was very strange. He could absorb other individuals and turn them into his underlings, who were called 'shadows'. The shadows still retained most of their personality, but they had a sense of belonging and loyalty toward Thousand Shadows that could not be erased. In this condition, their memories were slightly altered.

The shadows slept inside Thousand Shadows, but at the same time, they could act for him.

The abilities of the shadows were preserved, or even enhanced, after fusing with Thousand Shadows. Thousand Shadows had lived for too long. No one knew how many shadows were in his body. He was an extremely mysterious member of The Ancient Ones.

Han Xiao recalled a secret that a player had found in his previous life. In order to live longer, Thousand Shadows sought help from specialized people and gave his Esper ability vitality. He then gave up his body and turned into a strange 'Esper Being'. Usual methods could not kill him. He had lived for close to a thousand years and was a member of The Ancient Ones.

Discovering the truth, Han Xiao was feeling gloomy. Thousand Shadows liked high-quality shadows, so he probably would not give up easily on Han Xiao. Han Xiao absolutely did not want to become a part of Thousand Shadows; he would lose himself and become a puppet!

Stephanie was Thousand Shadows' shadow. Her life story was rather tragic, too. Before she died, her true self returned for a moment and explained her origins.

Back at the start of the exploration era, before the Primordial Ones had been born, when the war between the three Universal Civilizations extended throughout the entire universe...

She was born in an era of war, an Antarrian. Her civilization's mother planet was dragged into the war. She displayed extraordinary talent from a young age, so she was chosen as a warrior, fighting for her home and quickly growing.

In a short period of a little more than ten years, she had already become the protector of her home, at the age normal Galaxy Human Race women were at their peak. At such a young age, she became the top protector of Antarr. She was so strong that even the three civilizations had heard of her.

However, a gigantic war broke out between the Crimson Dynasty and Federation of Light that used an entire Star Cluster as the battlefield. The Antarrians were affected. Their mother planet fell, and their colonial planets turned into ruins under the Crimson Dynasty's iron hoofs. Only a handful of people escaped with spaceships used for migration—Stephanie was one of the survivors.

People in wars were realistic. The survivors had no time to miss their mother planet and left the battlefield quickly, looking for a new home to rise again. However, an unwelcome guest had his eyes on Stephanie... Thousand Shadows.

Thousand Shadows was originally from a long-lived race and had already lived for many years. At that time, he had yet to give up his body and was not Beyond Grade A. He wanted Stephanie's power, so he intercepted the spaceship that the Antarr survivors were in.

In the ending, the Antarr Civilization was another extinguished civilization, and Stephanie became one of Thousand Shadows' shadows.

The history only recorded what happened—the cold words could not record emotions. The motives, feelings, and the reactions of everyone back then became mysteries. In Han Xiao's previous life, after Stephanie became a part of the dungeon, some players looked for her history out of curiosity. From a few descriptions in some history books, they came to know that some historians believed that if Stephanie did not 'mysteriously disappear', she might have become one of the [Primordial Ones].

However, during the exploration era, there had been way too many Calamity Grades that had a lot of potential, and most of them had died in battle. The Primordial Ones were the first group of Beyond Grade As that walked out of the mountains of corpses and seas of blood alive. Thousand Shadows was not one of the Primordial Ones. He was always very mysterious, only appearing as a Beyond Grade A near the end of the exploration era.

In just one look, these thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He took a deep breath. The true identity of the enemy had been discovered—it was definitely very stressful to be Thousand Shadows' enemy, but that was something for later.

The most imminent problem was dealing with nine Calamity Grades.

Especially Stephanie.

With a push, a beam of [Psionic Impact—Whale] headed right toward Stephanie. The enormous mechanical army around Han Xiao started to move toward all the enemies.

Bang bang bang!

Countless Psionic Cannons crisscrossed, and mechanical soldiers approached the enemies with weapons and shields in their hands. Stephanie and the rest moved, too.

The battle erupted; the scene instantly became chaotic!

Han Xiao never overestimated himself. Although his mechanical army was much stronger than before, facing nine experienced Calamity Grades was still beyond his capabilities. Among the nine enemies, there were two Mechanics. One of them was a Cannon Master, shooting out large beams from extremely high caliber cannons, shattering mechanical soldiers one after another.

The other one used the Galactic Stronghold Style. A several-hundred-meter-tall fortress expanded from his hands. It had extremely strong firepower and its own guards.

Clank!

Metal clashed against metal nonstop, electrical sparkles replaced blood, and scrap metal and wires fell like rain.

Among the rest of the enemies, there were two Pugilists, one Mage, and four Espers. Stephanie was one of the Espers!

Stephanie's ability was the most mysterious. Like a diving eagle, she headed right for Han Xiao in the middle of the army. Everywhere she passed, the nearly mechanical soldiers all shattered. The air around her looked like it was bent by high temperature. From very far away, she raised her hand and aimed at Han Xiao.

With just this one move, several notifications popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

You have entered the [Slightly Slowed] state. -12% DEX. Duration: 8 seconds!

You have entered the [Slightly Weakened] state. -6% all attributes. Duration: 8 seconds!

You have entered the [Slightly Confused] state. +10% chance of being interrupted while using abilities. Duration: 8 seconds!

You have entered the [Abnormally Excited] state. Your attack is fluctuating at 80%–110%. Duration: 8 seconds!

You have entered the [Light Illusion] state. -10% accuracy, -10% perception. Duration: 8 seconds!

You have entered the [Slightly Tired] state. +8% expense in energy and stamina. Duration: 10 seconds!

Your Ability [Steel Body] is activated. All True Damage is nullified!

Chapter 673: Are You Surprised? Are You Shocked?

Han Xiao felt his body become heavier and slower. A ton of debuffs were applied to him in the blink of an eye.

It's really still the same. Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he was not surprised at all.

Having completed Stephanie's dungeon a few hundred times, he was extremely familiar with Stephanie. Even though the Stephanie inside the dungeon was a weaker version, her abilities did not change. Han Xiao knew her combat style like the back of his hand. Giving the enemies a bunch of debuffs at the start was exactly the same as what she would do in the dungeon.

Without hesitation, Han Xiao backed away with Void Travel. Stephanie was stronger in close range battles and had bonus damage against metal. He did not want his mechanical suit to be destroyed so quickly.

Luckily, I got rid of that Psychic called Zeglin, or things would be even tougher now.

Not stopping at all, Han Xiao controlled the mechanical army to execute the stalling strategy in Phillip's database, preventing Stephanie and the others' momentum of rushing toward him. Meanwhile, he used the army as a barrier and moved within, approaching the Mage and two Mechanic enemies occasionally, trying to deal some damage.

In front of nine experienced Calamity Grade, the mechanical army was under a great deal of pressure. It became a tough fight very quickly. Machines fell broken one after another and flew back up after Han Xiao used [Waste Modification] on them, returning to the battlefield.

The battlefield was chaotic. The tactical screen in Han Xiao's helmet displayed the various data as Han Xiao calmly analyzed the situation.

Stephanie disrupted the electromagnetic waves over a large area, so Han Xiao could not contact Wilton and the others. Out of caution, the Phillip sub-program that he had left for Wilton came in handy. Although he could not receive the location information of the reinforcements, he was certain that they were heading over. His current mission was not to fight them head-on but stall them and wait for the reinforcements to arrive.

Boom!

The impact from ten Calamity Grades fighting shook the mountains and the ground.

Even the weather changed. It was initially bright and clear, but the sky was filled with dark clouds and lightning bolts.

Han Xiao kept shifting the battlefield away from the populated areas on the Northern Continent and toward unpopulated glaciers. Everywhere they passed, ice that had formed over millions of years cracked open, mountains shook, avalanches occurred, and the landscape was in a mess.

The impacts of the fight between Calamity Grades were bringing disasters to this planet. With the battlefield as the center, earthquakes spread out to the entire Northern Continent. Near sea areas far from the battlefield, the sky darkened, and the sea was filled with violent waves. Tsunamis and tornados collided with cities near the sea.

"It's a tsunami, run!"

"Wh—What's going on‽"

The residents of the cities near the sea on the Northern Continent were horrified by the natural disasters and ran for their lives.

Of course, Han Xiao could not see the reactions of those people. However, he did not need to see to know that the aftershock of their battle was already creating disasters on Planet Aquamarine.

"This is why they purposely chose here to be the battlefield." Han Xiao's expression was hostile. He dodged an invisible tornado-shaped impact wave from Stephanie once again, and the mechanical soldiers behind him were broken into pieces.

They had shifted the battlefields many times, and the battle was reaching the climax.

The blue light in the sky started burning again. It was another Psionic Sky Cannon attack controlled by Phillip!

Boom!

The mechanical army quickly avoided the bombardment area. Stephanie and the others did, too, but the fortress of that enemy Mechanic moved very slowly and could not get out of the attack range. Its shield shattered, and the fortress turned into broken pieces.

This was the enemy's second fortress that had been destroyed.

Using this opportunity, Han Xiao retreated slowly while fighting. They were already at the edge of the north side, and he started to shift toward the sea.

"Problematic Sky Cannons." Stephanie frowned. She looked up, pointed at one of the Pugilists, and said, "You, go up there and destroy Black Star's Sky Cannons."

The Pugilist nodded. Flames shot out from under his feet as he rose up like a rocket, turning into a black dot in an instant and heading toward outer space.

"Don't waste time. Long duration battles are Black Star's strength. Quickly restrain him."

Stephanie's tone was impatient. She led the other teammates and dashed toward Han Xiao once again.

She knew that Black Star was difficult to kill, but her plan was not to kill him but capture him. However, Han Xiao was too swift. She did not have a chance to close the distance on Han Xiao. Only close-range combat would maximize the power of her Esper ability.

After chasing for a while, they clashed once again above the sea. The impact created waves thousands of feet high. Energy waves shot into the sea and formed enormous vortexes.

As the mechanical army's numbers kept decreasing. Han Xiao started to show signs of fatigue. Suddenly, Han Xiao showed a flaw in his defenses. Stephanie's eyes sparkled. She caught the opportunity and turned into a black shadow, appearing behind Han Xiao instantly as if she had teleported, then pressed her palm toward Han Xiao's back.

This was the first time that she had used this ability in this battle. It was so she could surprise Black Star. As long as she managed to hit Black Star, his strength would decrease by at least ten percent temporarily!

However, the next moment, as if Han Xiao had expected this, he avoided her palm with a weird movement. Then, psionic energy appeared between his hands as he patted her chest.

Bang!

The light blue Psionic Impact ring exploded. Stephanie was blown close to one thousand meters away. She rubbed her hurting chest and frowned, surprised by Han Xiao's reaction speed.

This sudden attack had no signs at all, so Black Star only had microseconds to react.

On the other side, Han Xiao was secretly relieved. Stephanie was a boss-type character. Just like him, she had many abilities other than her Esper abilities. If one was unfamiliar with her, it would be very easy to be tricked. However, he knew Stephanie's abilities all too well, so there was no chance that he would be tricked. He did not farm that dungeon hundreds of times for nothing.

He's stronger than I thought. Stephanie squinted. Just as she was about to attack again, she suddenly noticed that there were a few high energy individuals approaching very quickly. Her expression changed as she stopped in place and did not act recklessly.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He looked up and saw six shooting stars landing from the sky, hovering above.

The flames extinguished, revealing Wilton and the others. Looking at the shocked and confused expressions on Stephanie and the others' faces, Wilton snorted. He raised his hand, and the others finally realized that he was holding a person.

Stephanie looked closer, and her face suddenly changed.

The person that Wilton was holding was the Pugilist whom she had sent to destroy the Sky Cannons. He now had no signs of life at all. It was clear that he had been beaten to death.

These six people are enemies... The expressions of Stephanie and the other six Calamity Grades all turned bitter.

Wilton let go of the corpse, letting it fall into the sea and get swept away by the waves, disappearing.

"Black Star, we're late." Wilton nodded.

Han Xiao smirked.

The reinforcements had arrived!

He looked at Stephanie, shrugged, and chuckled.

"Are you surprised? Are you shocked?"

Seeing that Black Star looked like this was completely expected, Stephanie could not remain calm. She was completely dumbfounded.

He sought help long ago?

And he called six Calamity Grades‽

Why would he ask so many Calamity Grades to settle a surface civilization internal matter‽

Unless...

Stephanie's heart suddenly skipped a beat.

Black Star knew that we were planning to ambush him?

How is that possible‽

Chapter 674: Intense Battle and Disasters

Boom!

As the reinforcements had arrived, Stephanie and her colleagues had no time to react as Wilton and the rest instantly joined the battle.

It was a battle of seven against eight. The average level of the enemies was higher than Wilton and the rest, but the numbers now matched.

For a short time, Wilton and the other five were able to deal with one enemy each, making things so much easier for Han Xiao. He could concentrate on dealing with Stephanie and the enemy Mechanic.

Swoosh!

Like bolts of lightning, fifteen Calamity Grade Supers fought above the sea, stirring up the tide.

While Stephanie fought the mechanical army, she suppressed the shock in her heart. As a Calamity Grade who had experienced hundreds of battles, she was able to quickly adjust to sudden situations.

She could not figure out how Black Star had discovered their ambush, but it was the reality, and the only thing she could do was deal with it.

Stephanie's brain worked quickly as she analyzed the situation.

They have six Grade A Supers. Even with me being here, we won't be able to defeat Black Star's helpers within a short time. It will take a lot of time to capture Black Star...

Stephanie frowned.

Meanwhile, two mechanical armies collided midair. The colorful lights from the energy lit up the dark sky.

Using the army as cover, Han Xiao used Void Travel and appeared right in front of the opponent Mechanic. With a short combo of Mountain Ape Throw and Psionic Impact, Han Xiao broke a few of the enemy Mechanic's bones. The enemy Mechanic endured the pain and backed up. Han Xiao activated his Psionic Shield to block an invisible wave coming far away from Stephanie, making the sound of suppressed thunder.

Boom boom boom!

The two sides fought intensely. As Han Xiao fought, he was also observing Stephanie.

His reinforcements had arrived, so the enemies would definitely react to it.

Stephanie only had two choices—retreat and look for an opportunity in the future or continue fighting and defeat Wilton and the others, betting that Han Xiao did not have any more reinforcements.

Just as Han Xiao was speculating, Stephanie put her hands together. Her body suddenly started vibrating at a high frequency unobservable to the naked eye. Chain reactions started to occur in the space around her.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

In the midst of battle, Wilton and the others suddenly felt like their hearts skipped a beat. As all kinds of debuffs were applied to their bodies, they felt their bodies become slower and more difficult to control.

Xiu!

Again, Stephanie used her teleportation ability, turning into a shadow and suddenly appearing behind Wilton.

This did not work on Han Xiao, but Wilton clearly could not react in time before Stephanie's palm pressed on his back.

Hum!

This press felt soft and hardly had any strength to it, but Wilton's entire body trembled. He felt a strange vibration entering his body. All his muscles and bones started to vibrate at the same frequency.

Just as this thought appeared, an intense pain erupted in his body!

Inside Wilton's body, the high-frequency vibration caused his muscle fibers to break, his bones to crack, his organs to tear, and his blood vessels to explode!

After just being softly touched by Stephanie, Wilton was instantly covered in blood.

"Captain!"

The other two Purple Crystal Grade A Supers noticed the incident. Their expressions drastically changed as they hastily left their opponents behind, wanting to rush over to help.

Expressionless, Stephanie's palm on Wilton's back suddenly grabbed tighter. Her fingers sunk into his body then twisted violently.

"Argh!" Wilton's eyes were completely red.

In the almost unbearable pain, he punched backward with all his might. Having already achieved her goal, Stephanie did not fight head-on with a Pugilist and backed away.

Wilton's back armor was shattered, showing his skin. A large area of muscles and bones were bent and shattered, mushed together in a spiral, and bones protruded from under the skin. It looked terrifying.

In just an instant, Stephanie had heavily injured a Calamity Grade Pugilist. The faces of Wilton and the rest all drastically changed—Stephanie's destructive power was beyond their expectations.

Han Xiao's eyes turned firm as he realized what Stephanie's plan was. This woman was not going to retreat. She had chosen the second plan—continue fighting.

With what he knew about Stephanie, this was not surprising.

Stephanie had been active during the times of war in the exploration era, so she was able to carefully plan before acting and dared fight enemies head-on. She was not one to easily give up on a mission.

This means that this will be a tough fight. Unless we crush them, they will not retreat no matter what.

Han Xiao clenched his teeth. Such enemies were clearly more difficult to deal with.

Stephanie was very strong. The name of her Esper ability was Resonance Coordination. It sounded ordinary, but it was an extremely powerful Esper ability. There were tons of ways to use it, and its destructive power was terrifying.

As the frequency of the resonance could penetrate many defensive measures and cause structural damage, Stephanie's every attack had high True Damage and armor-penetrating damage. Her ability to penetrate defenses was exceptionally strong, and she could largely reduce the opponent's defense.

Han Xiao was not afraid of True Damage; the Germinal Organization leader was still blessing him from heaven.

However, his reinforcements did not have the [Steel Body] talent. Stephanie's ability was more than enough to make them fearful.

Wilton and the others were elites at most. The quality and quantity of their talents and abilities were inferior compared to the hidden boss-level Stephanie.

Stephanie's Resonance Coordination not only had terrifying single target lethality, it was also just as powerful when used as an AOE. Through the vibration frequency, she could give a ton of debuffs to the enemies within an area. When facing weaker Supers, she could even create ultrasound and infrasound to shatter their organs.

This meant that be it against one or multiple opponents, weaker or the same grade, they were all Stephanie's strength.

She was even more difficult to deal with than Ember!

Han Xiao had once fought alongside Jayne, whose nickname was Seaquake. Just like Jayne, Stephanie's Esper ability was also related to vibration. However, Stephanie's Esper ability strength, range, and applicability were all far superior to Jayne's. This was a high-grade vibration-type Esper ability!

She's a murder machine. I can't let her get to the others. I'm the only one that can face her...

That thought flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He turned the mechanical army's cannons around and aimed at Stephanie, firing countless rounds and forming a dense net of attacks. At the same time, Han Xiao headed toward Stephanie and fought her at close range.

Stephanie's expression did not look delightful. She wanted to get rid of Black Star's helpers first, but Han Xiao had come to her and held her back.

Under the onslaught of attacks, Stephanie could not afford to get distracted.

The punches of both sides landed continuously on each other, making loud bangs. She was completely stalled by Han Xiao and could not get away.

Seeing this, Wilton breathed a sigh of relief. He did not dare fight Stephanie; Black Star actively dealing with the most dangerous enemy made him feel relieved. He glanced at Han Xiao, clenched his teeth, and found his own opponent to fight.

Within the mechanical army, both sides clashed with each other time after time. The aftershock formed countless storms, spreading and expanding in all directions.

Boom!

The beams from the Sky Cannons landed on the sea nonstop, creating tsunamis hundreds of meters high.

Thunderstorms finally started to pour from the dark sky.

As their title suggested, the battle between more than ten Calamity Grades was indeed a calamity to the planet.

After fighting for a few hours, there were now only twelve of them left. The many attacks from the Psionic Sky Cannons had finally killed the opponent Mechanic.

A Godoran Calamity Grade had been killed by the enemy, while that enemy was also heavily injured by a round of focus fire from Han Xiao's mechanical army then finished by Wilton.

Three Calamity Grades had died. The battle was devastating. It was now a battle of six against six!

"Huu... huu..."

The Mountain Ape mechanical suit was heavily damaged. Han Xiao had already repaired it three times using [Waste Modification]. He gasped heavily for air, dragged his exhausted body, and collided with Stephanie time after time.

Stephanie was not in a good state either. She was bleeding from her forehead, and her body was covered in wounds. Her clothes were almost all torn, but her eyes were still vicious.

The mechanical army around became much sparser. The two of them did not hold back and fought fiercely like beasts.

Neither of them had much stamina left, and they were quickly recovering. They were in a stalemate.

She has boss-type Molding Talents. She has a lot of energy, health, and very fast recovery speed. It will take days to determine the winner if I keep fighting this way

Han Xiao clenched his teeth. He had only been able to gain the upper hand with his health-energy cycle, mechanical army, and immunity to True Damage. Stephanie was Thousand Shadows' shadow; her ability was enhanced, and her level was most likely around 240. She was undoubtedly a top-notch Grade A+.

The longer the battle lasted, the greater his chance of winning. Han Xiao was still stronger in terms of long duration battles. However, he could not delay the battle any longer.

Just one Calamity Grade would be able to destroy a planet's surface. The disasters brought by a battle between so many Calamity Grades were already starting to affect the entire Planet Aquamarine.

The natural disasters caused by the aftershocks of battle were irreversible!

Even if they stopped immediately, the disasters they caused before would still continue to spread by themselves.

If they fought for a few more days, living beings on Planet Aquamarine would probably all be dead.

The stalemate has to be broken. The two sides are now on par. As long as I become a little stronger, I will be able to break the fragile balance!

Having made up his mind, Han Xiao dived right into the violent sea without saying a word.

He could go through his Promotion at any time, only that it would take some time. Under Phillip's control, a part of the mechanical army in the sky stayed to restrain the enemies, while the rest followed Han Xiao into the sea to protect him when needed.

Stephanie frowned and glanced through Wilton and the rest. After hesitating for a moment, she had made up her mind—she did not use this opportunity to eliminate the other enemies but followed Han Xiao and dived into the sea.

Her rich experiences told her that no matter what goal Black Star had, it was best to stop him.

As the strongest Supers of both sides went into the sea, everyone's expression changed, not knowing why Black Star had suddenly split up the battlefield.

Could it be that he did not want to be disturbed by the others and wanted to fight Stephanie in the sea‽

"Captain, should we go down to back him up?"

Wilton clenched his teeth and said, "No need. Just do what we're supposed to—do not let our opponents follow them down. Let Black Star deal with that woman."

He felt that Black Star did not need reinforcements, and subconsciously, he did not want to face Stephanie.

That woman was too dangerous. He would not have to endure the pressure if he left her to Black Star.

Although he had been ordered to back Han Xiao up, Wilton was not willing to sacrifice his life for it.

At the same time in Black Star City, reports of natural disasters kept being sent to Bennett's table. The satellites had discovered that the source of these disasters was the battlefield of Han Xiao and the others.

Many officials and professionals were crowded in the office, anxiously reporting the situation to Bennett.

"A few hours ago, earthquakes occurred in many areas on the Northern Continent. Many fissures and rifts appeared. Earthquakes caused tsunamis. Thirteen coastline cities have already been destroyed, causing incalculable casualties!"

"According to the satellite report, His Excellency Black Star is now fighting with enemies on the sea. The storms and tsunamis caused are approaching the other continents while growing in power. In about three hours' time, they will reach land. The various nations have already started the emergency evacuation."

"An hour ago, eleven new earthquake sources appeared in various locations around the world. The degree and range of earthquakes are still expanding. According to our calculations, within ten days, 24.7% of all land areas will be affected by earthquakes."

"Also..."

Bennett listened to one report after another while anxiously walking back and forth. This was completely different from the Mutation Disaster; these natural disasters were things that could not be resolved.

"Send out rescue teams and support the affected areas as much as possible. For the time being, forget about the Six Nations' doings." Bennett issued his orders before pausing momentarily. "When will the disasters reach Black Star City?"

Black Star City was inland. The disasters would not reach there so soon.

An official gulped to wet his throat, shivered, and said, "According to the calculations of the research and development department, if His Excellency Black Star continues to battle, the seriousness of the disasters will multiply rapidly. In about 4 hours 35 minutes, the chain disasters they cause will exceed the critical point..."

"What will happen when it exceeds the critical point?" Bennett's heart skipped a beat.

"Unless we leave this planet, we can only wait for our deaths."

Bennett's fists tightened.

Chapter 675: Promotion!

Boom!

The fallout of a battle between more than ten Calamity Grades created enormous whirlpools all over the sea in the area.

The violent winds sucked the seawater up, forming water tornados that extended all the way into the sky, connecting the sea and the clouds.

It was a doomsday scene above the sea.

The moment that Han Xiao dived into the sea, those noises suddenly became faint. The seawater weakened the sound coming from above, but the sound of the powerful tides and streams under the sea was amplified. It was as if he was in the middle of hundreds of enormous drums being played together, surrounded by stereo sound effects.

The radar showed that Stephanie was following behind, and Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

I can't let her get close during the Promotion.

Han Xiao ordered the mechanical army around him to turn back and hold back Stephanie while he quickly dived deeper.

The ocean before his eyes was dark, turning from deep blue to black in the distance. The visibility was low, there was no source of light anywhere and no end in sight. It was even darker than the universe.

Fortunately, I don't have Thalassophobia[1].

The ocean was the hotbed of life. Many ancient creatures lived in the sea of Planet Aquamarine. However, at this point, all the marine lives of the area had escaped. The ocean was completely devoid of any sign of life.

Stephanie was stalled by the mechanical army. Han Xiao quickly dived deeper and found a trench that had formed a few hours ago.

Here will do.

Han Xiao immediately opened the interface, selected the Completed Promotion mission, and activated it.

A shiver in his marrow and soul quickly passed through his entire body. He was familiar with this Promotion feeling.

This time, a chain of notifications popped up on the interface.

[The Ultimate Trial] Current Progress: 50/50

Level 180 Promotion Mission completed! END bonus increased! 1 END = 120 HP = 130 Stamina

You have taken another step on the path of evolution. You have ascended in the hierarchy of life.

Detected Race: [Chaos Observer (Human Form)]...

Randomly drawing 8 compatible evolution paths...

Drawing complete!

Please choose one of the following 8 options for your Race Evolution.

Warning! The evolution process is irreversible. Please choose carefully! [Appendix—Evolution Path Feature Descriptions]

[X-type Galaxy Human Race]—67% Compatibility

[Void Stroller (Human Form)]—78% Compatibility

[Dark Shadow (Human Form]—72% Compatibility

[Void Disciple (Human Form)]—71% Compatibility

[Void Distorter (Human Form)]—69% Compatibility

[Void Whisperer (Spirit Form)]—84% Compatibility

[Void Slime]—55% Compatibility

[Octa-claw Race]—31% Compatibility

First, Han Xiao eliminated the non-Void race choices. The octopus-looking Octa-claw Race was not even within his consideration, and Void Slime was way too weird.

Void Whisperer was a spirit form choice, suitable for Mages and Psychics. Han Xiao had such a strong body, so he was not willing to give it up.

The only possible choices were the four human form evolution paths.

Han Xiao quickly scanned through and immediately made a decision.

Void Lord's core enhanced his Void Genes. As Han Xiao had jumped into the Void Race evolution system from the human race, it was kind of like a midlife career change for him. Hence, he naturally could not compete with those that started as Void Beings. However, the genetic substances that had Void Genes in them such as the Void Lord core had enhanced his evolution progress in the Void Race system, allowing him to catch up.

With the benefit from the Void Lord core, an option that was supposed to appear in the next Race Evolution had appeared this time. This was a higher level being on the Void Race evolution system. According to his data, this being was one entire level higher than the other options on the evolution chain!

Be it the current attribute bonuses or the evolution potential in the future, this species was the best choice!

Han Xiao quickly selected his choice.

Selection complete. Undergoing Race Evolution... Evolution complete.

Your race has been changed to: [Void Distorter (Human Form)].

Molecular structure improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed, and adaptability enhanced...

Your potential aptitude has been improved!

You have received bonus attributes: +44 STR, +83 DEX, +65 END, +120 INT, +92 MYS, +34 CHA, +1460 Energy. Energy Level bonus attributes have changed!

Han Xiao's eyes widened rapidly, and a dim light appeared in his pupils.

All the cells and genes over his body started to change, and pain erupted in both his body and his mind. His vision kept going back and forth between Void Vision and reality. His brain was trembling.

His body greedily absorbed the energy of the Void Dimension. His entire body was emitting a mysterious gray and dark blue light.

If the level of Void Prowler and Chaos Observer were to be evaluated on the military scale, these two would be privates, and Void Distorter would be at the sergeant level!

This Race Evolution hugely enhanced his connection with the Void Dimension. His body seemed to have become a container, and Void Energy poured right into him, absorbed by every cell in his body.

His energy changed under the Void Energy erosion.

You have received Void Energy bonuses!

+30% Energy recovery speed

+1000 Energy

You have received a new Energy Attribute: [Void]!

Your energy will now have Void characteristics.

A new Energy Attribute!

Han Xiao was overjoyed. Enduring the immense pain, he quickly looked at the interface. The interface showed that he now had two Energy Attributes. One was the Mechanic class' magnetic attribute Mechanical Force, and the other was the new void attribute.

Han Xiao's joy was almost overflowing.

The change in Energy Attribute was not as obvious as character attributes, but it was very important. It could even change one's combat style.

Although the interface introduction was ambiguous, Han Xiao had already felt the change in the energy in his body during the Race Evolution. Furthermore, he remembered stuff from his previous life, so he knew very well what the [Void] attribute's effect was.

Energy Erosion!

The ability to transmit energy using the Void Dimension as the medium!

Both these characteristics were very powerful in battle, and they were suitable for any class!

The evolution was still going on. The Void Energy in his body started to saturate. The evolution process created an enormous vortex under the sea.

This attracted Stephanie's attention.

I can't let him do as he wishes!

Stephanie did not know what Han Xiao was doing, but that did not stop her from wanting to stop Han Xiao. She vibrated the seawater, shattering mechanical soldiers one after another, and cleared a path.

She directly headed to the middle of the undersea vortex and launched a powerful wave right at it.

Boom!

The vortex was shattered into streams in the blink of an eye. At the last moment, Han Xiao dodged being hit directly and was just pushed away by the fallout.

Stephanie was a powerful enemy. Han Xiao did not have time to slowly feel the changes in his body. He glanced at the various new talents and abilities on the interface before throwing tons of Experience into the interface, leveling up rapidly!

He leveled up fifteen times directly!

The level up notification popped up.

[Truth Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.25 (max).

+450 Energy, +2 STR, +4 DEX, +4 END, +10 INT.

You have received 7 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

As his class reached its maximum level, Han Xiao stopped leveling up.

As usual, he put all his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence.

His total level now was 195!

Before Han Xiao could look at the changes in his attributes, the tremendous increase in his strength made him feel like the rich and powerful energy was about to overflow from all the cells in his body and that he had to use it urgently.

Without hesitating, Han Xiao took back his Mountain Ape mechanical suit and dashed toward Stephanie.

This time, Stephanie finally saw what Han Xiao looked like now. Her expression changed.

Han Xiao's skin had become silver-gray with a crystal-like texture, sparkling with the light of energy. He had symmetrical deep blue patterns on his body. His entire body was covered with silver flames fueled by Void Energy. His silver hair was swaying in the water like a dancing flame.

His eyes looked like obsidians, and his pupils had become rice-sized white dots.

This appearance was similar to a Void Prowler, but the energy emitted was much stronger.

New Racial Talent—[Void Molt]!

What is th—

Stephanie was dumbfounded.

At this moment, Han Xiao opened his arms. Half of his palm reached into the Void Dimension. He bent his fingers like a claw and pulled down like tearing open a cloth.

"Try this!"

The next moment, the world before Stephanie's eyes was suddenly deformed.

She felt as if all her muscles, bones, nerves, and blood vessels were squeezed together then separated again. She felt as if she had become a piece of cloth and was twisted and bent by someone who was trying to squeeze the water out of her body.

In just a short moment, it felt like countless years to her. This indescribably strange feeling had exceeded most people's knowledge. It was like Stephanie had a dream. She forgot what the dream was about after she woke, but the sense of inferiority still lingered as if she had dreamed of something extremely horrifying.

While she was still confused, continuous pain suddenly exploded in every corner of her body!

Stephanie regained focus. Her expression dramatically changed, and she was about to retreat. To her shock, the seawater around her was all spinning at a high speed, generating a terrifying force that prevented her from escaping.

Sh*t! Stephanie was stunned.

The movements there transmitted to the sea surface as well. All the small vortexes in this area were shattered and fused into a gigantic vortex that seemingly could consume the sky!

Boom!

The ten Calamity Grades all stopped fighting and looked at the horrifying endless vortex under them

In their eyes, the ocean was no longer the ocean. It had become a galaxy, and this vortex was like a black hole.

Deep, mysterious, and terrifying!

Like the entrance of an endless abyss!

The people who had made this could only be Han Xiao and Stephanie.

"What have they done?" Wilton's eyes widened.

At the same time under the sea, it was as if Stephanie had been thrown into a washing machine, unable to control herself among the whirlpools, enduring the terrible forces tearing and damaging her.

At the center of the most peaceful whirlpool, Han Xiao grabbed tightly onto the Void Dimension. A huge force of resistance came from his hand. He could only maintain the current situation no matter how hard he tried. His energy was reducing at an astounding speed, releasing from his hands.

"This is marvelous!"

Even Han Xiao was startled by the effect of this attack.

This ability was indeed one of the new abilities from Void Distorter.

[Void Distortion]!

[1] Thalassophobia is phobia of the deep sea. Back

Chapter 676: Broken Balance

After completing his Race Evolution, Han Xiao's Racial Talents changed as well.

[Advanced Void Travel] was a shared talent for Void species, so it did not change. [Void Vision—Observer], [Chaos Entity - Release], and [Observer's Mark] were gone, however, replaced by Void Distorter's abilities.

The three new talents were [Void Molt], [Void Distortion], and [Void Ripple]

[Void Molt] was an enhancement ability. As his genes were enhanced by Void Energy, and he could enter a special state by burning energy with the Void attribute. In that state, all his attributes would increase, and the Void attribute of his energy would be enhanced as well.

Han Xiao's current appearance was what he would look like when activating this ability.

Void Distorter's signature talent was, of course, [Void Distortion], the ability to affect reality by pulling the Void Dimension. It was an ability with a large area of effect and a very high continuous consumption of mana. It would also send out psychic impacts to the enemies within the range.

With Han Xiao's current strength, the range and power of [Void Distortion] were both remarkable, so this ability could be used regularly against enemies of the same grade.

The enormous whirlpool at the moment had been caused by Void Distortion. It had caught Stephanie by surprise, and she was being spun around nonstop.

[Void Ripple] was a single target damage ability. Its effect was concentrating Void Energy to unleash explosive damage on the enemy. Even Han Xiao was startled when he saw the theoretical damage numbers. Most of the damage dealt by this ability was True Damage.

Chaos Observer's abilities are mainly supportive, while Void Distorter's abilities are pure combat and destruction oriented.

Most of Void Distorter's abilities were related to space. This Race Evolution gave him a total of four abilities. Furthermore, this evolution skipped an entire tier on the evolution chain, so his potential had grown a huge amount.

While still grabbing onto the Void Dimension and maintaining the gigantic whirlpool caused by Void Distortion, Han Xiao used the time to look at his attributes after the Promotion.

After calculating, the Race Evolution and fifteen-level increase had brought him a total of 132 Strength, 224 Dexterity, 220 Endurance, 507 Intelligence, 169 Mystery, 34 Charm, 5,850 Energy, and 11,300 Stamina.

It was amazing!

Han Xiao was very satisfied. He looked at his attributes on the interface.

Level: 195

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Void Distorter (Human Form)

Attributes: 468 STR, 898 DEX, 940 END, 2633 INT, 432 MYS, 139 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Points: 15

Health: 196,560

Stamina: 154,720

Energy: 25,530 [Lv.12]

[Lv.12 Energy bonus attributes: +169 STR, +239 DEX, +269 END, +336 INT, +206 MYS, +32,520 Maximum Stamina, +352% Machinery Affinity (Super Electromagnetic Sense)]

Energy Rank: 20,170

Grade: A+

[Grade A Ranked Bonus: +10 END, +8 All Resistances. +10% Highest Attribute, +5% Other Attributes, +30 Free Attribute Points, +5 Potential Points]

[You're a Grade A+ Mechanic. Sadly, your brain is filled with muscles.]

Bullsh*t! My brain is filled with intelligence!

Han Xiao curled his lips and decided not to argue with the remarks.

Level 195, I'm finally Grade A+.

Han Xiao looked at the amount of Experience he had left. At this stage, the Experience cost of every level was extremely high, so leveling up fifteen times consecutively had cost him a lot of Experience.

He estimated that the remaining Experience should be able to level up ten or so times.

Upon arriving at Grade A+, he was now much stronger. Before his Promotion, he could defeat about ninety percent of all Calamity Grades, but now, Han Xiao felt that not many people in the same grade as him would be able to pose a threat.

He was now a top Calamity Grade!

However, knowing his limits, Han Xiao did not intend to mess with any Beyond Grade As.

At level 195, he was already a top Calamity Grade. However, he would only be able to reach Beyond Grade A at around level 240. Just this level difference was already enough to warn Han Xiao against doing anything.

After all, that was tens of levels of difference at the late stage. The strength difference between levels was much more significant than the earlier stages.

With my current strength, the most I can do is not be afraid of anyone in the same grade. Han Xiao was not going to get arrogant.

Having already spent more than half of his energy, Han Xiao stopped the Void Distortion. The enormous whirlpool was still there, but it gradually spun slowly. Without Han Xiao's Void Distortion, Stephanie regained control of her body, immediately escaping the whirlpool and instantly shooting up to the ocean's surface.

Han Xiao followed her and slowly flew up to the sky.

Wilton and the others saw that the two of them had finally come out of the ocean. They all looked over and were all shocked. Being covered in burning silver flames, Han Xiao looked just like a Pugilist. While Stephanie was wet, wounded everywhere, and had a fearful expression on her face.

The others realized what had happened. Clearly, the two of them had gotten into a huge fight under the sea, and Black Star had used some kind of ability and created this enormous whirlpool, which had wounded Stephanie badly.

"Advance!" Han Xiao led the mechanical army and charged forward, not giving Stephanie any time to rest.

His strength rocketed. Plus, he had recovered to his peak with the Promotion. This had instantly shattered the fragile balance between the two sides!

With his increased Intelligence, his mechanical army had become stronger.

Boom!

The battle started again. The moment Han Xiao entered the battle, the stalemate situation was broken.

After his Promotion, he completely suppressed Stephanie while still being able to assist his teammates. He controlled the tempo of the battle alone.

Stephanie felt a huge increase in pressure and was completely stuck on the passive side of the battle. She could not understand how Black Star had been on par with her moments ago, yet now he had suddenly become so much stronger. Could this be a trump card of his‽

Could it be that he could grow quickly during battle?

She remembered that there were this kind of battle race in the universe. Not killing them would make them stronger.

Could Black Star be one of them?

If he was, it would make sense. No wonder Black Star had risen so quickly in such a short time. He might really be one of those talented battle races!

Many guesses flashed through Stephanie's mind. She looked around at her wounded teammates and was shaken.

Including her, everyone was already at their limit. However, Black Star was still very much at his peak, and his helpers were very tough as well. After fighting for so long, Stephanie could not see any hope of capturing Black Star.

"Retreat!"

Realizing that the situation was getting worse, Stephanie decided to retreat and leave the battlefield.

After fighting for so many hours, Stephanie and the others were all exhausted, but if they continued to fight head-on, they would still be able to last much longer. However, once they decided to retreat, their spirit broke, and they lost all their advantages. They were all held back by Han Xiao, who was at his peak after the Promotion.

Stephanie and the others fought while retreating, causing them to enter a vicious cycle—the more they wanted to retreat, the worse the situation became.

However, if they fought head on, it would just be delaying their inevitable death. Stephanie had no choice but to retreat. Only now did she realize that she was in a tough spot. Within the few hours that they were in a stalemate, they spent way too much energy and now could not escape.

If the enemies had retreated from the beginning, Han Xiao and the others would really not have been able to stop them. However, they only thought about retreating now. It was too late!

He did not want those dangerous people to escape. Who knew what trouble they would cause next time?

When Stephanie realized the situation, they had nowhere to run.

The battlefield gradually shifted to land. Stephanie and the others were finally at their limits.

Han Xiao started his slaughter!

Bang!

A punch landed on the heavily injured enemy Mage, and Void Ripple flew into the target's body. This person's entire body trembled, and his body started to scrunch up like a cloth. However, instead of water being squeezed out, it was blood. His health became zero, and he fell from the sky.

Xiu!

A Psionic Impact entered right into the body of an enemy Esper. Dark blue light exploded from within. With a loud band, this person exploded from within!

Boom!

A heavy knee kick landed on the lower body of a Pugilist. A large amount of nanotechnology particles suddenly appeared on Han Xiao's knee, which turned into a sharp blade, stabbing right into the body of this Pugilist. The moment it stabbed in, the nanotechnology blade shapeshifted. The next moment, countless alloy spikes extended from within the muscles, as if spikes had suddenly grown out from this person's body.

As Han Xiao backed away, the nanotechnology particles returned as well. The spikes on this person's body all 'retracted'. Blood shot out from the countless holes on his body as he fell from the sky.

Han Xiao killed one Calamity Grade after another, leaving only Stephanie still resisting. She was indeed very strong. Just Stephanie alone was able to cause quite a lot of trouble.

However, she was too outnumbered.

Stephanie heavily injured three of Han Xiao's helpers. This was the last trouble she caused. Then, she was defeated by Han Xiao as well.

Ignoring their injuries, Han Xiao's helpers immobilized her and prevented her from escaping.

Han Xiao pressed Stephanie on the ground, and Psionic Impact shot right in her face time after time without stopping, creating a several-hundred-meter-deep crater on the ground. Stephanie was restrained by Wilton and the rest, so she could not resist.

In the end, Stephanie was so heavily injured that she was unable to move. She only had the energy to breath.

Han Xiao did not kill her. He felt that it would be useful to not kill all of them. Plus, Stephanie was a boss-level character, so she would definitely produce great potions.

All Stephanie could feel was how heavy her eyelids were. Before falling unconscious, she squeezed out his last bit of energy to glare at Han Xiao.

When setting the ambush, she had never even considered the possibility that she would be defeated there.

"Black Star..."

Stephanie glared at Han Xiao, engraving his appearance deep into her heart before falling unconscious.

The place became quiet.

"We finally won." Han Xiao took a deep breath. Only then did he feel the tiredness in his body. All he wanted to do was have a good sleep.

Honestly, Stephanie's trap had indeed been very threatening. If he did not call for help beforehand, he might really have fallen into the trap. If he had undergone his Promotion earlier, without the Observer's Marks aiding him in picking the battlefield, Black Star City would have been destroyed.

However, the battle had now ended, and the result was determined.

Stephanie's team had been completely eliminated!

"Thanks for your help." Han Xiao turned around and nodded at Wilton and the others.

"You're welcome." Wilton swallowed his saliva and spoke respectfully. He did have some thoughts earlier but now all he had for Han Xiao was respect and fear.

This fight might not have been as astonishing as his fight with the eight Vanguard Officials, but how many Calamity Grades did Black Star kill today‽

Last time, Black Star had proved his defense; today, Wilton had witnessed Han Xiao's attack for the first time.

Just thinking about it sent shivers down Wilton's spine.

Luckily, Black Star is our ally... Wilton was internally relieved.

Meanwhile, Nagakin was sorrowful. A comrade of his had been killed. Han Xiao had no way to comfort him; all he could do was give him a pat on the back.

Godora had sent those people to help him. Losing a Calamity Grade was no small loss to Godora. Han Xiao felt rather sorry and remembered this favor, considering how he could make it up to Godora.

He was not someone that took the help from others for granted.

To maintain a relationship, it took effort from both sides.

At this time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something, and his expression changed.

"Wait, we can't rest yet. Phillip, gather the disaster reports and tell me the locations."

Forcing energy out of himself, Han Xiao turned into a stream of light and quickly left.

He could not rest yet. He had to deal with the disasters brought by the battle. If they were not stopped in time, Planet Aquamarine would suffer a lot of damage.

Wilton and the others were willing to help. They split up and headed to different disaster locations.

Chapter 677: Class Advancement Requirement

In the Black Star City government building, Bennett was walking back and forth anxiously. Most of his people had been sent out to deal with the disasters, so only a few officials were in the room, looking at Bennett. Every one of them looked nervous and hesitant.

Other than the sound of footsteps and heavy breathing, there were no other sounds in the room.

Bennett clenched his fists. He felt a deep sense of powerlessness. Ever since Planet Aquamarine started to connect with the universe, he had been feeling this way. In battles of this level, he realized that all he could do was wait for the results.

Although Bennett trusted Han Xiao, he still planned for the worst. He had already ordered some people to start preparing to evacuate. He could not bet all his people on it.

This time, the official responsible for observing the battle hastily ran in and said with an overjoyed tone, "Your Excellency, the battle ended! Black Star won!"

Bennett's tightened body finally relaxed, and his fists curled open.

The people in the room were surprised and could not help but cheer softly.

"I got it... Step up the disaster relief measures and reduce the damage caused as much as possible.

Bennett suppressed his excitement and issued several orders. This world shaking battle had brought disaster to the planet. They had to minimize the damage caused.

"By the way, have you been able to contact Black Star yet?"

"His Excellency Black Star sent a message earlier, saying he is taking his people to deal with the disasters and needs our cooperation."

"That's great. Cooperate with him fully and follow any order he gives."

Bennett was thrilled.

...

The fallout of the battle caused earthquakes, tsunamis, tornados, and other disasters to occur in many areas of the planet. Fortunately, Han Xiao ended the battle quickly, so the disasters did not exceed the critical level.

The tornados were easiest to deal with. Calamity Grades could extinguish the storm eye and make them disappear. Contrary to that, the earthquakes were irreversible, so they could only save the affected cities to reduce the damage.

In twenty-four hours, Han Xiao, Wilton, and the rest dealt with around a hundred disasters, big and small. In the next few months, there would still be more chain disasters, but they would all be detectable.

There were still some matters on Planet Aquamarine that needed Han Xiao to sort out, such as what to do with the Six Nations.

However, Han Xiao was exhausted and planned to rest for one day first, at the same time familiarizing himself with the changes brought by the Promotion.

Han Xiao brought the captive back to Bennett. Bennett was busy doing disaster relief, but he still squeezed out the time to thank Han Xiao.

Although the enemies came because of Han Xiao and Planet Aquamarine was sort of dragged into it, Bennett was not an idiot. He knew that Planet Aquamarine was only thriving because of Black Star, so it was only natural that they were on the same boat. Of course, he would not blame this protector. If there was anyone that he was angry at, it would be the enemies who used such a despicable strategy.

Wilton and the others left and rushed back to report what they had seen on this mission.

Han Xiao thanked them again for their help and contacted Godora's Serbia the Fifth to discuss the compensation for the Calamity Grade that they had lost. Technically, he did not have to compensate them, but Han Xiao would not be that stupid.

Godora only had around twenty Calamity Grades, and every one they lost was a very big deal. Serbia the Fifth felt heartache too. When he heard that Han Xiao was going to compensate for it, he did feel a little better.

The Purple Crystal Civilization knew about this from Wilton. They contacted the Godoran Civilization and expressed their intent of paying some of the compensation for Han Xiao. Han Xiao's record of killing many Calamity Grades increased his position once again. Purple Crystal was now even more interested in him. This act was to clearly express their intent of trying to build a relationship with Han Xiao.

...

When Han Xiao returned to his room, Stephanie was still unconscious. Han Xiao extracted potions from her till she was extremely weak.

Stephanie was strong, so Han Xiao would only not be worried about imprisoning her when she did not have the strength to resist.

Round three of [Prey] was completed. Han Xiao did not claim the reward immediately. One of the rewards was to draw a random ability from the ten enemies, including Stephanie.

As Feidin was not there, the Great Mechanic Han was unconfident about these luck related things. He planned to return to the headquarters and touch Feidin before claiming it.

During the battle, he rocketed to level 195, reaching the limit of [Truth Mechanic] and triggering the requirement for the next Class Advancement.

This time, it was a common Mechanic Class Advancement mission—to build one machine that matched the requirement. Han Xiao had triggered this kind of mission before, but this Class Advancement mission matched up to his level, so it was extremely difficult.

The grade of most equipment and items could be classified as one of the following: Poor Gray, Fair White, Good Green, Great Blue, Exceptional Purple, Rare Pink, and Epic Orange. Orange equipment was the top grade.

However, other than these usual grades, there were two special grades—silver and gold.

Gold was the most special grade. It was extremely rare, and it represented that the item was at the 'Universal Treasure' level. There were only a few in the entire universe.

Silver represented the 'Legacy' attribute. If an item had a famous history or signified some kind of honor to be passed on, it would become a silver grade item and receive bonuses.

Legacy could stack with the usual grades. For example, an item could both be at orange grade and silver grade.

This Class Advancement mission was to build legacy-level orange equipment or 'Legendary' equipment!

What determined if a machinery had the legacy attribute depended on the blueprint. This meant that he had to find a special character to learn a silver legacy blueprint from, build it, and reach the orange grade. At the same time, the Class Advancement also had a requirement for the level of the equipment—it had to have a minimum level of level 180.

Therefore, I have to find a legacy level 180 mechanical equipment blueprint, then build it to reach the orange grade...

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Even the requirement for the Mountain Ape mechanical suit did not reach level 180.

Damn it, you're making this difficult for me!

Han Xiao could remember quite a few methods to obtain a silver legacy blueprint, but only a very few legacy equipment reached level 180. Those were also extremely complex and difficult to obtain.

Furthermore, the higher the blueprint's level, the more difficult it was to build a high-grade product out of it. Han Xiao performed some mental calculations, and with his current Intelligence and Machinery Affinity, the absolute highest he could reach was just a level 180 pink equipment.

Han Xiao shook his head.

Although this mission was difficult, it was not completely impossible. Furthermore, there was no risk in it since he just had to build one piece of equipment. Thus, there was no need to depend on luck and find a Mission Completion Card for it.

The legacy blueprint isn't a problem, but my attributes aren't enough to build a level 180 orange equipment. Hmm... do I have to learn new subclasses to increase my attributes?

Without much consideration, Han Xiao denied this solution.

In the later stages, leveling up would become harder and harder. The benefits of the main class were much higher than any subclass. Furthermore, there was still a Promotion mission waiting for him at level 200. It was not worth obtaining a subclass.

He did not want to waste his Experience on subclasses; it was best to spend it on his main class. After all, there was still a very long time until the players logged in again, so he had to reduce his expenditure.

Besides, there were not many subclasses that he needed at the moment, and Han Xiao had a better choice.

If I'm not going to increase my attributes, I will need to find some Mechanic talents...

Han Xiao pondered. Every time he thought about Reynold's talent, he would be tempted.

If he could obtain [Perfect Mechanical Sense], he would be able to complete the requirement right away. Unfortunately, he had yet to trigger a mission from Reynold.

I need to get some Mechanic talents. I'm still a Mechanic after all.

Glancing at the unconscious Stephanie, Han Xiao felt pressured.

The surprising outcome of this incident was that he now knew that the master behind those hunters was Thousand Shadows. The threat of a Beyond Grade A made Han Xiao feel like there was a stone on his heart. Compared to the Tyrant, Thousand Shadows was more fearsome.

Eliminating Stephanie's team did not mean it was the end—he had barely earned the time to rest. Who knew who Thousand Shadows would send next time? The next round of the mission would definitely be more dangerous.

I need to get stronger.

Han Xiao felt a burning desire for strength.

...

Over the following few days, Han Xiao stayed on Planet Aquamarine and helped control the disasters.

Stephanie stayed silent after waking up. Han Xiao had yet to decide on what to do with her, so he just locked her up.

As Stephanie's team had been eliminated, no one was there to maintain the fake memories of the Six Nations' leaders. They all recovered as if they had woken up from a dream.

From the records, they discovered what they had done after 'losing their memories'. Everyone's face turned pale in horror.

Oh my god, what did we do‽

They were terrified. Luckily, Black Star had eliminated the mastermind, or they still would have been controlled.

The Six Nations were worried that Black Star had misunderstood them, so they quickly explained that the declaration of war was a misunderstanding, as were the missiles.

At the same time, the leaders of the Six Nations quickly contacted Bennett to explain what had happened and ask for forgiveness.

Bennett did not reply but only invited them to a meeting, saying that this planet had just survived a disaster and they had to discuss the future development plans.

It seemed like Bennett was not planning to hold them accountable for what they had done when their memories were modified. In the Six Nations' eyes, this represented what Han Xiao meant as well.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations were relieved. They quickly rushed to Black Star City for the meeting, memorized their apology scripts, and planned to explain what had happened.

However, what happened was completely different from what they had imagined!

To Black Star, the Planet Aquamarine armies were meaningless, so the upper echelons of the Six Nations did not take any defensive measures. However, to their shock, as soon as they alighted the plane, Bennett captured all of them.

All the upper echelons of the Six Nations were escorted to the conference room where they met Han Xiao, who was waiting here.

They saw that Han Xiao had an expressionless face and hastily explained themselves.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what is the meaning of this?"

"You must have misunderstood us. Please let me explain."

Han Xiao waved his hands, signaling for them to shut up. "If not for me, you all would have died during the Mutation Disaster. Yet, you declared war against me, betraying our agreement. I'm very disappointed."

"B—but we were controlled by someone," one of them said anxiously. "You know that!"

"Yes, you were controlled..." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "Does that mean I should act as if nothing happened? What if the Black Star City's protective shield could not stop your missiles?"

They had nothing to say to this.

Many people noticed what Han Xiao meant, and their expression changed.

Han Xiao tapped the table and said, "You guys are victims, too, so I won't kill you, but I can't just let it be."

"You mean..." someone said apprehensively.

"Disband your governments and give control to Bennett. This civilization does not need this many governments—one is enough."

From the aspect of a civilization developing as a whole, uniting everyone was very important. Too many governments would only cause resources to be wasted. The governments of the Six Nations had become unnecessary—they were a waste of talents and resources. They were almost a burden to Planet Aquamarine.

As there was no government that ruled over everyone, the Planet Aquamarine civilization had been divided for a very long time. This incident had made Han Xiao feel that it was time. Plus, with the negative effect of the Six Nations' declaration of war against him, this would minimize the objection of the civilians.

Even though this meant that they would have to go through some short term of pain, in the long term, the civilization would become much healthier. Furthermore, there were many benefits to taking over a civilization. As long as Planet Aquamarine's technology could catch up to the galactic level, it could become a great logistics base for the Black Star Army.

Like a bolt of lightning, Han Xiao's words petrified the upper echelons of the Six Nations.

"Yo—you're eliminating the Six Nations?" a leader said with a shivering tone. He was angry and afraid. If Black Star was planning to eliminate their nations, they would not have the slightest chance of surviving.

"Eliminate your nations?"

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. He stood up, walked to the window, and opened the curtains. Many areas could be seen from there—people were crossing by, and magnetic suspended trains shuttled continuously.

"That's a nation."

Han Xiao pointed outside the window before pointing at the officials of the Six Nations in the room.

"You guys are not."

Chapter 678: Hail Feidin!

The disbanding of the Six Nations' governments was quick.

Han Xiao's strength, power, and prestige were all higher than the Six Nations'. Despite being unwilling, the government officials of the Six Nations had no chance to fight back. In the face of overwhelming strength, they realized that if Black Star wanted to take over the entire Planet Aquamarine, it would be a piece of cake, yet he had waited till then to do so.

In the past, Bennett would not have agreed to the plan. However, after this incident, he was willing to take on greater responsibility. In his eyes, the future of the entire civilization was more important; the Six Nations were way too unreliable.

Peaceful means were used to disband the Six Nations. Neither Han Xiao nor Bennett wanted another war to break out on Planet Aquamarine. The bloody example of the Old Era was right in front of them, so Han Xiao's target was only the governments of the Six Nations.

To replace them from top to bottom.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations were arrested, and Bennett's people were placed into the governments. The other government officials at all levels were greatly alarmed, but there was little resistance. The declaration of war from the Six Nations had not only caused them to lose the support of the people, but they had also lost the loyalty of many lower-level officials. The government was not completely united, and every official had their own independent ideas. Throughout Planet Aquamarine, Han Xiao's reputation was more useful than the Six Nations'; he was widely respected.

Bennett got rid of some of the high-ranking officials while retaining the vast majority of the middle and lower ranked officials. The Six Nations were vast—these people were required to manage them. Furthermore, a pyramid-shaped power structure would falter when the bottom level was taken away. It was not suitable to immediately replace the original political structure, or it would cause chaos.

After all, most middle- and low-level officials were simply trying to earn a living. As long as they were not invaded by foreign enemies, they did not mind their wages being paid by another group of people.

Even the upper echelons were not united. Some of them were willing to work for Bennett's new government, including Gu Hui. He was utterly disappointed in his original government. Seeing Han Xiao taking over the Six Nations, he briefly struggled between patriotism and racial justice, and in the end, the latter prevailed.

Things could not be changed anymore; staying there and contributing to the entire civilization was his best choice. Gu Hui knew that letting Han Xiao lead Planet Aquamarine might be a much better choice.

After all the dust settled, only then did Han Xiao announce this to all the civilians. Unsurprisingly, this message sent the Six Nations' people into an uproar.

Although many people were dissatisfied with the declaration of war by the Six Nations, they did not think that their government would disappear in such a short period of time.

Countless people were worried sick that this might be the start of another era filled with chaos. However, after some time, they realized that their lives did not change much at all. The original territories of the Six Nations became six special zones where most of the original laws were retained. Bennett knew that this had to be done slowly so that the civilians could gradually adjust to the new government.

Reality was not a fairy tale; even though Han Xiao's image was like a savior on Planet Aquamarine, there were still passionate patriotic protests as every government knew how to cultivate strong supporters. There were also those with ulterior motives who acted on the opportunity. Such backlash was inevitable during the unification of a civilization. Most people remained silent.

After all, the Six Nations had launched missiles at Black Star City first, so they were not in a position to complain.

For most people, as long as their lives remained unchanged, they would not do anything about the change of government. The people of Planet Aquamarine had experienced countless wars and disasters, so they cherished the stability of their lives. Furthermore, many were the survivors of dead nations from the Old Era and wanderers, not fully loyal to the Six Nations and having more understanding of the situation. This was also one of the reasons that Han Xiao had been confident in doing this.

Since the interstellar era, most stereotypes had shattered. The lines of the nationality were blurred for most people, replaced by the mindset based on the entire race. The importance of the nations depended on what it was compared with, and it was clearly not comparable to the continuation of the entire race. Hence, most people did not oppose Bennett's new government. Furthermore, Black Star was behind Bennett, who was way more reliable than the Six Nations.

The entire civilization was united, and Bennett finally decided on the name of the new government—Aquamarine Federation.

Naming the government after the planet was easier for the people to accept. Han Xiao, though aware of the meaning of the name, still felt that it was weird.

Aquamarine Federation? Why does that sound like a retail store‽

However, no matter what the name of the Planet Aquamarine government was, it was still his logistics base.

The situation was basically finalized.

The takeover of the Six Nations brought a lot of follow-up problems, so Bennett and others were terribly busy. Han Xiao estimated that it would take a few years for things to be fully organized. Planet Aquamarine also needed some time to get through the painful period. The benefits of a unified civilization would gradually become apparent over time.

After the incident was resolved, Han Xiao did not stay any longer. He took Stephanie and returned to Base No.1 on Planet Golden Gate.

The battle with the Vanguard Officials a month ago had brought a lot of fame to Han Xiao—nearly everyone knew about it. This time, the news of Black Star killing several Calamity Grades one after another once again shocked the entire Star Field.

The Purple Crystal Civilization did not conceal this incident. They believed Han Xiao's statement that Stephanie and the others were assassins sent by Klent. They vigorously promoted the fact that Klent's assassination had failed, which boosted their people's morale and weakened the negative impact of the losses in the secret war.

The Klent Civilization was utterly confused.

We do want to kill Black Star, but we haven't done anything yet. When did we send assassins?

It must be another Star Cluster that sent people to kill Black Star, since they can blame it all on us!

Klent was furious.

Do these people think we are the scapegoat king‽

Although the two sides were at war, Klent was not willing to take responsibility for a failure that they did not commit. They publicly announced that it was entirely fabricated.

Purple Crystal's reply was very simple. I'm not listening! I'm not listening! I'm certain it's you!

The partners of the two sides were at war, and their governments were accusing each other. The various organizations of the Shattered Star Ring were all watching the drama between Purple Crystal and Klent.

Han Xiao, who had caused this incident, also received a lot of attention.

The fact that Black Star had finally mastered psionic energy had made many organizations take him even more seriously. This meant that Black Star was much more threatening!

Killing many Calamity Grades matched up to his Beyond Grade A seed title, and this kind of lethality was more threatening than just being tanky. In a short period, Han Xiao's reputation and position in the entire Star Field rocketed once again.

The other Star Cluster civilizations, while shocked, secretly lifted Han Xiao's position on the Beyond Grade A seed list up a few places.

Han Xiao had already felt the influence of this incident on his way to Base No.1—everyone recognized his face. When he returned to the base, he also noticed that many mercenaries looked at him with even more admiration.

This trip back to Planet Aquamarine had taken about twenty days, so he had ten more days of holiday.

After returning to the base, Han Xiao first inspected the operations of the Black Star Army during this period. Tens of thousands of trainees from various training camps had become official mercenaries, and about a hundred battleships had been added.

My mechanical army is quite damaged. I can use these ten days to replenish it.

He had to return to the battlefield after the holiday, so he decided to build his army with the remaining time he had. Before that, he wanted to first claim the reward for the third round of [Prey].

Feidin had not gone out recently. Han Xiao found him, chatted with him awhile, and touched him a few times before letting go of Feidin, who had a strange expression on his face.

Chen Xing, who happened to be out, was blushing a bit. She quickly returned control of the body to Feidin.

As Feidin became stronger, he was able to suppress Chen Xing alone. Plus, his relationship with Chen Xing was getting more affectionate, so he occasionally let her out for a break, which Han Xiao happened to bump into.

Although the soul was different, the body was the same.

As the luck on his hand was lingering, Han Xiao rushed to the side and opened the interface to claim the reward for the third round.

Round Three complete.

Please select the target to draw abilities from...

There were ten enemies, but Han Xiao was only interested in the abilities of two of them—Stephanie and that Mechanic.

If he selected that Mechanic, there was a very high chance of him getting a Mechanic talent, so that would be a safe choice.

If he selected Stephanie, unlike from Shana, her Esper ability was not compatible with him at all, so the effect of the abilities would definitely be weakened. The best result would be getting a Template Talent, but that depended purely on his luck.

After considering for a few seconds, Han Xiao's eyes became firm; he had made his decision.

A Mechanic talent is great, but Molding Talents are hard to come by!

A man must dare to dream!

You have received the reward: Draw one ability/talent from Stephanie.

Alert: Stephanie is an Esper. Part of the possible abilities have been automatically adjusted to your class.

Randomizing... complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Cell Resonance] - Ability: You can condition your body state through the vibration of your cells, increasing the energy production efficiency of your cells. Recovers 11% energy, purges one debuff. Cost: 1,500 Stamina. Cooldown: 90 seconds.

[Electromagnetic Resonance] - Ability: By affecting the frequency of electromagnetic waves, you are able to obstruct certain communication methods and radar detection or the brainwaves of individuals. There is a chance that [Confused], [Hallucinating], and [Abnormally Excited] might be applied to the target. The closer the distance, the stronger the effects of the debuffs. Success rate is related to INT. Cost: 150 Energy. Cooldown: 6 seconds.

[Object Weakness Attack] - Ability: You can easily discover the weakness of objects. Your next attack will deal extra damage and three chain damages ranging from 5% to 15% damage of this attack. There is a chance to cause the [Heavily Injured] effect. Cost: 240 Energy. Cooldown: 28 seconds.

[Will to Battle] - Talent: +180 END, -75 INT, -25 LUK.

[Legendary Battle Technique] - Talent: Every third attack will deal 35% extra True Damage.

Han Xiao was stunned before becoming overjoyed.

I really got a Molding Talent‽

Hail Feidin!

Chapter 679: Saving the World with Normal Attacks

All five choices were decent, and they all had different focuses.

[Cell Resonance] could instantly recover energy and purge a debuff. It could be used by any class and was a powerful support ability.

[Electromagnetic Resonance] was a rather good assistive ability as well. It could reduce the target's strength. When facing an opponent of the same grade, this could give the user a quick advantage. [Object Weakness Attack] was an explosive damage type ability. Though its applicable situations were limited, it was still not too bad.

[Will to Battle] was a tank talent. +180 END was actually quite high, but it had a side effect. Han Xiao felt that he was tanky enough, so he was not interested in this talent at all.

Luckily, the lowest limit for Luck is zero, otherwise mine would go negative if I chose this talent...

What was most surprising to him was the fifth choice—[Legendary Battle Technique].

This was a proper Molding Talent!

Plus, it was one of the best 'Battle Technique' talents!

Every third attack would deal an extra 35% True Damage, which meant that his attack increased by a huge amount out of nowhere, as talents were passive abilities and had no cost at all.

Every third attack? With the attack speed of Calamity Grades, how many third attacks would there be in just one second?

This was spectacular!

The other four choices paled in comparison. Han Xiao did not even have to think and directly picked the fifth choice.

You have received [Legendary Battle Technique]!

That was hella lucky!

Han Xiao was very excited. He quickly went to the combat training room to test the new talent.

The floor split open, and the alloy wall used to test damage rose up. Han Xiao started punching the wall continuously.

True Damage ignored defense. For example, if the theoretical damage of an attack was 10,000 and the target's resistance reduced it to 5,000, adding the True Damage, that attack would deal 5,000 plus 3,500 damage.

Almost double!

If the attack was completely absorbed by a shield, a magic barrier, or heavy mechanical armor, the effect of the True Damage would only go to the shield durability and armor value. When the enemy was actually damaged, only then would this deal True Damage to the enemy.

Therefore, tank enemies that took on attacks with their body would be completely countered by this!

If not for the Germinal leader's talent, I would have had a very tough time against this. Han Xiao was glad.

No wonder Stephanie was a boss-type character—her abilities were too overpowered!

Han Xiao was excited. He was already very tanky. Comparatively, although the attack of his Army Style was not weak, it did not appear as important as how tanky he was since he had always been fighting enemies that were stronger than him or many enemies at once. Most of the time, he relied on how tanky he was to defeat the enemies.

If he used the authentic way of utilizing the Army Style, he would completely destroy any enemy that was about the same level as him, even more so now that he had mastered psionic energy. He would be able to fight many enemies at once even without making use of how tanky he was.

However, his health-energy cycle made him way too tanky, causing the Army Style to pale in comparison. His Indestructible Body title had covered up the fact that he was a Mechanic for too long.

But not anymore!

The [Legendary Battle Technique] was already strong enough when used by others. When used by a Mechanic using the Army Style, it would be absolutely terrifying!

From the NPCs in his previous life that had similar talents, the Great Mechanic Han knew that this type of talent could be applied to summoned creatures and mechanical armies. The summoned creatures could enjoy the talents of the Mage through their magic link, while the mechanical army could share the effect of this talent through Mechanical Force. After all, the mechanical army was considered a type of equipment, so the talent would apply to them just like it would apply to a weapon in one's hand.

Han Xiao expanded a few elite mechanical soldiers that he had brought along and carried out tests to find out how this talent worked.

After testing, he found out that every machinery had its individual [Legendary Battle Technique] effect count. This meant that every third attack of that machine would trigger the True Damage, instead of the total times the entire army attacked.

The attack count of every machine was calculated separately and not together. So, if Han Xiao fired one machine twice then changed to another machine for the third attack, it would not trigger.

Han Xiao started fantasizing. If the attack count was calculated together, it would mean that if a hundred machines fired together, thirty-three of them would have extra True Damage.

Gently giving himself a slap, Han Xiao shattered his own fantasy.

Hmm, it's already strong enough.

Han Xiao was very satisfied. This meant that if a hundred machines all fired three times, the last hundred attacks out of the total three hundred attacks would all have True Damage. The ratio was the same as if the attack count was calculated as a whole. The difference was just the frequency that the talent was triggered.

However, this talent did not require the attack to land to count—it could still be triggered by attacking at nothing!

This meant that the triggering timing of this talent could be controlled. If he used it well, he could even make every attack that landed on the enemy have extra True Damage.

Han Xiao immediately had a lot of ideas in his mind.

A strong talent could completely change one's combat capability.

To the Great Mechanic Han, [Legendary Battle Technique] was as strong as his health-energy cycle. It increased the strength and lethality of his mechanical army once again!

If I can make this idea a reality, my actual combat capability will multiply many times over! I might really be able to crush anyone under Beyond Grade A!

The excitement in Han Xiao's eyes was almost overflowing.

The effect of touching Feidin was dreamlike!

The phrase 'becoming stronger through the battles' inside the [Prey] mission introduction was indeed true. Although he had been targeted by Thousand Shadows, Han Xiao felt that it was worth it now that he had received this talent.

Han Xiao browsed through his attributes on the interface. He was so strong that even he was afraid of himself.

Just moments earlier, he had worried that once he returned to the battlefield, knowing how tanky he was, the enemies would only send a few people to fight him so that he would not be much of a threat.

Now, however, if they sent too few people, he would be able to kill them all!

Han Xiao locked himself inside the modification room. Using the last ten days, he planned to adjust Phillip's combat control mode so that the mechanical army's fighting method would be able to fully utilize the power of [Legendary Battle Technique]. For example, he could let one team of artilleries standby with their third attack, use the other units of the army to create an opportunity, and let this standby team focus fire when suitable, making sure that when his attack landed, it would deal a ton of damage. However, in order to have the army do such a delicate job, he needed a large calculation module.

Herlous and the others could handle any Black Star Army matters, so he did not have to worry. The best way to increase the Black Star Army's position was for him, the leader, to become stronger.

The flames of war filled the West Wind, Chaida, and the Kaya Star Systems.

Ralph had been counting down to reminding Black Star to return to the battlefield. He needed him to stabilize the battle between the high-level combatants. The Bloodshed Land's Jorde was also wary of Black Star, who had disappeared for two months.

At the same time, in the middle of Hidden Red Robe Abbey's palace, Austin was hovering about four meters above the ground. The oversized robe dragged on the floor. Desoro and the others were standing at the side.

Austin slowly opened his eyes and said with a sentimental tone, "I never expected him to change this much."

The Forbidden Sorcerers around all had strange expressions on their faces. Some time ago, Austin had summoned Lagi, and they had watched their full conversation from the side.

Lagi was Austin's fourth disciple. The Forbidden Sorcerers present had all followed Austin for a long time and knew Lagi. However, upon seeing him again after so many years, that once vigorous and fearless former Forbidden Sorcerer commander felt like a completely different person.

They could not imagine what Lagi had gone through in these years.

Austin shook his head and said, "However, although his personality has changed, he's still as determined and resolute as he used to be, rejecting me like that without hesitating."

After banishing Lagi for so many years, Austin had long forgiven his mistake. Thus, he asked if Lagi wanted to return under his command. To his surprise, Lagi was determined to return to Black Star without even the slightest hesitation.

Although Lagi made it look like it was not a big deal, Austin could see that Lagi was really thankful to Black Star for saving him. He no longer longed to return to Hidden Red Robe Abbey; Black Star had replaced his position and received Lagi's loyalty. Lagi was not only doing this because he was thankful but also because he saw a lot of potential in Black Star.

When Austin saw the Observer's Mark on Lagi's head, he understood what Han Xiao meant as well. He had planted an Observer's Mark on Lagi despite knowing that it would be discovered—this was to express how important Lagi was to him.

Seeing that, Austin was willing to let him go.

"Following a Beyond Grade A seed is a dangerous path. Don't die..." Austin sighed.

At the dock outside the palace, Lagi was walking to the spaceship. When he arrived, many Forbidden Sorcerers had gone to welcome him, but when he left, he was alone.

He turned around and looked at the Mage palace that he had once known every corner of for the last time, and a mixture of sentimental emotions appeared in his eyes. Then, he shook his head and stepped onto the spaceship.

Whoosh!

The hatch closed, covering his lonely yet unbending back.

The spaceship slowly lifted off, turned into a stream of light, and disappeared.

Chapter 680: End of Slacking Off

Inside the house of happiness, an interrogation was going on.

"Who sent you?" Han Xiao yelled as if he did not know.

Stephanie was constrained by Electromagnetic straps all over her body, through which high voltage currents coursed. It seemed like she did not feel pain at all, and she looked at Han Xiao with an expressionless face. Her face was pale, her lips slowly opened, and she said with a soft voice, "Like I said, you won't get any intelligence from me."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and did not speak.

The [Prey] mission did not end yet, and the fourth round was still in an inactive state. Thousand Shadows could share the senses of his shadows to a certain extent, so Han Xiao did not want to expose the fact that he knew the truth. Doing so would make the next round more dangerous. Therefore, for the past few days, he had conducted fake interrogations on Stephanie whenever he was free, acting like he did not know about Thousand Shadows.

Whether he was just doing meaningless work or not, being cautious would do no harm.

Han Xiao had already made hundreds of Genetic Medicines from her, but Han Xiao was rather stumped by what to do with her.

If he did not know that the enemy behind her was Thousand Shadows, he might have kept her to produce more medicines. However, Thousand Shadows could sense his shadows, so keeping Stephanie was a huge hidden risk.

The look in Han Xiao's eyes kept changing. In the end, he sighed. With a flash of Mechanical Force, nanotechnology particles shot out from compressed orbs and covered his arm like black sand, turning into a psionic cannon, pressing onto Stephanie's head.

Bang bang bang!

After some time, the sound of cannon fire stopped.

The door opened, and Han Xiao walked out, shaking his head.

Although Stephanie's history was rather tragic, he did not become soft hearted. Thousand Shadows' shadows had lost themselves and were unable to escape his control. Death was a relief for them instead.

The reward for killing Stephanie was 280% for killing someone many levels higher, giving Han Xiao more than 350 million Experience, replenishing his Experience a little. It also gave him a Stephanie Character Summon Card.

Character Summon Card—Stephanie: [Resonance Penetration]—Reduce the physical defense of the target by 50% – 80% using close range resonance. For every 100 END the target has, the duration will decrease by 1 second.

Basic Duration: 24 seconds.

Minimum Duration: 3 seconds

Usage: 0/4

Han Xiao closed his eyes and recalled the images from earlier. When struggling for her life, Stephanie seemed to have recovered to her true self. He clearly saw the relief and gratitude in Stephanie's eyes as her life faded.

This time, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Stephanie's Last Wish]

Mission Introduction: In the last moment before death, she begged for your help to make up for the one thing she regretted the most in her life.

Mission Requirements: Find the last Antarrian bloodline.

Reward: 15,000,000 Experience

Remarks: This is a Ruins Mission. Some people might be interested in this.

Triggered a mission...

Han Xiao was a little surprised.

Antarr was Stephanie's civilization, which was long gone.

It seemed like not being able to protect her civilization was her biggest regret. However, after becoming Thousand Shadows' shadow, her belief had become twisted, and she only could recall it moments before her death.

Ruin Missions were a special type of mission. The reward from the interface were usually very low, but they were mostly related to places that were buried in history. Exploring ruins would often lead to more rewards.

If I have the time, I might do it.

His holiday was coming to an end. Han Xiao thought for a while, took out his communicator, and flipped dozens of pages through his contact list to find Ralph.

In the Kaya Star System, a fleet was moving in stealth mode. This was a guerrilla fleet, mainly from a partnered organization, the New Phylen Rebels. Most of the battleships were assault models.

Inside the main control room of the Shining Crow grade flagship, the commander Morred and the others were having a strategic meeting around a silver table. The people in charge of the other partnered organizations of this fleet were listening from the side. Above the table was a three-dimensional star map, marked with the dense Bloodshed Land strongholds and fleets that were colored deep red.

"In our area, there are twelve Bloodshed Land strongholds. This operation is the highest level order given directly by the combat command. Including us, a total of twenty-seven fleets are involved in this mission. What do you guys think?"

Morred was a Phylen Human. His body was thin and boney, and he looked very weak, but the strength of his muscle fiber was close to that of an alloy. His weight was close to one ton. He was one of the high-ranking combatants of the New Phylen Rebels, a Calamity Grade Mechanical Pugilist. His body was fused with semi-organic metals.

When Han Xiao took his leave from the war, the situation of the secret war changed drastically. Bloodshed Land's army gathered with the forefront armies. With unstoppable momentum, they kept expanding the strongholds in the West Wind, Kaya, and Chaida Star Systems. In two months, they built hundreds of stronghold planets that guarded each other. The positions of these strongholds were carefully selected, allowing them to affect many Star Zones. They had completed the first part of their strategic blueprint.

The rulers of the three border Star Systems did not interfere in the unofficial secret war. According to some gossip, the Bloodshed Land had already sent out emissaries to contact and negotiate with those three Star System Civilizations. Although only two short months had passed, according to neutral intelligence organizations' data and investigation, the influence of Purple Crystal had dropped by about 13.7% in those three Star Systems.

Reducing Purple Crystal's influence of border Star Systems was one of the main strategic goals of the Klent Kingdom. It was true that Star Systems were a part of Star Clusters, but the Star Clusters were determined and planned later. Hence, Star System Civilizations were not technically under the Star Cluster Civilization's command.

If Purple Crystal's influence dropped severely, the Star Systems that had received an invitation from Klent and pressure from the Crimson Dynasty in the future would announce independence and join Klent. Even though the Colton Star Cluster's border Star Systems and Klent's Seoul Star Cluster were separated by a desolate region, those border Star Systems would still be able to become parts of the Seoul Star Cluster. With the Star Cluster level stargate technology, distance was not a limitation.

In order to redetermine the area of a Star Cluster, the most important factor was support from a Universal Civilization. This was where Klent got their confidence to snatch these Star Systems. Purple Crystal was semi-neutral; unless they were willing to become a vassal of their Universal Civilization, the Federation of Light would not help them.

The Tyrant Heber's armies were all elites that had fought hundreds of battles. They were known in the Shattered Star Ring to be the top tier military forces. In a direct battle, Section Zero would be no match for them.

Section Zero's largest advantage was their strategy. The Combat Command took Han Xiao's advice and adjusted their strategy during the two months when the Bloodshed Land was at their peak strength. They stopped looking at temporary losses and gains, split up the Bloodshed Land's forces, and focused on harassing and surprise attacks. They were waiting for an opportunity.

Morred and the others were indeed discussing the large scale counterattack operation that had been in the works for a long time!

"The Bloodshed Land's biggest army is in the West Wind Star System, where all eight Vanguard Officials are. Other than Black Star, no one will be able to deal with them. Comparatively, the Kaya Star System has the fewest Bloodshed Land troops, so it's the most suitable target," a staff sergeant said.

Morred nodded and said, "The goal of this operation is to get rid of the twelve Bloodshed Land strongholds in this area. The twelve strongholds are connected by a hyperdrive base station. Despite them having a very quick reinforcement speed, their total size will not change. Our twenty-seven fleets will attack every stronghold planet and split their troops up. Then, the Knife Team will raid and destroy this hyperdrive base station, making the enemies lose the ability to quickly shift the battlefield. Following that, we'll rapidly destroy the twelve strongholds."

The crowd nodded. This was the right method to deal with hyperdrive base stations. The attacking side would gain the upper hand. Section Zero's strategy was simple and efficient.

"The twenty-seven fleets can be classified into four types of fleets—Restraint Teams, Feint Teams, Standby Teams waiting to attack the strongholds, and the Knife Teams that are going to raid the hyperdrive base station." Morred knocked the table. "We are one of the three Knife Teams. The enemies have set up a very strong defense around the hyperdrive base station, so our mission is very important."

"When everyone arrives at their positions, we will start the operation..." The deputy's words had yet to finish. Suddenly, the 3D star map was replaced by a communication request that interrupted his sentence.

Ralph appeared with his hands behind his back. He looked around and loudly said, "This operation is temporarily postponed. New reinforcements will be joining the operation. Morred, standby nearby and wait to rendezvous with them. They will be raiding the hyperdrive base station with you."

Postponing the operation just for reinforcements?

Everyone was stunned. Morred reacted the quickest. He frowned and said, "Who are these reinforcements?"

Ralph smiled satisfyingly and said with a joyful tone, "Black Star."

Morred's eyes sparkled.

It's him!

After the shocking battle two months prior, Black Star had left the battlefield. Now, he had finally returned!

"With such a strong helper, our chances of winning are even higher. At least in terms of high-level combatants, we're at an advantage!"

Morred nodded heavily. No wonder the operation was postponed. It was acceptable since it was because they were waiting for Black Star.

A few days later, the Black Star Army's fleet arrived in the Kaya Star System and rendezvoused with Morred.

The main ship connected, and Morred waited with the several ship captains at the bridge. The hatch far away opened, and a man in black clothes walked out first, followed by a group of people in mercenary clothing. This time, Han Xiao had brought six hundred battleships. The people following him were Herlous, Harmon, and a few Grade B officers. Reynold was in charge of logistics, and Lagi had yet to return.

Quickly sizing Han Xiao up, Morred approached him and extended his hand passionately.

"I'm the commander of this guerrilla team, Morred. I'm from the New Phylen Rebels. We welcome your assistance, Black Star."

"Hi." Han Xiao shook his hand.

"Let's not waste any more time. The operation's plan is like this..."

The two of them walked side by side as Morred explained the steps of this mission to Han Xiao. The others followed behind as they walked toward the main control room.

Han Xiao was distracted as Morred explained. When accepting the mission, Ralph had already told him the details, so what Morred said was all repeated.

Ralph had been looking forward to his return. As soon as his holiday ended, Ralph sent Han Xiao to the Kaya Star System to join this counterattack that they had planned for a very long time.

Within the past two months, the goals that Han Xiao had set had basically all been completed. He had learned a Cutting-Edge Knowledge, completely rebuilt his mechanical army, completed his Promotion and leveled up to 195, turned a huge amount of Experience into actual combat capability, and learned the very surprising attack type Molding Talent. His strength had skyrocketed.

As Purple Crystal was at a disadvantage in the war, they had more and more hope for Han Xiao. As soon as he returned, he was given a very big responsibility.

I've made a good start. As long as I keep accomplishing difficult tasks, my position in Section Zero will definitely increase very quickly!

His goal was to make the Black Star Army a force that had help from Purple Crystal, so of course, he would not reject the important missions.

He put aside the Class Advancement mission for the moment. The Experience that he had saved in his interface was limited, and he was afraid to finish it too early since the update time was ten years long. His current strength was enough to deal with most situations. There were not many Lv.180 legacy blueprints, and they were extremely complicated to obtain. Before the next time he could slack off, Han Xiao would have no time to finish the Class Advancement mission. The secret war was an important part of his plan; he had to take it seriously.

As they arrived, Morred turned on the 3D star map and explained in even further details. Only then did Han Xiao start to listen carefully. A mission popped up on the interface that required him to follow with Morred to complete the raid of the hyperdrive station.

After some analysis, Morred scanned through the data of those people, and his expression became solemn.

"According to the intelligence, the hyperdrive base station is guarded by tightly grouped guards. There are fifteen Calamity Grades standing by. Among the fifteen calamity grades, twelve of them were found by the Bloodshed Land in the Seoul Star Cluster, and the other three are officers of the Bloodshed Land.

Morred pointed at a drawing, on it was a ferocious looking female creature with a light green skin. She had short and gold hair, and a few ferocious scars stretched across her face. She was blind and used mechanical eyes.

"Tamaria, Bloodshed Land Adjudicator, high grade Calamity Grade, nickname 'Poisonous Bones'. It's said that she's killed more than a billion people, including 10,000 Supers and 100 Calamity Grades. This rumor is exaggerated, but the truth is most likely not far from it. In conclusion, she's very murderous and is a famous mad woman under the Tyrant..."

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and thought, Green skin? She probably has Beastman blood.

Even the Tyrant's female subordinates were muscular.

There were many talented people under Heber's command. Other than the eight Vanguard Officials, there were also many famous Calamity Grade officers. It was just that the eight Vanguard Officials were the most famous.

Morred stared at Han Xiao and said, "This woman and the other fourteen Calamity Grades are all yours."

Han Xiao turned around and patted Herlous' shoulders. "You heard the man. They're all yours."

Herlous' face was filled with question marks.

"I'm kidding. Why would I let you die like that?" Han Xiao laughed. "Don't worry, it's just fifteen Calamity Grades. Even if I can't win, can't I run?"

Chapter 681: Black Star's Weakness

An enormous black and metal space station hovered in space. Its exterior was equipped with rows of satellite-level guard cannons. Nine armed satellite fortresses circled the space station.

This was the T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station, which was the target of Section Zero's attack.

At this time, Tamaria and the other upper echelons were all in the conference room inside the base, attending a remote meeting.

The war commander, Jorde, appeared on the projection screen.

"According to reliable sources, eleven days ago, Black Star left his headquarters after two months. We speculate that he will be returning to the battlefield soon. Everyone present, pay attention to Black Star's whereabouts," he said in a serious tone.

All of Bloodshed Land's commanders in the three Star Systems were attending the meeting. Black Star had returned to the battlefield—this was the reason that this meeting was being held. After Black Star's battle with the eight Vanguard Officials, Jorde had paid a lot of attention to Han Xiao.

Although one person would not be able to determine the entire war, Black Star was one of the most dangerous high-level combatants of Section Zero. Sending out a notification just for him was very necessary in Jorde's eyes so that everyone would at least be prepared.

"According to the recent rumors and his fight with the eight Vanguard Officials, I have arranged some intelligence on Black Star. I will send it to all of you later," Jorde said.

He firmly believed that knowing his enemies would get him an advantage in battle. Purple Crystal would definitely place Black Star in a very important position. This set of intelligence on Black Star could make sure that every commander knew about the enemy. If they were attacked, they would know how to deal with Black Star.

The conference ended very quickly, and the commander of the T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station received the information. He only looked at it for a few seconds before Tamaria walked to him and grabbed the communicator away to look at it herself.

The base station commander was speechless. Tamaria's position in the base was higher than his. This green-skinned woman was not only the captain of more than ten high level combatants but also the supervisor. Other than obeying his orders during battle, she usually did not even pay attention to him at all. The base station commander was already used to it.

Tamaria only glanced through before she sneered and threw the communicator aside.

"I was wondering how strong Black Star could actually be, but it turns out he's so easy to deal with..."

The base communicator picked up the communicator and browsed through it. He then immediately understood what Tamaria meant.

Jorde had added the method to deal with Black Star in the intelligence as well.

Indeed, the result of Black Star's fight with the eight Vanguard Officials was astonishing. However, after analyzing the fight, Black Star's weakness had become obvious as well—his attack ability was very limited. Through the entire fight, he was completely suppressed by the eight Vanguard Officials, only surviving due to his Indestructible Body. Due to that, the trouble that he could cause was minimal.

Although Black Star was rumored to have mastered psionic energy recently, there were tons of other Mechanics around the universe that had. It was far from being impossible to deal with.

Furthermore, strategic psionic weapons were equivalent to galactic nuclear weapons. Even Star Cluster civilizations would not use them unless they had no other choice, and they definitely would not in this unofficial secret war. Unless Black Star wanted to visit the Hegaboye Court Martial of the three Universal Civilizations and enjoy more than a hundred years in prison, he would not use Primordial Psionic Energy.

Due to those many reasons, Jorde had detailed the method to deal with Black Star in this intelligence—all they had to do was send one or two experienced Calamity Grades and three to five normal Calamity Grades to destroy Black Star's mechanical army. Black Star would then pose no threat and become useless in the war.

According to how the Section Zero's organizations had been avoiding losing any high-level combatants, as long as Black Star was dealt with, the threat of the other Calamity Grades of Section Zero would also decrease tremendously.

No wonder Tamaria was disdainful. Black Star was not as difficult to deal with as they had imagined.

"Nonetheless, Black Star's body is great." The fangs in Tamaria's mouth showed, and her tone was full of desire and cruelty. "I wonder if I can get his abilities after I eat him."

Tamaria's race's culture was very savage and bloody. They believed in gaining the enemy's power by eating their flesh and that consuming strong enemies would make them stronger. Tamaria was extremely interested in Han Xiao's body and thirsted to gulp him down. She licked her lips.

Ohm!

At this time, the alarm of the base suddenly sounded. Everyone's expression changed as they hastily returned to their stations.

Seeing that the commander had returned, someone quickly reported, "Commander, Stronghold Planet 4 has been attacked. Requesting reinforcements from other strongholds. This is the enemy ship's data collected by the radar."

T-04 Hyperdrive Base was the core that maintained the wormhole in the twelve strongholds. Any kind of reinforcements had to be reported to the base station. After approval, the quick reinforcement route would then be opened. The base station's job was to overlook everything.

The base station commander quickly scanned through the report and said, "Which strongholds have responded?"

"1, 6, 9, and 12."

"Open Reinforcement Channel 12." The base station commander did not hesitate.

The operational team nodded and got to work.

Visible through the wide-angle projection porthole of the space station, thousands of blue beams launched from two special devices of the base station, creating a deep blue circular shaped wormhole on both sides. The energy at the edges of the wormholes rippled, expanded, and gradually stabilized. The two wormholes aligned with each other in both location and size.

The next moment, streams of hyperdrive light shot out from the left wormhole and directly into the right wormhole in an instant. These were the reinforcement fleets, having taken less than thirty seconds to arrive.

"It's done." The base station commander nodded.

However, before he could catch his breath, three planets out of the twelve stronghold planets turned red on the monitoring interface again, signaling that they were under attack!

"Hmm? This isn't a simple attack!"

The expression on the base station commander's face drastically changed. He quickly gave out the reinforcement orders and loudly said, "T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station, get ready for battle. Activate all armed satellite fortresses, and send out all fleets. The enemies may appear any time!"

These signs were common when attacking Hyperdrive Base Stations. The base station commander reacted very quickly and instantly discovered that Section Zero's target was the base station. However, this was a plot that they had to take part in as the attackers had the upper hand. The only way to resolve it was to defeat the attackers.

Section Zero had been strategically splitting up their troops for two months. Now, the effect of that finally surfaced. They chose T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station as the target of their counterattack because this area had limited troops and had yet to build a long-range stargate.

Everyone in the base station started to act. Tamaria narrowed her eyes and stood up. Not only was she not nervous, she even looked excited and eager.

"Great, someone's finally here to fight. I haven't exercised my bones for too long. They're getting rusty."

Very soon, more strongholds were attacked and requested reinforcements. Despite knowing that this was a plot, the base station commander had no choice but to deploy more and more troops.

As they were getting nervous, the radar of the base station rang with a piercing sound of alarm.

"Warning! Warning! A large number of unknown targets are approaching!"

They looked at the porthole, which was now adjusted to see extremely far distances. Streams of hyperdrive lights stopped and showed the Section Zero fleet.

"They're here!" The base station commander clenched his teeth.

"Finally!" Tamaria tightened her fists and walked out in big steps.

...

The T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station was in sight, and the armed satellite fortresses were activated.

"The enemy fleet has completed their preparation. It seems that they guessed our strategy."

Morred looked at the projection and did not mind. He did not think that such a simple strategy would fool the enemies. It just had to be effective.

"Time is limited. All units, attack!"

As the order was given, this fleet quickly accelerated and marched forward. Through radar identification, both sides started firing at each other from an extreme distance. The crisscrossed particle cannon beams filled this dark area of space with vibrant colors.

The nine armed satellite fortresses formed an enormous irregular shaped shield, protecting the base station from attacks.

There was a total of three Knife Teams attacking the base station. Reinforcements appeared from two other directions and dispersed the attacks. The pressure on Morred's fleet was greatly reduced.

Han Xiao's team followed Morred in the charge as well, mixed within the fleet.

The distance between the two sides was still huge. They were firing at each other from far away and had yet to enter the close-range combat stage. Han Xiao suddenly received Morred's communication.

"Black Star, did you see the nine armed satellite fortresses? They are the generators of the base station's protective shield. This kind of protective shield is very strong, and we don't have enough time to slowly destroy it. The commanders of the other two teams and I have discussed this. We plan to all send out one team to board the armed satellite fortresses and destroy at least one of them!"

Morred spoke very quickly. What he meant was that as long as one armed satellite fortress was destroyed, the protective shield would have a hole in it. Before the other armed satellite fortresses got into position to close the gap, they would be able to use this opportunity to rush in to attack the base station. The mission would only be successful when the base station was destroyed.

They did not have much time. In this operation, the Restraint Teams and the Feint Teams had the most numbers. As the enemies' reinforcements would only be divided when these strongholds were facing enough pressure. This way, not many enemy teams would be able to back up the hyperdrive base station. They had to use the opportunity when the enemies were split up and destroy the base station.

"No problem. My teammates don't have to follow me. I will act alone."

The mission on the interface changed to 'destroy an armed satellite fortress'.

Han Xiao nodded and agreed. He let Risda control the spaceship then jumped out of the ship, activating the Mountain Ape mechanical suit and switching into Interstellar Travel mode. With a deep blue arc, he avoided the direct crossfire area and headed to an armed satellite fortress from the side.

The other teammates headed to another fortress, and the other two teams sent out ships as well. Han Xiao moved alone. As long as he could get to the armed satellite fortress, he would be able to destroy it very quickly.

I'm swifter and a smaller target when I move alone. Plus, with my name, it's easier for me to restrain the high-level enemy combatants if I move alone.

In his vision, the tiny armed satellite fortress started to look bigger. He could clearly see the mechanical structure on the surface of the armed satellite fortress. Very soon, the fleet stationed to guard the base station discovered him, and some of the cannons turned and fired at him.

With the tactical screen reminding him of the direction of high energy particle cannons, Han Xiao focused fully on dodging the attacks, sometimes using the Hovering Shield Shuttle to form a psionic shield and block the stray attacks.

Not long after, Han Xiao headed right into the base station defense fleet, bolting swiftly between the enemy spaceships.

With his brain in a highly active state, he processed tremendous data every second. Han Xiao had no time to pay attention to the outside world—he was completely focused on dealing with the attacks coming from all directions. After an unknown amount of time had passed, he suddenly felt that the pressure became much lighter!

Han Xiao turned around and saw that, without realizing it, he had penetrated the entire line of defense. Further away, Morred and the other two Knife Teams were also in close combat with the base station fleets, dividing the enemies' attention and decreasing the density of attacks on Han Xiao's side.

Finally, some good teammates.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Without further delay, he headed right toward an armed satellite fortress.

The armed satellite fortress was spherical. It looked like a small planet from the outside. It was less than one percent the size of Planet Aquamarine. It sounded small, but when looking at it from a close distance, Han Xiao felt it did not look much different from a normal planet.

The blue protective shield stopped him outside. Han Xiao pressed onto the protective shield and activated the shield neutralizer to its maximum output. The shield within a hundred meters started to ripple at a high frequency. Its light started to dim, and its energy level started to decrease. Estimating that the shield had reached its critical point, Han Xiao's other arm turned into a psionic cannon and fired right at the shield!

With a blue explosion, a more than thirty-meter-wide hole appeared in the protective shield. Compared to the entire protective shield, this hole was as tiny as a droplet of water in the ocean, but it was more than big enough for Han Xiao to enter.

Han Xiao looked around, the hole was shrinking from its edge, repairing itself. He summoned more than twenty Army Boxes and rushed in before the hole closed.

This armed satellite fortress had a simple artificial atmosphere for the maintenance personnel. Han Xiao quickly landed on the surface.

Landing on the ground, he looked around. Around him was an undulating mechanical landscape, cold and lifeless, full of mechanical beauty.

"Warning, hum! Five high energy reaction sources detected!"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked over.

At the edge of the sky, five enemies with a strong 'I'm a Calamity Grade' vibe approached and landed nearby. The person at the front was wearing a ferocious and bulky heavy mechanical suit and carried a huge dark-gold mechanical axe on one shoulder.

Clank!

The facial armor of this person opened, showing a ferocious face and short and gold hair. It was the person that Morred had warned Han Xiao to be careful about, the Bloodshed Land Adjudicator stationed at T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station, Tamaria.

"I've been waiting here for you for a long time."

Tamaria stared at Han Xiao and smiled ferociously.

When she first spotted Black Star, she had been overjoyed. Following Han Xiao's route, she had brought a few people to this satellite in advance to wait for Han Xiao's arrival.

In terms of duty, she was meant to deal with Black Star. Personally, Tamaria was also eager to fight with Han Xiao.

"Just five?" Han Xiao looked around and sneered. "All of your Vanguard Officials could not even kill me. You're underestimating me. It will probably take all fifteen Calamity Grades in your base station to even give me any pressure."

"Ha, Jorde has found your weakness. We're not trying to kill you, so there's no need for all fifteen of us to be here. Five of us is more than enough."

Han Xiao was not surprised. After his last battle, Bloodshed Land would no longer deploy many people trying to kill him but had instead decided to send fewer people just to restrain him.

Tamaria licked her lips, her bloodthirsty desire overflowing. "Your body is amazing. Wait for me. I will bite off your flesh piece by piece, chew your bones till they shatter, drink your blood till they dry, suck on your bone marrow, and eat every single cell from your body. I heard your recovery ability is very strong. I hope you can make me feel full."

Han Xiao felt disgusted. If these words had come from someone else, they might just be trying to threaten him, but he could hear that Tamaria truly meant it.

This woman wants to eat me‽

How twisted... I don't like it!

Boom!

At this time, the ground started trembling. The surface of the armed satellite fortress cracked open. Artilleries rose from within like metal forests, and all the barrels turned around and aimed at Han Xiao.

Thousands of Thousand Beast Soldiers sprinted out from under the ground and surrounded him.

This was the armed satellite fortress's defensive measure against enemies on its surface.

In the blink of an eye, enemies were everywhere!

Tamaria closed her facial armor and roared, "Before this war ends, you're not going anywhere!"

Chapter 682: Hope of the Village

Boom!

From afar, the Thousand Beast Soldier army charged straight for Han Xiao like a tsunami. The earth shook as they got nearer, and their specially-made armor glowed with a deadly light.

Tamaria raised her arm and threw out her dark-gold axe. The axe sliced through the wind and formed a spinning ball of red flames as it smashed down toward Han Xiao's head.

Hu!

Han Xiao stomped down on the ground, and his body shot toward the sky to avoid the trajectory of the flying axe.

The axe that was flying in midair suddenly changed its trajectory and chased after Han Xiao.

Han Xiao looked down from above and saw an alloy chain attached to the end of the axe. The alloy chain seemed to be able to extend indefinitely with the other end of it attached to Tamaria's mechanical suit. She could obviously control it from afar.

A floating guard behind Han Xiao then released a psionic shield and collided with the incoming axe!

Clank!

Sparks flew in all directions!

The burning axe was not able to make a dent in the psionic shield and returned to Tamaria's hands as the chain shortened.

This attack signaled the beginning of the battle.

Phillip raised the alarm, and as Han Xiao lowered his head to take a look, all the artillery towers on this armed satellite fortress began to open fire at him!

Tuk tuk tuk!

The large barrel of the cannon spat out billowing smoke with missiles and laser beams being showered down on him from all directions and in all different colors!

Han Xiao was not only facing five Calamity Grade Supers but also the defensive measures of this armed satellite fortress.

His psionic thrusters were activated at full capacity, and Han Xiao transformed into a blue bolt of lightning as he dodged the never-ending wave of attacks nimbly.

Boom!

All the explosions were narrowly avoided by him, but the high temperature of the aftershock heated up the exterior of his mechanical suit.

Mushroom clouds covered the entire sky and the bolts of lightning from the artillery fire made it seem as though a large thunderstorm cloud was expanding above the armed satellite fortress.

The particle cannons shot through the dark clouds to reveal the light of the world.

Ignoring the danger of the battlefield, this scene was like Buddha's light breaking through a thousand clouds and was extremely spectacular.

Dark clouds covered Han Xiao's vision, and the Armor value of his mechanical suit continued to decrease under the barrage of cannon fire. Han Xiao's expression remained calm, and he activated the Army Box. Together with his [Mechanical Force Field] skill, his Mechanical Force was boosted.

His energy had a new [Void] attribute, and he could borrow the void to transmit energy.

This meant that the efficiency of his Mechanical Force being transmitted was greatly increased.

Clank!

The sound of his Mechanical Army being activated could be heard from the clouds, and his Mechanical Army went to war!

"Orders for the army have been received. Attack region has been confirmed, hum..." Phillip's voice sounded from Han Xiao's helmet.

The next instant, over a million psionic cannons opened fire and rained down like a thunderstorm!

Boom!

The entire region was instantly flattened, and the metallic ground cracked up from the psionic canons. Mechanical parts flew in all directions, and craters could be seen all over the surface of the satellite.

Almost forty percent of the defensive canons were destroyed in just a single blow!

The armed satellite fortress was completely suppressed by Han Xiao's army. Han Xiao's Mechanical Army descended and dismantled the artillery towers of the armed satellite fortress.

Fighting could be seen all around with the smoke of war covering the entire battlefield.

All of a sudden, a high energy alert sounded from Han Xiao's mechanical suit, and he immediately dodged to the side.

Hu!

Tamaria's axe then shot narrowly past his body.

The mobility of a Pugilist was extremely high, and the moment her first attack missed, Tamaria turned around in midair and swung her axe down in rapid succession.

Her powerful attacks resulted in a deafening sonic boom with every attack.

Han Xiao released two psionic shields with his hands and received the attack without any hesitation. Sparks shot out in all directions, and a loud clanging sound resounded like thunder.

Swoosh!

Dark silver nanoparticles then rushed out from the tube at the back of the Mountain Ape suit and transformed into four half bodied phantoms. The phantoms floated behind Han Xiao and aimed their canons at Tamaria and Han Xiao, who were fighting.

Bang!

The four phantoms launched their first round of attacks but did not manage to stop Tamaria from engaging in close combat battle. She circulated her energy to form a flaming shield and blocked their attack!

Bang!

The second round of attacks was fired, and Tamaria remained indifferent. Such a level of attack was not sufficient to make her dodge.

When the third round of attacks was fired, Tamaria wanted to block it as before, but suddenly, she felt a powerful force ignoring her arm and going straight for her organs.

The [Legendary Battle Technique] was activated!

The sound of the explosion was louder than before!

Bang!

Tamaria's expression dropped, and she could not help but retreat.

What a powerful penetrating force!

Tamaria suppressed her surging blood and had a face of shock.

Han Xiao made use of the opportunity to widen the gap between them as he looked at the battle information from his interface.

Thirty-five percent of True Damage from the previous attack had exceeded 12,000 points of damage. Apart from the basic boost from his Mechanical Force, he did not use any other skills. Just the additional True Damage from the [Legendary Battle Technique] skill had exceeded the reduced damage from the three rounds of attacks!

A Molding Talent is truly terrifying! Han Xiao thought to himself.

This talent was truly the bane of all Pugilists.

Tamaria should be a level 230 Pugilist who was toward the tanky side. Her Endurance should be about 1,600 points, so she should have a few talents to increase the strength of her body. Her health should also be above 300,000.

Currently, Tamaria's health should be more than fifty percent higher than Han Xiao's, but both of them were tanky in different ways. Han Xiao relied on the conversion between energy and health, and his recovery rate could make a Pugilist who walked the path of being a tank doubt their own life.

This talent truly exceeded my expectations. As long as my Mechanical Army can ensure that their attacks hit the target...

All those thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's head in less than a second, and the other four Calamity Grade Supers caught up and launched their various attacks!

Han Xiao hurriedly avoided all the long-ranged attacks and suddenly felt an attack coming from behind him.

One of his opponents was a Pugilist who walked the path of agility. He nimbly made his way around Han Xiao like a shooting star, and his alloy dagger shot toward Han Xiao's spine. He wanted to immobilize Han Xiao.

Han Xiao did not even turn back, and the four phantoms collapsed back into their nanoparticle form. The nanoparticles then formed a mechanical hand that was about seven to eight meters tall. The fingers and palm formed a psionic shield and blocked the sneak attack of this Pugilist.

Bang!

The mechanical hand then threw the Pugilist away as though it was throwing away rubbish!

After experiencing the strength of his new talent, Han Xiao no longer fought Tamaria and the others personally. Instead, he issued a new command, and half of his Mechanical Army surrounded the five Calamity Grade Supers.

He would attack them from the side to disrupt the enemy's attacks and harass them.

"Do you think this junk will be able to stop us‽"

Tamaria's roar resounded, and the flames on her body exploded.

At the same time, outside the protective shield of the hyperdrive base, Morred and the other two Section Zero fleets were fighting with the defensive fleet of the enemy.

They had boasted the upper hand at the start of the battle and forced the enemy to retreat. However, the other strongholds had received news from the base, and a portion of their troops had immediately been sent to reinforce this hyperdrive base.

The battle was extremely intense at the moment, and neither party had the upper hand.

"Only Black Star has boarded one of the armed satellite fortresses. How is the situation over there?"

Morred could see Han Xiao's location from the main control room.

Section Zero had sent a few teams of powerhouses to attempt to board nine different armed satellite fortresses. However, all the others had been forced back, and only Black Star had managed to board one of the armed satellite fortresses.

Morred's palm was covered with cold sweat. His fleet was currently outside the protective shield. Whether or not he could destroy the base was dependent on if Black Star could destroy the armed satellite fortress.

He was the hope of the entire village!

"Sir, we have observed the battle between Black Star and the armed satellite fortress. The enemy has sent five Calamity Grade Supers to stop him, and they seem to have tied Black Star down."

"This is bad." Morred felt his heart tighten.

If Black Star was tied down, the entire battle would end up in a stalemate. The longer the battle dragged on, the more disadvantageous it would be for them.

Gritting his teeth, Morred issued an order.

"Inform the other two fleets. Ask all their Calamity Grade Supers to form a small team and reinforce Black Star. He has been pinned down by the enemy and needs support!"

Chapter 683: One Combo!

At the center of the base station, the base station commander was also observing Black Star's movements.

"Black Star is the only one to have penetrated the protective shield. Tamaria has taken people to deal with him," an observing officer said.

The base station commander nodded and looked at the radar. Suddenly, his eyes constricted.

"Hmm? The enemy has sent a Calamity Grade team toward the armed satellite fortress that Black Star is in? They're trying to back Black Star up," the base station commander said with a deep voice. "Just in case, send five more Calamity Grades to Black Star. We can't let the enemies destroy our armed satellite fortresses. If the base station loses its protection, our loss will be inevitable!"

As the order was sent, five more Calamity Grades were deployed.

Both sides sent reinforcements to the battlefield that Black Star was in.

...

On the armed satellite fortress, Han Xiao had been fighting with Tamaria and the other four with his mechanical army for quite a while.

The battlefield extended over hundreds of miles. Everywhere they passed, the surface of the fortress was torn apart and messed up.

The battle in the sky had reached its climax.

Boom boom boom!

The five Calamity Grades dashed left and right. Broken mechanical soldiers fell from the sky one after another.

Boom!

The dark-gold mechanical axe was being spun around like a tornado, crushing every machinery in its path. Tamaria punched and kicked all the mechanical soldiers around her into pieces.

The other four were also continuously damaging the mechanical army.

It seemed like the enemies were unstoppable. However, they were actually wounded and exhausted.

The attacks of close to a million machines were very intensive. They were going to get hit sooner or later. Following the triggering requirement of the [Legendary Battle Technique], Han Xiao had changed Phillip's control method. The first two attacks were focused on limiting the enemy's dodge routes to increase the accuracy of the third attack.

Furthermore, he split up the attack frequency of the various units. This meant that the army's every round of attack included a lot of True Damage. It was very lethal and gave the enemies a lot of pressure.

Tamaria did not dare ignore the attacks. She had to focus fully every time the army attacks. Otherwise, if she got hit by the True Damage attacks, suffering light injuries would be lucky.

She was furious.

This is called limited lethality‽

Jorde, you're full of sh*t!

Most of the low-grade mechanical soldiers were still fragile when facing Calamity Grades, but their attack was now on a different level.

Previously, most of the time, Han Xiao had used the mechanical army to reduce the enemy's energy before he went to beat up the enemy personally. Now, however, the enemies were completely trapped in the mechanical army and were barely able to hold on. They did not even have a chance to approach Han Xiao.

Phillip firmly controlled the entire battle. Han Xiao was free enough to carry out Virtual Intrusion on this armed satellite fortress.

The armed satellite fortress seemed to have countless defensive measures and had held back half of his mechanical army. In order to quickly destroy this satellite, Virtual Intrusion was the most efficient method.

Boom!

At this time, Tamaria suddenly used some sort of ability and penetrated the army's encirclement, dragging a blood red flame behind her. Like a rocket, she bolted up to Han Xiao!

"Ha!"

With a loud roar, the mechanical axe slashed down!

"Tsk."

Han Xiao had no choice but to stop the Virtual Intrusion. Two psionic shields appeared from each of his hands and blocked this attack.

Clunk!

The axe was stuck between the shield. This time, as if the axe suddenly had an absorption force, the flames all over Tamaria's body flowed right into it as it became more and more red.

The next moment, a thick, powerful blood-red wave launched from the axe!

It landed at zero distance!

Boom!

Being attacked by a powerful hit, Han Xiao coughed and was about to back off. To his surprise, Tamaria moved quicker and tied Han Xiao's arms with the chain at the end of the axe, pulling him back.

"Like I said, you're not going anywhere!" Tamaria roared and heavily headbutted Han Xiao's forehead.

Boom!

Han Xiao felt dizzy. Tamaria had at least two thousand Strength, so it was normal for her to overwhelm him in terms of raw strength.

The vibration penetrated the helmet's shock absorption module and caused a buzzing in his ears.

Tamaria was just about to continue attacking, but Han Xiao suddenly exited the Mountain Ape and exposed his body. Not only did he not look panicked, he even looked a little speechless.

"You really are... eager to die."

The next moment, Han Xiao's actions made Tamaria confused.

Not only did he not escape, he wrapped his arms around Tamaria's waist and hugged her.

"You..."

Before Tamaria could react, she instinctively felt an extreme sense of danger. Suddenly, she figured something out, and her entire body was frozen.

All the mechanical army in the sky suddenly turned their barrels around and aimed at Han Xiao... as well as Tamaria!

"Let me go!"

Tamaria was extremely shocked and hastily tried to push Han Xiao away.

However, the Mountain Ape mechanical suit, now controlled by Phillip, shot out dozens of compressed orbs that turned into all sorts of traps and were planted around the two of them. With all those traps, neither of them were able to move for about two to three seconds.

They both became stationary targets.

Han Xiao chuckled beside Tamaria's ear and said, "Didn't expect that, did you? I'm just the bait."

"Do you want to kill yourself ‽" Only after Tamaria said this did she realize that Han Xiao had the Indestructible Body title. Rage and despair appeared on her face. She clenched her teeth and said, "Do you really think you're unkillable?"

"No." Han Xiao blinked then said something that Tamaria did not understand. "But I'm immune to True Damage."

The next moment, countless psionic cannons from all directions fired at once!

Boom!

The expanding ball of light consumed the two of them. The other four Calamity Grades ran away with all their might.

The ball of light expanded to its maximum before exploding. The shockwave blew away everything around it, like using an eraser on a drawing.

The exploded ball of light turned into sparkling light debris and fell like rain.

At the center of the explosion, Han Xiao was healthy and vigorous. He summoned the mechanical suit and wore it again. Then, he let go of the charred corpse that was still emitting black smoke, allowing it to fall from the sky.

With [Steel Body], he was immune to True Damage. Through the health-energy cycle, the health lost from the explosion swiftly recovered. Not only was he not injured, he even felt revitalized.

Oh, it's because the attribute increase from the Advanced Strengthened Life has already stacked so many layers. No wonder...

Han Xiao slightly raised his brows.

Using himself as the bait to control the enemy before using the mechanical army to focus fire—this was his trump card after obtaining the ability of the health-energy cycle. As long as the enemy approached him without knowing, they would fall into the trap.

After obtaining [Legendary Battle Technique], the lethality of this method had become an ace card that could now kill the enemy.

Tamaria had instantly been killed under the focus fire!

No matter who she was, in Han Xiao's eyes, she was just a Grade A+ Pugilist that had about seventy percent health, enough to be killed with one combo.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the other four terrified Calamity Grades with a smile.

"Come on, let's get to know each other."

The four Calamity Grades shivered. With horrified expressions on their faces, they only had one thought in their minds.

Don't come any closer!

Chapter 684: Deciding Victory

Boom!

The armed satellite fortress was plowed by the mechanical army again and again. The four Calamity Grades were no longer surrounding Han Xiao but running for their lives.

While attacking the enemies, Han Xiao was also hacking into the armed satellite fortress. After all, destroying the armed satellite fortress was his main goal. After killing Tamaria, the other four did not dare get close to him at all, so no one interrupted him.

Many of his Virtual Technology abilities were upgraded compared to before, so Han Xiao successfully obtained control of the armed satellite fortress without too much effort. A Grade A+ Virtual Mechanic could penetrate most artificial intelligences.

Han Xiao searched through the modules of the armed satellite fortress and sighed.

"No self-destruction module? Shame."

After giving it some thought, Han Xiao controlled the armed satellite fortress to open its surface tunnels. He then sent some of the mechanical soldiers into the armed satellite fortress and planted secondary psionic bombs.

In terms of efficiency, destroying the energy furnace inside the armed satellite fortress was much more convenient than destroying the armed satellite fortress from outside.

At the same time on the main battlefield, a few small, agile spaceships dashed between the chaotic battlefield. In them were the Calamity Grades sent by Morred. They were trying to break through the enemies’ defenses and back Han Xiao up.

However, the high energy particle cannon attacks were too concentrated on the battlefield, so the reinforcement teams were forced to retreat again and again, unable to penetrate the enemies.

As the Bloodshed Land fleets arrived at the battlefield through quick reinforcement channels one after another, the main fleet could no longer provide cover for these reinforcement teams.

"The situation isn’t good. We took too long. Many enemies in the strongholds have gotten rid of the teams that were restraining them earlier and are arriving at the base station extremely quickly. The number of enemies we’re facing has multiplied many times!"

Inside the flagship, Morred’s expression changed as he heard the report.

He clenched his teeth and pushed the words through the gap of his teeth.

"If this goes on, we will only achieve a pathetic victory! Black Star is the key to breaking the situation, but he’s alone without backup. Are the helpers we sent still unable to break through their defenses?"

"They can’t. The enemies seem to know our intention and completely blocked all routes to the armed satellite fortress that Black Star is

on."

Morred’s expression became firm. He waved his hand and said, "Send my orders. All units, retract the formation and push forward in his direction. Open a path for the reinforcement teams and penetrate the enemies’ defenses!"

en

As soon as his sentence ended, everyone was shocked.

The current situation was very clear; it could be divided into five layers.

The most exterior layer was where Morred and the three Section Zero fleets were. One more layer inside was the base station’s defense fleet. Those two were fighting each other.

After the defense fleet was the base station’s gigantic protective shield, separating the exterior battlefield and the base station core. One more layer inside were the nine armed satellite fortresses around the base station. In the center of all this was the target that Section Zero planned to destroy-T-04 Hyperdrive Base Station.

Morred’s order was to have the entire fleet march forward without backup and open a path for the reinforcement teams for Black Star. This was no different from giving up any possibility of retreating and deliberately entering the enemies’ encirclement.

If they penetrated the enemies’ line of defense but were unable to break through the base station protective shield immediately, it would be the end of them.

"This is a gamble. It’s too risky!"

"I don’t agree with such a reckless method. It’s better to fight steadily."

Many fleet captains objected. They belonged to the partnered organizations and were not Morred’s direct subordinates.

The downside of an alliance force was showing again—when facing a danger that required them to take risks, they would not be united and would prioritize their own safety before the overall outcome of the battle.

Objections came from the communication channel nonstop. Morred’s expression became more and more angered. Only the New Phylen Rebels were directly under his command, but they were far from enough. He needed help from the other organizations.

Bang!

Morred could not take it anymore. He bashed the table and interrupted the objections from the various captains.

"I know, each and every one of you wants to be favored by Purple Crystal and become a long-term partner of a Star Cluster civilization. But you don’t want to fight for it with your lives. Do you think that the Purple Crystal civilization is easy to fool!

"I’ve had enough of being defeated by the Bloodshed Land again and again. There’s an opportunity right in front of us. His Excellency Black Star is fighting the enemies with his life. As long as we back him up, we will be able to break the stalemate and win this battle!

"You’re all big organizations from your Star Systems, famous and renowned, why have you all become a bunch of cowards? If you don’t even have the guts to take a little risk, pardon me for saying this, but why did you even join this war?"

The communication channels became quiet; no one spoke.

Seeing this, Morred said in a deep voice, "Execute the order!"

The entire fleet was no longer moving forward slowly. They retracted their formation and bashed right into the base station defense fleet’s formation like a hammer!

Enduring attacks from all directions, the fleet entered deep into the enemies’ fleet and headed toward the armed satellite fortress that Han Xiao was on.

At first, the enemy fleet was messed up by the sudden change, but they adjusted their formation very quickly and obstructed Morred’s fleet.

Not long after, Morred’s fleet was no longer charging forward quickly. Like they had stepped into a swamp, every step forward became difficult. At this point, they had already reached deep into the line of defense and were only a short distance away from the armed satellite fortress’s protective shield.

Yet, it seemed like the Morred fleet had to take ten times the time they took to get here to overcome such a short distance.

"Hang on. The armed satellite fortress is right in front of us!"

The command room was shaking from the attacks as Morred loudly ordered, "Reinforcement teams, it’s your turn!"

At this time, the atmosphere was tense among the reinforcement teams.

With a serious face, the captain of the Calamity Grades loudly said, "Everyone, get ready for battle. His Excellence Black Star needs our help. Go!"

The next moment, those Calamity Grades jumped out of the spaceship, moved swiftly using the other spaceships as cover and finally penetrating the line of defense under Morred’s nervous gaze. They headed toward the armed satellite fortress.

Morred looked at those Calamity Grades full of hope as they quickly approached the armed satellite fortress.

Whether they would win or lose all depended on this!

However, as he was being extremely nervous, something suddenly happened!

The members of the reinforcement team were just about to reach the protective shield of the armed satellite fortress when the armed satellite fortress suddenly emitted a blinding light and exploded!

The entire armed satellite fortress exploded from within. This fortress that looked like a small planet turned into a blinding explosion in the blink of an eye!

Countless scraps of armor, parts, and machines were blown away, turning into floating space debris. The impact was as large as a planet exploding!

As the fortress was destroyed, the base station protective shield lost one of its generators. The shield in this area suddenly disappeared, showing an enormous hole more than big enough for a fleet to enter.

Behind the hole was the hyperdrive base station now without any defense.

The path toward the enemies’ core opened!

A person flew out from the wreckage of the armed satellite fortress.

Han Xiao!

The sudden explosion attracted the attention of everyone on the battlefield. Friend or foe, they all looked over with shock on their faces.

Black Star had destroyed the armed satellite fortress all by himself!

The mechanical army had already been retrieved. Han Xiao took his Army Boxes and left the wreckage. There were quite many burn marks on his mechanical suit.

He saw the reinforcement team members right away. He waved and sent a voice message.

"You guys are late."

The reinforcement team members were all mentally prepared for a bloody fight ahead, but now they felt as if they had just punched a ball of cotton. Dumfounded, they all looked at Han Xiao.

Wh—Where are the enemies?

Did you kill all of them?

They were completely shocked.

How many Calamity Grades did Black Star just kill!

"What an amazing job!"

Morred was stunned for an instant before he was overjoyed, yelling with excitement.

He had thought that Black Star was held back by the enemies and had no back up, but it seemed like the situation was the opposite of what he had speculated!

He had never expected that Black Star could destroy the fortress even while being surrounded by many Calamity Grades!

How damn reliable!

The protective shield broke very timely; it was a perfect opportunity.

Not having the time to think about other things, Morred grabbed the opportunity and quickly issued the orders. The entire fleet headed right through the hole in the gigantic protective shield, firing intensely at the base station.

At the same time, the base station was trembling from the attacks. The scene inside was full of chaos. Piercing alarms echoed in every corner.

"Warning! Warning! High energy attack detected!"

Like the countdown of the grim reaper, the bright and firework-like beams of attacks outside the windows rapidly approached.

Inside the main control room, the base station commander looked out the porthole, shivering and twitching from fear. Like everyone alongside him, he was in despair.

He could not understand it. Why is Black Star so much stronger than the intelligence said?

He had sent out five Calamity Grades to back Tamaria up just in case. They were supposed to guard against the reinforcements of Black Star. However, he had never expected that Black Star would kill Tamaria when those five Calamity Grades were still on the way!

She was the strongest person there, yet she had been killed just like that!

When the five reinforcements arrived, the four Calamity Grades following Tamaria were either dead or heavily injured. They were crushed. Black Star did not stop there and went ahead to demolish the five Calamity Grades that had just arrived!

Black Star eliminated more than half of the high-level combatants stationed at the base station all by himself!

The ‘how to deal with Black Star’ information in the intelligence file was absolutely useless!

This completely messed up all their plans. The base station commander was petrified and unable to think.

In the face of such overwhelming strength, he felt powerless and had no solution for it. All he could do was watch as Black Star turned the armed satellite fortress into fireworks.

Time seemed to slow down, and the attacks got closer. The bright light lit up the base station commander’s face and filled his vision.

At this moment, he only had one thought in his mind.

I lost… to Black Star.

Chapter 685: Postwar Conference

Thousands of attacks landed on the hyperdrive base station, tearing it to pieces silently in an instant.

At this point, Han Xiao had already returned to the Blacklight Stealth. He took off the mechanical suit, massaged his shoulders, and smiled when he saw the hyperdrive base station getting destroyed.

Victory at last. My efforts didn’t go to waste.

The notification of the strategic mission being completed popped up on the interface. Destroying the armed satellite fortress alone made the Mission Rating very high. His Favorability with the Purple Crystal increased by 1,350, and he was also awarded with tens of millions of Experience.

However, this was just a small part of the reward that he received this time. Killing Tamaria who was many levels higher than him alone gave him more than half a billion Experience.

Earning Experience through killing Calamity Grades is actually quite efficient. Without the players here, that’s a rather good option.

War was indeed an opportunity. Where else would he be able to find so many Calamity Grade enemies?

Through this battle, he had a clearer idea of his own strength. Compared to two months prior, his combat capability now was on a completely different level.

With (Legendary Battle Technique], he could crush most opponents with just his mechanical army. Despite having just entered the Grade A+ territory, his actual combat capability had already exceeded top Grade A+ Supers.

With so many powerful Molding Talents that synergized with each other, the actual effect in combat was better than he imagined.

Not even sending ten normal Calamity Grades to fight him would basically be gifting him kills!

As long as a Beyond Grade A Super doesn’t interfere, the others in the Bloodshed Land should all be no match for me…

Han Xiao only had this thought for a second before he immediately slapped himself and got rid of it.

That was close. I almost flagged my own death!

Han Xiao turned to look at the battlefield.

With the base station destroyed, the enemies lost their reinforcement channel. The stalemate was broken instantly. The morale of Section Zero was boosted, and they started to clean out the remaining enemies. The enemies’ complete defeat was just a matter of time.

Han Xiao had completed his mission, so he did not take part in the following battles. He slacked off with the Black Star Army fleet at the side.

Morred and the three fleets intercepted and surrounded the remaining enemies. The ending of this battle was already decided. As it quickly ended, Section Zero finally achieved their first big victory.

The three fleets cleaned up the battlefield and picked up the loot before leaving the scene in groups.

After more than an hour in hyperdrive, the fleet slowly stopped in a safe area.

Han Xiao received Morred’s invitation to attend the postwar conference on the flagship.

After calling up Herlous, Harmon, and the other officers, Han Xiao linked his spaceship with the flagship.

Whoosh!

The hatch opened. In front of them was the link corridor. Han Xiao led the others into the flagship. A few receptionists were waiting there. They quickly approached and welcomed him with a respectful tone.

"Your Excellency Black Star, everyone has arrived. They’re all waiting for you."

"Lead the way."

Han Xiao nodded and followed the receptionist to the door of the conference hall inside the flagship.

The door opened, and joyous and delightful voices came from inside. The atmosphere seemed very positive.

There were quite a few people in the room. All the people in charge of the partnered organizations within the fleet had been invited. After finally achieving a victory, everyone was elated.

Han Xiao stepped in, and chatter inside the hall suddenly stopped. Everyone looked over. Seeing that it was Han Xiao, their eyes were filled with admiration and respect. They opened up a path for Han Xiao.

"Black Star, you’re here. Quick, take a seat."

The center of the hall was a circular conference table, and everyone was sitting there. Morred sat at the host seat. As he saw Han Xiao, he quickly stood up and passionately invited Han Xiao to take a seat.

"Hi, how are you? Have you eaten?" Han Xiao sat on his seat and casually greeted the others.

"Haha, now that everyone is here, let’s start the conference. His Excellency Ralph has something that he wants to say to us."

Morred smiled and pressed the desk. Ralph’s remote projection image appeared above the center of the conference table.

Ralph cleared his throat and spoke.

"Everyone, you’ve done a very good job. You’ve eliminated the base station, causing the Bloodshed Land’s twelve strongholds to be isolated and their forces to be separated. Our troops successfully destroyed those twelve strongholds with very low casualties. This is our first overwhelming victory!"

Clap clap clap!

Everyone applauded.

"Morred, you were very decisive. Your contribution in destroying the base station is huge. Carrie, you restrained the enemies and completed your mission. Pierer, you…"

Ralph praised everyone present one after the other. The applause continued nonstop. Han Xiao’s expression was strange—this reminded him of exam result announcements.

They had just won a battle, and now they were already being evaluated for their contribution.

"Also, the biggest merit of this victory…"

Ralph turned to look at Han Xiao with a big smile on his face. "Black Star, you destroyed the enemy’s armed satellite fortress and defensive measures alone, which can be said to be the key point in turning the battle around!"

Everyone nodded in agreement.

Who said that one person could not change the battle? Black Star alone could complete this kind of key tactical mission-his actions determined their victory and decided the result of the skirmish.

"Ahem, I just did what I should." Han Xiao maintained his expression and waved his hand like it was not a big deal.

Morred could not help but add, "If not for you, at most, we would have ended up with a tragic victory. Of course, you deserve the biggest

merit!"

Han Xiao’s mouth twitched, and he had no choice but to smile politely.

Ralph smiled and said, "You don’t have to be humble. I have already reported to the superiors. They are very satisfied with your achievements. The people above have decided to increase their investment in the Black Star Army as a reward. Also, they will consider making you a long-term partner."

When Ralph said this, everyone’s expression slightly changed. They were jealous.

The biggest goal they had in joining the secret war was to become a long-term partner of a Star Cluster Civilization. Black Star was already one step ahead of them.

In the Purple Crystal Civilization upper echelons’ eyes, the Black Star Army’s importance had probably already exceeded any of the other Section Zero members.

Now this is what I wanted to hear, actual benefits… Han Xiao smiled.

"By the way, you also killed the Bloodshed Land’s Adjudicator, Tamaria. This is the first high-level Bloodshed Land officer that has died. The Bloodshed Land has lost an important member. You’ve done a good job."

Han Xiao was stunned. So, that testy woman I killed is the first important Bloodshed Land officer to die in the secret war?

This means that… I took Ty-Ty’s first blood?

So… Heber won’t get angry… right?

Due to the disadvantage they had been at for the past two months, Ralph had been incredibly stressed. He kept wanting to get revenge. As soon as Black Star returned, he had finally made the Bloodshed Land lose. Ralph felt relieved.

The more he looked at Han Xiao, the more satisfied he was.

In his eyes, the combat capability displayed by Black Star exceeded the standard of normal Calamity Grades. Usually, only Beyond Grade As would be able to crush a group of Calamity Grades. However, Black Star was not Beyond Grade A. Hence, he felt that there was only one explanation for this—Black Star’s potential was extraordinary. Furthermore, his potential was becoming real strength way too quickly. He was obviously much stronger than he had been two months ago!

Purple Crystal had looked into Han Xiao’s past before. About ten years ago, Black Star had just entered the galaxy and built his mercenary group. Back then, he was not even Grade B, yet in less than ten years, he had risen extremely quickly.

This meant that Black Star had the highest amount of Beyond Grade A potential!

In all the years since the end of the exploration era till now, none of the Beyond Grade As had risen as quickly as Black Star!

Ralph was exhilarated. As long as the Tyrant did not do anything, Black Star might be able to crush all the Bloodshed Land Calamity Grades. He was basically a murder weapon among the high-level combatants, the biggest advantage that Section Zero had!

This evaluation right after the battle was done on purpose. One reason was to use rewarding Black Star as an example to encourage more Section Zero members to win battles, eliminating the downside of an alliance force.

The second reason was to express their attitude toward Black Star on how important he was to them.

Killing two birds with one stone.

At this moment, no one realized that the effects of this skirmish would be much greater than they thought…

Chapter 686: Tyrant's Plan

After this victory, Section Zero temporarily did not carry out any more counterattack operations. Han Xiao left the main fleet after getting the contacts of Morred and the others.

The reward for this mission came very quickly. Purple Crystal was very generous, giving him a total of twenty-seven million Enas and other rare resources, clearly expressing Han Xiao’s importance to them.

After this battle, Ralph saw Han Xiao as a treasure.

He told Han Xiao to stand by temporarily. Only on important missions would he consider using the Black Star trump card. There was no need to deploy him for normal guerrilla missions.

Of course, Han Xiao was more than willing to slack off. He could make use of this opportunity to digest the resources that he had just received from the Purple Gold Civilization and replenish his mechanical army. Furthermore, Lagi was on the way there as well.

At the same time, the influence of this war was slowly spreading

"Section Zero achieved a huge victory in the Kaya Star System, destroying twelve Bloodshed Land stronghold planets."

To the various civilizations and organizations of the Shattered Star Ring who had been paying attention to the secret war, this news quickly made them feel energized. Ever since the start of the war, this was Section Zero’s first successful counterattack. They have finally put a stop to their string of failures.

These organizations knew what Purple Crystal’s strategy was-give up some areas strategically and split up the Bloodshed Land’s forces. They knew that the secret war would enter a stalemate sooner or later and that the war would probably only end after many years.

The talented individuals appearing in the secret war became the focus of the various organizations.

War had always been a stage for the strong, a shortcut to honor. There were always people who became famous through war. To all those who have been paying attention, Han Xiao was clearly the brightest star born on this stage. Everyone else paled in comparison before him.

Black Star’s turning point since the start of the war was when he was able to survive the attacks of all eight Vanguard Officials. With that, he earned the nickname of ‘Indestructible Body’, which spread across the entire Star Field.

Just two months later, he once again gained astonishing achievements, killing ten Calamity Grade Supers, including the Bloodshed Land Adjudicator, Tamaria. He once again made sensational news.

The Beyond Grade A seeds in the past had been quiet for a long time. After so many years, none of them became a new Beyond Grade A. Similarly, when those Beyond Grade A seeds first entered the list, that was when they were the most famous. Like a cycle, it was now Black Star’s turn.

It had not been long since Black Star became a Beyond Grade A seed. These two achievements were his signature deeds, sparking discussion between countless people. These two unbelievable achievements produced a chemical reaction, making Han Xiao the latest Star Field level hot topic. His fame in the Shattered Star Ring skyrocketed, and his position grew just as quickly.

Before this, Black Star had not been considered someone huge in the Shattered Star Ring—the majority of his position was because of Floating Dragon. However, he had gradually stepped out of the Floating Dragon title, and his own position had started to grow. He could be said to be an overnight sensation.

ans

Through this battle, it was not just potential that Han Xiao had shown but his true combat capability, which almost no one in his grade could match up to. To many organizations, Black Star was almost half a Beyond Grade A. It seemed like he really had a chance to sit on the Beyond Grade A throne one day.

The rise of every Beyond Grade A was always sensational. If a fifth Beyond Grade A really appeared in the Shattered Star Ring, the issues between Klent and Purple Crystal would become unimportant.

When Han Xiao stood his ground against the eight Vanguard Officials, those large organizations had still been spectating. However, after the news of him killing several Calamity Grades spread out, many people could not just watch anymore.

Some wanted him dead, while some wanted him to live.

More people wanted to contact him.

Many that were previously just watching decided to join in.

Han Xiao had yet to know that the storms he had stirred up had made the influence of the secret war exceed beyond what it was supposed to have.

A cyclone hidden under the secret war was brewing

At this time, Klent and Purple Crystal knew nothing about this, nor did they think that this war would go out of their control.

In the Bloodshed Land headquarters, specifically in the Tyrant’s palace, the small mountain-sized Heber sat on the hovering throne, looking down at the frightened Jorde.

"Tamaria… died?"

Jorde shivered. Not daring to look up, he looked down at the ground and said, "She died at Black Star’s hands. I’m responsible, too. My intel was inaccurate…"

It would not matter if those below Calamity Grade died, but Tamaria was different. She was one of the key members who had followed the Bloodshed Land through battles from the earliest time. She had even received personal guidance from Tyrant before. The death of an experienced adjudicator was a huge loss.

"Hmm, okay," Heber said with an indifferent tone.

Jorde stood still for a while but did not hear the next half of the sentence he had expected, so he cautiously asked, "What… are you planning to do?"

"Dying in war is a righteous end for warriors," Heber said slowly. "In war, you can kill people, and people can kill you."

Jorde was stunned. Did this mean that Tyrant was not planning on getting revenge?

"Er… I thought you…"

"You thought I would be furious and immediately avenge Tamaria?" Heber frowned slightly. "Then, what would I need you people for?"

Heber was domineering, but that did not mean that he was reckless and impulsive. He was calm and would not change his plan just because one or two of his subordinates died.

As long as there was no Beyond Grade A on the enemy’s side fighting, he would not easily make a move. This had been decided with Klent long ago.

Usually, Heber would be biased toward his subordinates, but in wars, he was cold-blooded.

Wars were trials of blood and fire; Heber was not going to protect his subordinates. He needed his officers to grow in the flames of war. Even if all of them died, he would not feel heartache. His organization was his tool, not his weakness.

Jorde did not know what to say.

"However, this isn’t over," Heber said.

"What does that mean?" Jorde asked honestly.

"He will be held accountable for this; our fight will be inevitable," Heber said coldly. "He has Beyond Grade A potential, but as of now, he still is a Calamity Grade. If I kill him now, it will be too boring, so I will give him time to grow.

"If he stays at Calamity Grade, I won’t do anything to him, but as soon as he becomes Beyond Grade A, I will personally strike and beat him to death!"

After a pause, Heber said, "If he can’t become Beyond Grade A even by the end of the war, I will still kill him by then."

"But… Black Star is very strong. He will cause a lot of casualties to our high level combatants." Jorde could not help but speak up. He hoped that Heber could change his mind and kill Black Star immediately.

"I know the casualties will be high…" Heber looked down at Jorde, speaking slowly. "Therefore, Black Star is the enemy I’m leaving to you guys. Survive against him, become stronger or die. Those that don’t even have this little amount of faith in themselves can request to come back to the headquarters. They won’t ever have to go into the battlefield again."

Heber knew that Han Xiao was strong, so he wanted to use him to train the officers under his command.

Now that all the forces were paying attention to Black Star, if he, a Beyond Grade A, personally attacked a Calamity Grade, it would seem petty of him. Even though Black Star was a Beyond Grade A seed, he would still be able to easily kill him.

Heber disdained killing Black Star. In his eyes, not only would that be a despicable act, it would also be short-sighted.

Killing Black Star immediately would at most clear the obstacles of this war and decrease the casualties of his organization. In Heber’s eyes, that was not even worth mentioning compared to what he could get from killing a Beyond Grade A.

He was willing to give Han Xiao time to grow.

The Bloodshed Land was so enormous and powerful because he, the Beyond Grade A, was the core that united all of it.

As long as he was there, no casualties were unrecoverable.

As long as he was there, the Bloodshed Land would be able to rapidly develop.

He needed an opponent worth fighting. If Black Star could really become a Beyond Grade A, the entire Star Field would be sensationalized. By then, if he fought Black Star, no one would have a problem with that.

I won’t bully you when you’re weak. I will wait till you reach my level, then kill you!

Domineering as usual!

This way, the influence that he would gain would be much bigger. Black Star’s death would once again bring glory to the title Tyrant’.

"Understood, I will let everyone know your intention." Jorde’s voice became louder as he was conquered by Heber’s personality.

Although, from the way Jorde saw it, letting Black Star grow was not a wise choice.

But…

It’s so domineering!

He had absolute confidence in Heber. Even if Black Star became a Beyond Grade A, he would still be no match for Tyrant.

His Excellency Heber’s perspective on the issue is on a different level. He saw a greater opportunity while my vision was limited by this war. I’m too petty.

"Black Star became stronger again."

In the Floating Dragon palace, Aesop was looking at the news. He sighed and looked at Ames, who was sitting on the hovering throne.

"I still underestimated him. Back then, I wanted Black Star to be your right-hand man. I never thought that he would grow this fast. Sooner or later, he will request to leave Floating Dragon."

Ames was silent. She wanted Han Xiao to become stronger, but she did not want Han Xiao to leave her side.

Aesop sighed and said, "He has done a lot for Floating Dragon, but I have seen many Beyond Grade As before. Other than those raised by the three Universal Civilizations, no one is willing to be under someone else. I know that he’s important to you, but the Shattered Star Ring is very big. He won’t be your subordinate forever."

"He won’t be able to leave," Ames said coldly.

Aesop frowned. "Don’t be willful. No matter what, Black Star is your friend. With this relationship, the two of you will definitely be allies. There’s no need to create a conflict…"

"I said, he won’t be able to leave!"

Ames raised her voice and interrupted Aesop before lowering her gaze.

"Unless I can’t stop him."

Chapter 687: DarkStar Leader and the Fallen Ark

Black Star Base No.1’s military factory was so large that the end of it was out of sight. Countless assembly lines operated every hour of the day. Mechanical parts were assembled into all kinds of equipment by countless mechanical arms. Several Mechanics walked in between the assembly lines, debugging them from time to time.

The top of the factory was the main control room that could look over the entire factory. Decks of blueprints were spread on the alloy table near the window of the main control room, flipped by a person’s hand.

Reynold sat upright beside the table, reading through the blueprints with a serious expression.

This time, the door of the main control room was shoved open, and Sylvia ran in with joy all over her face.

"Hey, I have good news!"

Reynold slowly moved his eyes from the blueprints and looked at Sylvia.

"Big sis, please do tell," he said with a serious face.

Sylvia was already used to Reynold’s personality and had learned to selectively ignore parts of it. She raised her hand, and a ball of flickering Mechanical Force appeared in her palm.

"Hehe, I’m Grade B now. Aren’t I amazing?" Sylvia said with an excited expression.

"Amazing," Reynold said with an upward tone and a poker face. He even raised his hands and clapped.

Seeing this, Sylvia felt awkward. She felt like something that she was proud of might not be worth mentioning in the eyes of a Calamity Grade.

But she could not resist sharing her joy. Han Xiao had taken the old officers out to war, so the one that was closest to her among the remaining people was only Reynold, who oversaw the logistics. Usually, she would ask Reynold any questions she had. Although Reynold was nominally her junior, he was actually considered Han Xiao’s teaching assistant.

Sylvia could not suppress her excitement of entering Grade B and became happy again after feeling awkward for a while. With aspiration on her face, she said, "Teacher will definitely be very happy when he hears about this. He’s always had high hopes for me…"

Most importantly, Han Xiao had promised her that if she could become a Grade B Super, she would be able to focus on combat in the future and not do homework every day.

I’m free!

I, Sylvia, am happy!

After enjoying being happy for a while, Sylvia realized that Reynold did not say anything. She looked up and realized that although Reynold was facing her, his eyes were secretly looking sideways at the blueprints on the table.

Is talking to me this boring? Sylvia snapped her fingers, put on an angry expression, and said, "Stop looking away. I’m talking to you!"

Reynold looked back and said with a serious expression as if nothing had happened, "Hmm, you’re right."

Wow, what a perfunctory response… Sylvia clenched her teeth, took a deep breath, and calmed her emotions. She then took out the communicator and said, "By the way, Teacher did something great recently again. Look, people all over the Star Field are discussing him on all platforms. They all say he has the highest chance to become the next Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring. Tsk tsk, I never thought that Teacher is this amazing. If he really becomes a Beyond Grade A, as his disciple, maybe we…"

With a pause, Sylvia suddenly realized that Reynold did not react again. She looked up and saw that Reynold was looking at the blueprints on the table once again.

"Still looking?"

Sylvia was embarrassed and irritated. She snapped her finger again louder.

Am I, such a beautiful lady, not even as attractive as those boring blueprints?

"No, I’m listening." Reynold coughed. He took the communicator from Sylvia’s hand and looked at the news on it. His face turned serious again, and he muttered, "Black Star… Beyond Grade A seed…"

Seeing that Reynold was finally not looking at the blueprints, a smug expression appeared on Sylvia’s delicate and exquisite face.

As Han Xiao’s secretary, she knew that Reynold’s contract duration was about to end. For the Black Star Army, she felt that she had to make Reynold stay.

According to her knowledge of Reynold, this person’s desire to learn exceeded even his physiological desires. Sylvia felt that the best way to make him stay was to keep reminding him that her teacher had become stronger and stronger, showing him how outstanding her teacher was. That way, Reynold might choose to stay and continue following Black Star to learn and work for the army.

Although Sylvia did not really want to share her teacher with Reynold, for the sake of the army… she decided to sacrifice that.

"Beyond Grade A… Beyond Grade A…" Reynold muttered. Usually, he always looked serious and formal, but now, he looked like he had something heavy on his mind. "Black Star… Black Star can solve this once and for all…"

"What?" Sylvia did not understand what he

meant.

"Nothing."

Reynold returned to being serious.

At the same time in the training camp of Black Star Base No.1, Brock put down the communicator that was playing the news. He wanted to pick up the wine cup and drink it to suppress his fear but realized that his hand was shaking

He was a DarkStar remnant. After the DarkStar leader went missing, he had kept his mission in mind and believed that the leader would definitely return. Hence, he had joined and infiltrated the Black Star Army, hoping to one day become an important chess piece for the leader. He was now acting as the drill sergeant in the base.

For the past couple of years, Brock had been working in fear, not daring to do anything out of the line, and carefully disguised his identity, afraid of being suspected by anyone. His trust for the DarkStar leader was what kept him going

However, when he saw the news of Han Xiao becoming a Beyond Grade A seed, Brock realized that his belief was shaken.

He could not help but doubt… if the leader would really be a match for Black Star. Would he really be able to complete his revenge?

Would it not most likely be suicide?

If so, him staying in the Black Star Army as a spy might be pushing the leader into the pit of fire.

Brock was perturbed. Black Star’s overwhelming strength made him despair. He almost could not even think about resisting.

He secretly made up his mind. If the leader one day returned and he was able to get in contact with him, he had to convince the leader not to mess with Black Star. It would be more difficult than messing with Godora!

On a devastated civilization planet in a certain Star Field…

The planet’s surface was burning with endless flames and smoke, the ground shattered, the cities were destroyed, and countless were slaughtered.

The fleet that completed its invasion retracted their artillery barrels, slowly rising above the atmosphere, leaving the almost completely destroyed planet surface civilization.

This invading fleet was made up of three thousand battleships.

However, not far from the planet, an enormous fleet a thousand times bigger was docked. The battleships seemed endless, as if they filled up the entire galaxy. The three thousand battleships were just a small division of this enormous fleet.

A fleet of such a size could even fight a Star Cluster Civilization directly.

The three thousand battleships returned to the large army with their loot, like a droplet of water entering the ocean.

The leading disk-shaped battleship of this team deviated from the others and gradually entered deeper into the army, arriving at the center of this enormous fleet.

At the center of the fleet was a gigantic planet-level main ship. Comparatively, the disk-shaped spaceship was like a pebble, and this gigantic main ship was like a mountain.

A conspicuous sign was painted on the exterior armor of the main ship-a gray, hooded man.

The disk spaceship entered the dock of the main ship, flew down the long lane, and stopped at the hangar.

Whoosh!

The hatch opened, and the DarkStar leader walked out. With emotionless eyes, he turned around and waved, signaling for the subordinates behind him to bring the dozens of weak captives and follow him.

After walking for a while, they arrived before an enormous alloy gate. The giant cyclops guard beside the gate saw the dozens of the captives behind the DarkStar leader and grinned.

"You’re quite fast. Go in, he’s waiting for you."

As he spoke, the alloy gate slowly opened. The DarkStar leader focused his mind, led the others, and walked in. The view before his eyes turned bright. Noises and heat waves landed right on his face.

This was an enormous palace that was now having a party. There were countless tables filled with the delicious food and alcohol of many races, and there were people everywhere. Countless creatures from different races were gulping down the meat and drinks, roaring and laughing loudly. There were also female dancers walking through the crowd, roughly groped by people from time to time.

The DarkStar leader even saw that there was someone in the corner hugging a dancer and bumping her against the wall, his laughing and roaring mixed into the noises.

Chaos filled the entire room. Despite having lived there for a few years, the DarkStar leader still could not help but frown, not used to this stimulating scene.

A drunk Beastman stumbled over. The DarkStar pressed him on the shoulder and pushed him away. He then walked to the center of the palace with large steps. At the center was a scarlet throne carved into the shape of some strange creature, like an ancient god he did not know the name of, which some Arcane Church branches prayed to.

On the throne was a skinny, boney human-shaped creature wearing a ragged hood. Other than his face, his body was covered tightly. He was facing down, not making a single sound. The hood covered his face.

The DarkStar leader came before the throne. Ignoring the chaotic scene around and the noises, he pointed at the dozens of captives behind him that were stunned by what they were seeing. "Your Excellency, I’ve brought the Espers."

Suddenly, the creature on the throne shivered, as if he had awoken from his sleep. He slowly looked up, showing his face under the hood.

Under the hood was a vortex-like black fog, with a red flickering dot of light in the middle.

With an unknown method, this faceless creature somehow spoke. His voice was rough and husky. "Well… done…"

As he was speaking, he suddenly twisted his neck. The black fog under the hood suddenly disappeared, turning into the face of a hybrid human without any special features.

The hooded man stood up and walked down from the throne and toward the dozens of captives. The DarkStar leader stepped aside.

He stood in front of the first captive, looked right into the horrified eyes of this captive, grinned, and grabbed the neck of this captive.

The next moment, this captive’s entire body shrunk and became dry, yet he did not die. He collapsed to the ground with his eyes opened wide, not even having the energy to speak a single word.

"Not bad."

The hooded man licked his lips as if he was enjoying the taste. Then, he did the same and turned all the captives into dried shells before returning to the throne. He looked at the DarkStar leader with a satisfied expression

"You’re good. I like you."

"It’s my honor to serve you." The DarkStar lowered his head with respect. "According to our agreement, for every satisfying Esper I bring, you…"

The hooded man waved his hand and interrupted the DarkStar leader. "I know, I will give you a new fleet. Hmm, I have some information here. Maybe you’ll be interested."

The hooded man shook his hand. A communicator flowed out from his palm and landed in the DarkStar leader’s hands.

The DarkStar leader opened and looked at it. His expression instantly changed. The rumors surrounding Han Xiao were playing on it.

"He seems to be what made you escape from the Shattered Star Ring." The hooded man smiled faintly. "Looks like he can become a Beyond Grade A."

The DarkStar’s face was grave. He took a deep breath and slowly said, "Thank you for this information."

"You’re welcome." The hooded man smiled and spoke in a rather friendly tone. He then waved and said, "You can leave now. Such a good environment is rare. Don’t disturb my sleep."

"Yes." The DarkStar nodded and led his subordinates. He did not care about the dozens of dried captives. The chefs would come to cook them later anyway.

Walking out of the palace, the alloy gate slowly closed. The DarkStar looked back. Through the gap in the gate, he saw the hooded man lower his head and enter into sweet dreams in the chaotic, loud, and insane environment.

"What a maniac."

The DarkStar leader clenched his fists, and a deep sense of fear flashed through his eyes.

The people behind him had arranged for him to leave the Shattered Star Ring and join under this hooded man. This man was the master of this enormous fleet and also a horrifying Beyond Grade A Super who wanted to fuse the abilities on the Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty together.

Following the agreement, the DarkStar had given the hooded man Ember. He could still remember the look of disbelief and shock on Ember’s face when he realized that he had been betrayed.

However, his resistance was futile. The hooded man had been very satisfied with the sacrifice, so he had made an agreement with the DarkStar leader-he could provide fleets for the DarkStar leader, but the DarkStar leader had to exchange them for Espers that could satisfy him.

Therefore, the DarkStar leader stayed there temporarily. He invaded and destroyed one surface civilization after another, searching for Supers with interesting Esper abilities. After a few years, he had obtained a large number of battleships and men.

Originally, the DarkStar leader wanted to continue building his forces. However, Han Xiao’s rocketing combat capability gave him pressure.

Following the current pace, Black Star might really become a Beyond Grade A Super. Then, it would be useless for him to return. If there was a Beyond Grade A in the Garton Star System, no one would be able to cause any trouble. DarkStar would never have a chance to rise again.

"I have to go back as soon as possible, otherwise everything will be too late."

The DarkStar leader made his decision. Black Star happened to be at war, so he could take advantage of that.

Furthermore, the DarkStar leader did not dare stay there any longer. In just a few years, he had been deeply affected by the chaos there. He could not imagine what would happen if he continued to stay, whether he would become just as insane.

This enormous fleet was a Beyond Grade A organization that was always relocating and moving. The hooded man was the leader of this organization. Among all the Beyond Grade As in the entire universe, he was the most notorious maniac!

This place welcomed wanted criminals from every Star Field who had no way out. It was the holy land for all criminals.

This was the… (Fallen Ark]!

Aroshia had followed Han Xiao to the war as well. She was staying in the fleet and slacking off like Han Xiao.

Inside a room with turned off lights, Aroshia hugged her knees, sat in a corner, and stared into the darkness in front of her blankly.

This time, dots of light debris suddenly appeared out of thin air and formed into the bright shape of a man, lighting up the room. It was Risda.

"It’s you." Aroshia had no expression on her face.

Risda’s body vibrated. He then spoke.

"Great, if Black Star becomes a Beyond Grade A, he will be able to fight the Mechanic Empire. Our people might be saved."

"Oh." Aroshia did not respond too passionately

"But Black Star might not be willing to fight the Mechanic Empire. You and I must convince him. He’s our biggest hope," Risda said.

Aroshia kept silent for a while before suddenly asking, "He might die, right?"

"Everything is possible; nothing is absolute." Risda shook his head and avoided the topic. "Remember what I said."

Then, Risda disappeared, and the room returned to darkness.

Aroshia buried her chin between her knees and stared blankly.

Meanwhile, Lagi was still on the way there.

Chapter 688: Leeks Coming from Everywhere! (1)

Half a month had passed since the battle that destroyed the hyperdrive base station. The Bloodshed Land seemed to be cautious as well, so there were no major conflicts between the two sides for the time being, just skirmishes. Purple Crystal had no new missions for Han Xiao, so he took his fleet around in standby.

During this time, he had been studying his loot —the armed satellite fortress.

There was a total of nine armed satellite fortresses. After the base station was destroyed, the other armed satellite fortresses had all been seized. Han Xiao had received one from Morred too, and he had taken it back for research purposes.

The blueprints for this kind of large mechanical satellite were very valuable. This one’s model was [‘Stout Shield’ Military Satellite Fortress].

Han Xiao had been slowly deriving its blueprint over the past half a month. While he lacked the necessary Cutting-Edge Knowledge, which made it impossible for him to get the complete blueprint, he did obtain some useful technology such as the shield generator used by the hyperdrive base station, which could also be applied to psionic shields.

Although he could not build the full version of the armed satellite fortress, the Great Mechanic Han was able to fuse a blueprint of the shrunk version of it. While it was smaller in size, it had the same functions as the original, just not as powerful.

The armed satellite fortress was basically strategic equipment, not a combat weapon between Supers. Han Xiao planned to turn some of the Black Star bases built on administrative planets into satellite fortresses, at least giving them a certain amount of maneuverability.

Han also seized the special armor of Bloodshed Land’s elite soldier, Thousand Beast Soldier, which he turned into his own blueprint and made preliminary improvements.

In the machinery modification room. Han Xiao stood in front of a row of cabinets, looking at the different types of mechanical suits inside.

"Thousand Beast Soldier Armor, Sunil NCO Class armor and Commander Class armor, my Snake Series armors, and some standard mechanical suit blueprints… If I combine them together, I should get some high-quality, mid-level mechanical suit blueprints."

Han Xiao caressed his chin and pondered.

He intended to build a special armor series for the Black Star Army to be used as the new standard equipment for the army.

This was not an out of the blue idea but something that he had thought about for a long time.

Due to his two astonishing feats, his fame across the entire Star Field was rocketing beyond his expectations. Initially, Han Xiao had thought that the Black Star Army would only be able to develop slowly and steadily since the players were not there, but wars were proven to have the biggest opportunities once again. The recent heated discussion about him becoming a Beyond Grade A seed made him notice that this was a great opportunity. Some development targets could now be moved forward.

He had always wanted to improve the army from a mercenary group to an armed force like the Bloodshed Land. A set of armor belonging to his own faction was equivalent to uniform seduc… culture, which would help to increase the cohesion of the faction more effectively than a mere army symbol.

However, most of the people who came to be mercenaries were free and loose. If he forced a business transformation, he would lose some of those who were unwilling to pledge their loyalty. After all, mercenaries were never worried about where to go next, so they would not easily pledge their loyalty to a mercenary group.

Nonetheless, his recent achievements had made people believe that he had an extremely high chance of reaching Beyond Grade A. The upper limits of an armed force depended on the strength of the leader. The cohesion of a normal Calamity Grade organization could not even be compared with a Beyond Grade A seed organization.

For example, the Bloodshed Land, assuming that it had grown to its present size without Tyrant, would definitely have a ton of problems. Internally, the authority would be held by several Calamity Grades, none satisfied by being on the same level as the others, thus causing internal disputes and factional conflicts. Externally, without a Beyond Grade A leader, despite being such an enormous organization, no one would be able to unite them. In the end, they would definitely go their separate ways.

Therefore, a leader who could suppress everything within determined the upper limits of an armed force.

Han Xiao had been in the center of attention recently, and his reputation had exceeded the normal Calamity Grade range. Through his contacts, he learned that many intelligence organizations even called him half a Beyond Grade A. Numerous organizations believed that he would become a Beyond Grade A. Those organizations were not blind; his combat record was hard proof, so no one would inexplicably underestimate him.

As the faction leader’s position increased, the Black Star Army’s appeal transformed as well. Even mercenaries knew that following a possible Beyond Grade A would be a more promising future, so the number of people lost in the business transformation would be significantly reduced.

Not only that, with his current position, he could even attract more new talents.

"Because of my reputation, the Black Star Army’s influence is growing every day. This is a great opportunity to scale up."

Han Xiao was in a great mood. He had initially intended to develop his forces through the support from the Purple Crystal civilization, but to his surprise, his own fame seemed to have allowed him to exceed what he had planned to achieve for the organization during the update period.

Strength was the most important!

"This expansion is an opportunity to improve the Black Star Army. There are many goals to be accomplished. First, the business transformation. Second, the expansion of manpower. Third, the increase of the armed troops. Fourth, becoming a long-term partner of Purple Crystal… Hmm, as long as the first three are completed, the fourth goal should not be a problem.

"Of course, the most important thing is my own strength. When I’m done with these trivial problems, I have to take a period of time to get a silver legacy blueprint to complete the Class Advancement mission. After that, complete the level 200 Promotion as soon as possible. The stronger I am, the faster the army will develop."

Han Xiao pondered and quickly set out a list of goals.

He did not expect to perform this well before the war, nor did he expect to spark such discussions. The way he saw it, the development plan that he had originally set was too conservative.

This wave of discussions surrounding him was an extremely rare opportunity that he had to take.

Dong! Dong!

At that time, someone suddenly banged loudly on the door of the modification room.

"Who is it?" Han Xiao regained focus and opened the door.

Hairy, muscular abs entered his vision. Han Xiao looked up at the three-meter-tall Harmon standing outside the door.

"Lagi’s back. He wants to see you," Harmon said with a low and muffled voice.

"Oh, I thought he’d throw me an excuse that the hyperdrive engine broke and drag his feet till the end of the war to return." Han Xiao was surprised.

Harmon scratched his hairy head and gave a long grunt, as if the muscles in his brain could not process the meaning of the sentence.

"By the way…" Han Xiao suddenly remembered something. "How come you are the one reporting? Where’s Herlous?"

Usually, if Sylvia was away, Herlous would be his male secretary, a more decisive, reliable adult male.

"He asked me to lie to you that he was training," Harmon said with a straight tone, giving off a strong vibe of the word ‘reckless’.

"Hmm…" Han Xiao’s mouth twitched, and he did not know what to say. "Then, what is he actually doing?"

"He’s playing cards."

Han Xiao was speechless.

"Okay, got it. I’ll go to see Lagi now."

Han Xiao closed his door and walked for a while before recalling something. He turned to Harmon and asked, "By the way, how many years till the selection battle for your tribal chief?

Harmon was one of the heirs of the Luhan Beastman Civilization’s Rockfall Tribe. The side mission from him was to join his War League and help him become the chief.

If he remembered correctly, this should be a Version 3.0 side mission, but in case the storyline had changed, Han Xiao decided to ask again.

Harmon counted with his fingers for a while and said with a hesitant tone, "I think eleven years less three days."

The average life expectancy of the Luhan Beastmen was about 250 years, which was quite long. The selection of chief was a major event, it usually gave more than ten years to the candidates for them to form their War Leagues. This was because one selection often determined the chief for the next two hundred years.

"It’s a good thing you have comrades," Han Xiao said with resignation, "otherwise I suspect you’d miss the selection battle and lose your position as an heir…"

Harmon opened his eyes wide and blew his lower lip unhappily, his thick lips shaking.

Han Xiao went straight to the bridge and immediately saw Lagi, who had been waiting for a long time. He smiled and walked forward, patting Lagi on the shoulder.

"You’re back."

"Yes, I didn’t die on the way," Lagi murmured. "I think it took all the luck I have in my life."

Han Xiao’s smile stiffened. You’re too pessimistic!

"Ahem, do you remember what I said before you left?" Han Xiao said with resignation.

"Yes." Lagi nodded and said, "You said you were going to cancel my workload and give me a raise."

"No, I didn’t. Don’t bullsh\*t!" Han Xiao clenched his teeth. "I said when you get back, you’ll be my vice captain!"

"Oh, then I remembered wrongly." Lagi’s kept a straight face.

"Are you sure?" Han Xiao was suspicious. Why do I feel like you did that on purpose?

Hearing Han Xiao’s doubt, Lagi’s face became upset as he muttered, "You don’t trust me… Sigh, I should have known. People like me have no credibility."

"Enough, you," Han Xiao said with resignation. "Since you don’t have any objection, I’ll announce to the whole army that you’re the first vice-captain. By the way, I’m also planning to announce your past. You were once the Hidden Red Robe Abbey’s Forbidden Sorcerers’ commander. This past will increase your reputation, and no one will be unhappy about you becoming the vice-captain. Do you have any questions?"

Lagi nodded. He had no objections, but he did emphasize one point. "Don’t forget, you promised that my vice-captain position is just a title, and my workload won’t increase."

Don’t you f\*cking remember that crystal clear?

The appointment of the vice-captain was quickly transmitted to the communicators of the hundreds of thousands of official members of the Black Star Army.

When opening the Black Star Army’s mercenary group resume, under the ‘leader’ column, the vice-captain position that had always been empty finally had a first name written in it—Lagi Schwer.

Lagi had only joined for a very short time, so there was still a huge number of mid- to low-level mercenary members within the army that did not know him. With curiosity, confusion, surprise, and so on, they opened Lagi’s resume and were immediately shocked.

Not only was this newly appointed vice captain a Grade A+ Super, he was also the Hidden Red Robe Abbey’s Forbidden Sorcerers former commander, as well as the fourth disciple of ‘Magus’ Austin!

Lagi’s past was very impressive. Few outsiders knew about what had happened between Lagi and Austin; to many, this was a core member of a Beyond Grade A organization leaving and joining the Black Star Army!

Han Xiao was at the height of his popularity, so his every action attracted attention from countless people. Not only the army members, the various organizations that were paying attention to him were also shocked.

One of the Magus’ core members is now the vice-captain of the Black Star Army. Are they now working together?

The perception of the Black Star Army had subtly changed for countless people, including its members. Black Star’s recent achievements and the Black Star Army’s expansion seemed to show an inexorable rise.

As many people could see, Black Star wanted to use his soaring influence to benefit the Black Star Army, intending to become a Star Field level VIP!

The question that followed suddenly sparked interest from all sides.

What would Floating Dragon do if Black Star rose?

After all, the Black Star Army was nominally Floating Dragon’s field team. Now that Black Star showed Beyond Grade A potential, if he did deliver on that potential, would he continue to stay under Ames given the amount of ambition that he had shown?

While it was still unclear whether Black Star would become a Beyond Grade A, ambitions were not easy to erase. Black Star’s soaring position would change the way he thought sooner or later, inflating his ambitions.

Countless people were excited when thinking about the possibilities of the future.

If the announcement of the vice-captain drew attention, Han Xiao’s subsequent announcement triggered an earthquake.

The Black Star Army publicly issued a large-scale recruitment order to the entire Shattered Star Ring!

Han Xiao planned to tap into the ‘Beyond Grade A seed’ title to attract a large number of talents.

He believed that there were plenty of people willing to bet that he would become a Beyond Grade A.

Joining at this time would be more valued than joining a Beyond Grade A organization, it was equivalent to becoming a partner at the start of a business. Even if they lost the bet, it would only cost them time, so the loss would be within an acceptable range.

It was a huge gamble!

As the Black Star Army made the announcement, countless people and organizations across the ten or so Star Clusters in the Shattered Star Ring were tempted.

Chapter 689: Leeks Coming from Everywhere! (2)

The moment the recruitment order from the Black Star Army was sent out, practically half the star field exploded from excitement, and all the responders began to gather!

In just ten days, Phillip had already received countless resumes from various sectors of the Shattered Star Ring.

Riding on this wave of heated public opinion, the number of applicants was far greater than any of their previous recruitments. The target was not just toward original mercenaries. As long as one did not have a ‘Wanted’ tag on them, everyone would be treated equally.

Philip first eliminated the weaker candidates and did a screening of the first batch of top-rated talents. Just these people already totaled 1.4 million, more than the total count of the Black Star Army. This would effectively double the official staff of the Black Star Army a few times over!

More than a million people had already been selected, and this was not even the final result. Han Xiao was prepared to open the floodgates fully instead of restricting entry this time. With his fame and reputation, he already possessed the qualifications to form a large organization. This time, he was making full use of the opportunity.

Now was not the time to consider if over-recruiting would cause them to be able to absorb the members properly. This recruitment was not just targeted toward talents but also a way to show his influence. The more sensational this response was, the higher the position of the Black Star Army in the entire Star Field. If one combined the results of the recruitment with his current fame, he would be able to engrave his existence into the hearts of countless influences around, ascending to the top in one step and becoming a famous force in the Shattered Star Ring!

Compared to the other large organizations, the Black Star Army, while huge in scale, lacked reputation and influence. However, this did not prevent the popularity of their faction from rising. This was of great benefit to their future development, so from Han Xiao’s perspective, the storm of public opinion was perfectly utilized.

Most of the recruited talents in the first batch had some sort of fame in their respective sectors. At least sixty percent were also battle-hardened elite interstellar warriors as well, with the lowest being at Grade C. While the number of Supers was small, if one cast their eyes across the entire Star Field, the total sum was still exaggeratedly huge.

Recently, the secret war had begun turning into a full-fledged tug of war. There were no signs of activity on both sides, and there was free time to deal with his own internal affairs. Purple Crystal attached great importance to Han Xiao’s potential and was glad to see the Black Star Army develop itself. Furthermore, this indirectly meant a supplement to Section Zero.

More than a million of the newcomers then travelled thousands of miles from various star clusters to the Garton Star System, going through the procedures at the Black Star Army Base. Han Xiao also returned to his own base to deal with the various issues caused by the huge swelling in his faction.

In the reception room of the Black Star Army Headquarters, Sylvia brought in three new recruits of different races and appearances, and Han Xiao stood up from the sofa to greet them.

"Your Excellency, Black Star." The three of them had respectful attitudes and stepped forward quickly to exchange handshakes with Han Xiao.

"Come, sit."

Han Xiao waved his hand, and they all took their seats, beginning to chat.

With millions of newcomers, Han Xiao had no time to meet up with them individually. The reason he was meeting with these three was because the new recruits were actually all at the Calamity Grade!

A Calamity Grade Super would never submit to another easily. Before he became known as a potential Beyond Grade A seedling, Han Xiao had tried many times to recruit a Calamity Grade, but other than Lagi, everyone else had rejected him.

However, his status today was greatly different when compared to that of the past. Being a highly anticipated Beyond Grade A seed was enough to make some of the Calamity Grades stop hesitating and run under his banner. If their bet paid off, they would then become the backbone of a Beyond Grade A organization!

If one likened the Beyond Grade A to an Emperor ascending to the throne, they would be the dragons that became his officialsbright futures awaited them!

It was a pity that Ames was too much of a slacker. Even if she was a bona fide Beyond Grade A, her attraction toward Supers might not exceed that of Han Xiao’s. Not many Supers would deign to follow a leader without any ambition. Furthermore, Ames could not even be bothered to actively recruit Officers.

Those three Calamity Grades were the cream of the crop among the leeks, probably considered leeks that had grown legs, running a thousand miles to deliver themselves to be harvested by him.

Status and strength went hand in hand, and the Calamity Grades in an organization were destined to be the upper echelons. That was the only reason they had come. After all, they could not be expected to climb slowly from the bottom like a Grade C Super, right? Thus, Han Xiao had to personally take a look at the three of them and use this opportunity to observe them.

Before meeting with them, Han Xiao had already flipped through their resumes.

Karmbe, Grade A Pugilist, male. Tall with extremely pale skin, he seemed to have the bloodline of the Blood Race. He used to be an external instructor in one of the Super institutions with a civilization in some Star System. He resigned later, walking through multiple galaxies and taking a lot of private employment.

Marian, Grade A Mechanical Pugilist, male. He was wrapped from head to toe in heavy, dark-gray armor and always wore a helmet, seldom revealing his face to others. He looked like some knight from a fantasy civilization, and the reason he had come over was the same as Reynold, because he looked up to Han Xiao as a Mechanic.

Misecech, Grade A Esper, male. His resume was clean. Other than him being a Calamity Grade, there was nothing worth noting. He had hung around with multiple mercenary groups but had not worked long. He was a typical spectator.

These people who took the initiative to sign up would not be very strong, but they were at least at the Calamity Grade. The Black Star Army had originally only had three Calamity Grades. With the addition of three more, this doubled the total number, raising the advanced combatants inside the army.

Thus, the Supers that took the opportunity to rush over were basically ‘career men’. They were accustomed to changing jobs and moved to wherever had some benefit. Naturally, they would not be loyal of this, Han Xiao was clear. He also did not hope for them to sell their lives to him. As long as they could complete the work based on their scope as Calamity Grades, that would be good.

After chatting with them for a while, both sides had observed enough by now. Han Xiao stood up and extended his hand, smiling. "Then, I’ll represent Black Star Army to welcome you three on board."

"That is our honor." Misecech immediately took the opportunity to speak first. Karmbe replied shortly after, and Marian nodded in silence.

"I’ll need some time to consider what roles to assign you. Don’t worry, I will not treat you badly."

"Haha, our requirements are not high." Misecech had a flattering smile.

After replying with some pleasantries, Han Xiao sent the trio off before asking Sylvia to take them through the formalities.

Han Xiao did not rest after but immediately entered another reception room.

There were tens of people within there waiting. The moment they saw Han Xiao, they immediately stood up, greeting him warmly.

"Everyone, please sit."

Han Xiao waved his hand, glancing at everyone present.

Within this reception room, everyone present were the emissaries of various civilizations from the Colton Star Cluster. They had come to seek cooperation of their own initiative.

Originally, the influence of the Black Star Army had been limited to the Garton Star System, but now, the other Star Systems around the Colton Star Cluster had started to notice the potential of Han Xiao, as well as the momentum of the Black Star Army’s development, thus coming to seek opportunities for development and mutual benefit.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I’m the emissary from the Black Raven Civilization. I hope that the Black Star Army will be able to establish a sub-base within the territory of our civilization. To this end, the Black Raven Civilization is willing to pay a cooperation fee each year, at the same time opening the internal resource trading channels. Furthermore, we’ll give the Black Star Army the mining rights for a sector."

"I’m the emissary from the Holy Stone Civilization. Our terms are the same as the Black Raven Civilization’s, but our cooperation fees can be raised further if needed."

"I am…"

Everyone introduced themselves one by one, giving their own prices just for Black Star to build a sub-base in their territories. This was akin to offering themselves up to aid Han Xiao in expanding his influence.

The Star System Civilizations could clearly see that Black Star had already been tied to the big boss of this Star Cluster. With him also having the hope of becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, the Black Star Army could very well turn out to be the Colton Star Cluster’s Beyond Grade A influence. Attracting him to their side early was naturally the most cost-effective scenario.

Right now, the base of the Black Star Army was situated within the Garton Star System. It was unknown just how many times Serbia the Fifth had woken up from his sleep due to laughing out in joy, as this implied that there would be a Beyond Grade A Super holding the fort in Godora in the future. The other star systems also wished to have the Black Star Army expand his organization into their territory, simply because of this same consideration.

As for those star systems that did not originally have this idea, after seeing all their competitors doing so, they decided that they could not sit still. Thus, over eighty percent of the civilizations in the entire Colton Star Cluster had sent their emissaries to this reception room.

After listening to everyone, Han Xiao nodded, his face remaining impassive, but his heart was secretly moved.

The conditions given by the various civilizations in the star systems were extremely rich. Leaving aside the cooperation funds and resource channels, the most profitable thing would be the large-scale mining rights of a resource planet.

A resource planet was different from a barren one. The former was chock full of resources, and all of such planets were recorded clearly, with only the region’s ruling civilization having the power to mine them on a large scale. If any external organizations tried to mine without receiving a permit, they would have to account to the civilization of that region or even be hunted down by their guards.

Every civilization would definitely pay close attention toward a resource planet. Even though the Star Cluster Civilizations had mining ships that were able to dissect an entire planet, they rarely used them as even these big shots paid much attention to sustainable development.

A barren star, however, allowed for private mining because the profit obtained from there could not be compared to that of a resource planet. The quality-price ratio was too low, so the civilizations found it a waste of their manpower and material resources, deigning to sell the mining rights to others instead. For those private mining companies, while the profits to be obtained were not high, the barren planets were rich in oil and water.

There would, however, be times when the private mining team struck gold. During their mining process, if they found out that the ‘barren planet’ was actually a hidden resource planet, the civilization would evaluate the total value of this resource planet before offering a bid to buy it back. In this area, the majority of the civilizations were honorable enough to not force the mining team to hand over the planet for free.

Han Xiao was still quite clear about these basic concepts. From his previous life, during the later versions, players could even purchase mining rights to the resource planets from civilizations.

With such a clear comparison, Han Xiao was acutely aware of the value of giving him the mining rights of a resource planet. This was equivalent to taking out a cake from the civilizations and cutting him a small slice. It could easily net him a profit in the region of billions of Enas!

This was fertile ground!

Tsk, I risked my life to earn that small amount of money. Any random mining operation on a resource planet would bring me back thousands of times more profit. Why am I still a mercenary? Han Xiao could not help but silently curse.

Indeed, the most profitable way of earning was to establish a civilization!

After settling his mind, Han Xiao put on a solemn expression as he said in a stately tone, "Everyone, you have shown me too much sincerity. To be honest, the terms and conditions you have given me are quite tempting. I’m very willing to cooperate with you, but my Black Star Army is currently in its recruitment phase. After this recruitment has ended, I’ll schedule time to visit your areas to build a base."

Hearing this, everyone agreed and began to chatter.

"No problem, we can wait."

"Of course, we understand. We can sign the contract first."

Han Xiao smiled. "Since no one has any objections, let’s fix it this way."

Everyone present handed in their contracts, and Han Xiao signed them with some emotions in his heart.

In the past, there had not been so many good opportunities available for him. However, opportunities were knocking constantly on his door. This led to Han Xiao recall the words that Aesop had once said to him.

As long as you surpass Grade A, many powers will immediately offer up benefits to you. You will rise to the heavens with a single step and be at the highest level of the dining table!

Right now, he had only revealed a chance of breaking through Grade A, but this sort of situation had already happened. It seemed as though the old man Aesop had not lied to him.

Having finalized this business, the emissaries all heaved sighs of relief. This time, they would be able to answer to their superiors.

After sending off this batch of satisfied emissaries, Han Xiao did not stop but instead approached yet another reception room. He still had matters to settle.

The impact of his expansion this time was too great, so he had to meet all kinds of leeks every day, to the point that he was so busy his feet did not have time to be fixed on the ground.

The large influx of people that he had caused had to be solved by him, even if he was crying internally from fatigue.

However, everything would lead to extremely rich rewards, making Han Xiao satisfied.

Opening the door of yet another reception room, the people within the room looked over and greeted him as they smiled.

The occupants there were people who were more familiar to him, the great figures around Shattered Star Ring. This included the leader of the Dark Underworld Army, Underworld Feather, the captain of the Sky Ring Army, Gureja, and a few other Army Commanders.

"Brothers, it’s been a long time." Han Xiao greeted them and curiously said, "You guys were being very secretive on the communicator. What happened for all of you to come look for me to speak face-to-face?"

The few army commanders exchanged glances before suddenly smiling.

The Sky Ring Army Commander Gureja stroked his steel- like bristly beard, winking as he spoke. "This time, we’re here to invite

you."

"Invite me for what?"

"As you already know, the situation in the Shattered Star Ring is currently quite turbulent. With opportunities everywhere, it’s hard for an organization to completely swallow all the opportunities alone. I’ve already discussed this with these few army commanders, and we’ve decided to integrate the entire Shattered Star Ring and establish a Mercenary League so that it is convenient for us to participate in various missions between the Star System Civilizations. In such troubled times, we need to combine forces and seize this opportunity!"

Without waiting for Han Xiao to speak, Underworld Feather, who was by the side, lazily interrupted, "Black Star, with you being so popular recently, how about you just come and lead our Shattered Star Ring Mercenary League as the leader? Anyway, you don’t seem to mind having a lot of things to do."

Gureja coughed and hurriedly added, "Her meaning is, since your current appeal is far greater than any of our Grade A Mercenary groups’, we came to you this time to recommend you to take the spot of leader and founder of the Mercenary League."

Han Xiao’s eyebrows jumped up, feeling a little surprised.

This was one of the branch storylines of Version 3.0—[Shattered Star Ring Mercenary League]. The major mercenary groups had joined forces to integrate the scattered mercenaries of the Shattered Star Ring, establishing a large-scale mercenary league. The league developed and became a huge faction later that was extremely popular with players.

He did not expect the captains of each mercenary group to plan to make him the head, so he ended up getting involved in the storyline this way.

"You guys are really…" Han Xiao’s mouth twitched, and he raised his thumb. "… SO smart and insightful!"

Chapter 690: Three Years

Gureja and the others got the answer that they wanted and were overjoyed. After finalizing the details, they left satisfied.

Walking out of the Black Star Army base, they turned around to look at the majestic base, and Gureja lamented, "Black Star stepped into the mercenary world less than ten years ago, but he already has such accomplishments under his belt. He is truly an amazing fellow."

Another person shook his head and sighed. "Every individual capable of becoming a beyond Grade A Super has their own legend behind them. They are not characters that we can understand."

"That’s right. He is no longer on the same level as us. Thankfully, we got to know him early," Gureja said with a complicated mood.

In one of the corridors of the Black Star Army headquarters, Herlous and the three Volga brothers were walking and chatting.

"Have you heard? Three Calamity Grade Supers have joined us. His Excellency Black Star personally met them. They will definitely take on important roles in the army in the future," the eldest Volga brother suddenly said.

"I know." Herlous nodded with both joy and depression.

He was happy about the high-speed development of the Black Star Army but depressed that his own status would be affected because of this.

With three Calamity Grade Supers joining the upper echelons of the army, the competition would definitely get more intense, and Herlous felt a great deal of pressure.

Strength represented authority, and he still had not touched the Grade A door yet. His importance to the army would only decrease as time went by. There were already many mid-level combatants in the Black Star Army. If not for the fact that he was the one who had followed Black Star the longest, he would not have the right to be part of the upper echelons with his Grade B strength.

Herlous already felt that he was growing rapidly, but he was not able to keep up with Han Xiao’s footsteps and the high-speed development of the Black Star Army. He did not wish to fall behind just like that and thus became extremely nervous.

In order to train his body, he halved the time that he spent playing cards… It would be impossible for him to stop playing cards. It would be impossible in this lifetime of his.

"The Calamity Grade truly seems so far away…"

Herlous let out a sigh.

The development of the Black Star Army made many of the old officers lament at the speed of their growth. However, the wheels of history would always continue to spin, and Han Xiao would not stop because of this.

Han Xiao spent a full seven days meeting all the emissaries from the various organizations and reorganized the structure of the expanded Black Star Army. Only then did he have some free time to himself.

Han Xiao locked himself up in his office and took out a piece of paper to summarize the benefits that he had received recently and made a new blueprint for development.

The rapid growth of the Black Star Army had exceeded his expectations, and the original development plan was no longer suitable. With many organizations and Star System Civilizations giving him the opportunity to expand, it would be a waste for Han Xiao not to make use of them. As long as he made good use of this opportunity, the development speed of the Black Star Army would be increased by ten if not a hundred times!

This was an enormous harvest!

Han Xiao began to organize which opportunity would be able to bring him the largest benefit and how much he needed to invest. He made a simple list for himself and began to analyze it.

At the same time, he also began to grade his faction based on the different grades of equipment. He had two different grading schemes. First, current size. Second, potential for development.

The evaluation of the current size of a faction was determined by the amount of resources, size, military strength, number of members, influence, and so on.

The evaluation of potential was determined by networks, allies, scope of operations, long term benefits, development opportunities, and the like.

Han Xiao chose an organization to be the benchmark for comparison. He rated the Bloodshed Land to be at the orange grade in terms of size and potential. With that as a reference, he began to analyze the Black Star Army.

"Not including the players, before this large expansion, the scale of the Black Star Army was limited to a few Star Systems. Our size was around the dark green or light blue grade. Currently, it should be at the light purple grade. When Phillip recruits the second and third wave, we should be at the purple grade."

Han Xiao mumbled to himself while spinning his pen.

"As for potential, the reputation of me being a beyond Grade A seed was an orange grade development opportunity. The secret war and setting up a bridge with the Purple Crystal Civilization are also orange grade. The contracts with the various Star System Civilizations are orange grade. Setting up the Mercenary Alliance is pink grade. Together with my own network and potential, the potential of the Black Star Army should be at the orange grade on average."

Han Xiao made a list on the piece of paper and nodded.

As long as he was able to realize the orange grade development potential, the Black Star Army would be able to quickly enter the level of a pink grade organization.

All the organizations of the pink grade were famous organizations on the Star Field level. While they were still a distance away from the Bloodshed Land, they were truly super-sized organizations.

Han Xiao began to make plans for the various opportunities of development.

"With so many Star System Civilizations inviting me to set up a branch, this is akin to expanding my territory. All the newly hired manpower can be put to use and sent to these new Star Systems to expand our scope of operations.

"I can let a portion of them pioneer the discovery of resource rich planets to resolve the problem of our organization’s transformation. Apart from employment missions and war duties, we can also obtain more revenue streams by mining for resources.

"Hmm, if the manpower isn’t sufficient, I can send the people from Planet Aquamarine to make up the numbers and allow a portion of them to become galactic residents. Furthermore, digging seems to be the specialty of those worms. With my reputation in the Black Spirit Race, I should be able to find a large number of elite laborers."

Han Xiao then put a tick behind the words ‘Star System Civilization’.

"Setting up a mercenary alliance within the Shattered Star Ring is also pretty simple. It will expand the scope of my operations and increase my influence. With the support of the other large armies, as long as I call for support, building the foundation of an alliance won’t be an issue. Everything else will just be a matter of time."

Han Xiao very quickly came up with the new blueprint for development.

Putting down his pen, a smile could be seen on Han Xiao’s face.

After memorizing what was written on the paper, Han Xiao reduced the paper to dust with a single snap of his finger.

"When Version 3.0 is released, the changes in the Black Star Army will probably shock the players."

…

The Black Star Army became bustling with activity, and after hiring a few waves of new members, the Black Star Army had almost ten million members. The majority of them were sent out to set up branches around the various Star Systems of the Colton Star Cluster, and the operations of the army expanded from the Garton Star System to half of the Star Cluster.

Han Xiao did not forget about the secret war, and after handling the expansion of the army, he went back to the battlefield and continued to fight.

After the commotion from his expansion subsided, the large wave of discussion about him being a beyond Grade A seed petered out. Han Xiao had already become the biggest winner, and the Black Star Army left a deep impression on the entire Star Field during this period. The fame of the Black Star Army had entered the ranks of the famous organizations within the Shattered Star Ring.

Under such circumstances, the Black Star Army was still the Floating Dragon Field Team in name. Floating Dragon remained silent throughout the entire matter, and with some people fanning the flames from behind the scenes, more and more people started to treat the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon as two separate organizations. At the same time, people began to discuss both parties splitting up.

The storm that Han Xiao had created had a long-lasting impact. More organizations began to participate in the secret war both openly and secretly, and the scope of the battle became larger and larger.

The secret war was a Main Storyline Mission in Version 3.0 (Crimson Tide). However, news of the secret war was overshadowed by the commotion that Han Xiao and the Black Star Army had created.

The war was still ongoing, and the Black Star Army continued to develop.

Three years passed in the blink of an eye.

Chapter 691: Successor

In Ames' palace, two people were standing outside the gate. One of them was Aesop, and behind him was a tall, purple-haired human lady. Her skin was a little blue, her face looked gentle and pretty, and she had alluring eyeshadow on. She was looking up at the palace apprehensively.

Aesop looked at the beautiful, purple-haired woman and said with resignation, "Vilna, don't be so nervous. It's just meeting Ames."

"I—It's my first time meeting a Beyond Grade A. What kind of person is Her Excellency Dragon Emperor? It's rumored that she's very controlling. Is that true?"

Vilna bit her lips and crossed her fingers nervously.

"Fake, of course! That's a rumor that only appeared in the last few years. It's to deliberately vilify Ames because Black Star… Sign, let's not talk about this."

Aesop seemed to have thought of something troubling. He shook his head and sighed.

"Anyway, Ames is very friendly. This is your first time meeting her since joining Floating Dragon, so leave a good impression, will you?"

"I—I'll try my best."

Vilna still did not have much confidence. She inhaled deeply and tried to calm her emotions.

After walking into the palace, Aesop got to know where Ames was by asking the guard. He took Vilna to an outdoor area. From afar, they could already hear the sound of energy clashing.

When they got closer, Vilna noticed two people fighting in this open area, and three people were watching from the side.

She looked at the fight, and her eyes were immediately caught by the two sides of the battle.

Ames was personally training Hila, flipping the light green force field barrier with her fingertips, spinning in midair. Her black dress was blossoming like a lotus, showing her long, snow-like legs from time to time.

Hila's face was cold. Her body was surrounded by thick dark red streams, and she kept attacking Ames' force field, making loud bangs.

Ames maintained the strength of her force field at the Grade B level. Still, she controlled it extremely accurately and completely overpowered Hila.

"Stop for a moment. Someone's here."

Ames suddenly stopped her Esper ability and slowly landed on the ground.

Hila glanced at Aesop and Vilna, slightly frowning, unhappy with how her spar had been interrupted. She deactivated her Esper ability as well, and the dark red energy surrounding her entered her body. Then, she followed behind Ames like Aurora, who had been watching from the side, sizing up Vilna.

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, I'm…" Vilna hastily wanted to introduce herself.

Ames raised her hand and said, "I know your name. Since you're Aesop's friend, stay around and see if there's anything you can do. I don't have any requirements here."

"O—Okay."

"You seem to be a little nervous." Ames slightly raised her eyebrow.

"Er… you're the first Beyond Grade A I've ever seen. I'm your idol… um, I mean, you're my admirer…" Vilna blushed and could not even speak properly.

"Don't be nervous. Beyond Grade A isn't a big deal. I don't bite." Ames smiled faintly and spoke with a gentle tone. She raised her hand and touched Vilna's cheek.

Feeling the touch of Ames' palm on her face, Vilna's body stiffened, and she did not know where to put her hands.

Aurora, who was at the side, pulled the hem of Hila's shirt and softly asked, "Sis, is this woman Floating Dragon's new officer?

"Yeah."

As usual, Hila spoke with very few words.

Aesop coughed and said, "We shall take our leave and not disturb you guys. I'll take her to get familiar with the job."

As he was speaking, he took Vilna away, who was still stunned, disappearing before the other three.

Ames' smile slowly faded. She looked in the direction that Vilna had left from and kept silent with complicated emotions in her eyes.

"I heard this new officer is someone Aesop called over from another Star Field. I wonder what she's doing here." Aurora was curious.

Hila pushed her red hair aside and said emotionlessly, "Aesop is training a new officer so that she can replace Han Xiao's position in the future."

"Han Xiao won't leave, right? Big Sis Ames is so good to him," Aurora said.

"Humph, there have been a lot of rumors in the past few years. Many people created rumors so that Han Xiao and Floating Dragon would be separated.

"Plus, don't I know him? If he really becomes a Beyond Grade A, he will definitely further strengthen the organization under his command. Because of that, he won't be able to continue using Floating Dragon's name, so he will definitely create one for himself."

Ames turned around and glanced at the two of them. "It's nothing worth chatting about. At least for now, he's still mine. Hila, continue to attack."

Three years had passed, and Ames was no longer troubled anymore. She was waiting for Han Xiao's choice.

The three of them stopped chatting and continued the combat training.

On the other side, Aesop took Vilna out of the palace.

This time, Vilna finally said with surprise, "The Dragon Emperor is so friendly. The rumors are not true at all."

Aesop shook his head with resignation.

Over the past three years, many people had been manipulating public opinion to vilify the Dragon Emperor, wanting to make Ames seem like someone who was very controlling and intimidating. Their goal was to split Black Star and the Dragon Emperor apart.

Throughout the last three years, Black Star's reputation had become more and more firm. The Black Star Army had also digested its rapidly expanding size and slowly stabilized. Its business range had already extended to most Star Systems in the Colton Star Cluster, becoming an enormous Star Cluster level organization.

Furthermore, the Black Star Army had officially become the Purple Crystal Civilization's long-term partner a year ago, receiving tons of support.

Nominally, the Black Star Army was expanding for Floating Dragon. However, Ames was completely uninvolved, clearly intending to just let things flow on their own. If a conflict could be created between the two of them, Black Star would definitely leave with the Black Star Army. If Black Star and Dragon Emperor became enemies because of that, it would be the best case.

The other Star Cluster civilizations and the various large organizations did not want to see two Beyond Grade As forming a union or alliance. It would only be balanced and aligned with the benefits of these organizations if the two of them were enemies and limited each other in various respects. Therefore, they did everything they could to spread rumors, believing that they would one day influence the mindset of the two of them.

Aesop trusted Han Xiao's potential fully, so he felt that Han Xiao would certainly leave Floating Dragon in the future. Hence, he decided to plan ahead.

As such, Aesop had found Vilna, a friend whom he had met in another Star Field. Despite having a rather soft and gentle personality, she was very reliable. He asked Vilna to come to the Shattered Star Ring and join under Dragon Emperor so that he could nurture Vilna to become Black Star's successor.

"You don't have to work on Floating Dragon Island. You're responsible for building a new Field Team. Quickly pack your things and let's get going," Aesop said.

Vilna nodded and curiously asked, "How do I start exactly?"

"You have to look for someone and express your intentions to him. He will provide help. Just follow his arrangements."

"Who do I have to look for?"

"Black Star."

Vilna's eyes opened wide. After coming to the Shattered Star Ring, she had immediately heard about the famous Black Star. Plus, he was her senior and currently the top officer of Floating Dragon.

"But I heard that our connection with Black Star only exists in name now. Are you sure he will help me?" Vilna was worried that Aesop was sending her into a wolf den.

"Stop talking about that, just a false rumor. Black Star is a core member of Floating Dragon. He will only help you, not hurt you," Aesop said with a heavy tone.

He deliberately sent Vilna to Black Star to let Han Xiao personally groom his successor. This was a signal of friendliness, expressing that they hoped things would end on peaceful terms.

He wanted Vilna to build a new Field Team to show that they had no desire for the Black Star Army. This way, he believed that Black Star would be willing to guide Vilna, use his Black Star Army to help Vilna develop, and give Floating Dragon a new Field Team.

Of course, if Black Star did not actually plan to leave, it would be even better. This would then just be expanding the size of Floating Dragon's Field Team.

"Understood."

Vilna nodded and could not help but be curious about Han Xiao. She wondered what kind of person this extremely famous senior of hers was.

At the same time, in the desolate region between the Seoul Star Cluster and the Colton Star Cluster, an intense war was underway.

The Klent Kingdom had built many logistics channels in the desolate region. Those were key facilities that Purple Crystal was always eager to destroy.

In the past three years, the situation of the secret war had been changing constantly. Finally, the battles in the West Wind, Kaya, and Chaida Star Systems had entered a stalemate. The Bloodshed Land had expanded to a certain extent and was finally stopped.

Han Xiao could demolish the majority of Calamity Grades. After suffering the huge loss of many more high-level combatants, the Bloodshed Land had learned their lesson and occasionally avoided direct contact.

The core members of the Bloodshed Land knew about the Tyrant's stance, so they took Black Star as a dangerous challenge to train themselves, treating him with extreme caution and not recklessly fighting him head-on. This led to fewer and fewer situations where Han Xiao was needed.

Letting him stay in Colton was a waste of talent. Thus, Purple Crystal had him lead a surprise attack team and move within the desolate region, searching for the Bloodshed Land's logistics transit stations and destroying them.

This operation had been going on for half a year. Han Xiao had been doing a great job, causing the Bloodshed Land's advantages to keep getting reduced, almost destroying all the transit stations.

At this time, he was leading his fleet to attack the last logistics transit station…

Chapter 692: Any Day That No One Attempts to Assassinate Me, I Feel Uncomfortable

Sylvia was wearing a light mechanical combat jacket and kept her shield constantly active. The suit's protection measure for her head was a semi-circular metal ring wrapped around the back of her head, fixed on her ears. Her face was protected by a semi-transparent arc-shaped shield, and in her hand was a silver alloy sword.

She was gasping for air like a wind box and felt that her lungs were about to start burning. The sweat all over her body made the mechanical combat jacket feel sticky and wet.

Roar!

A Thousand Beast Soldier suddenly dashed out from the side. Its huge mechanical metal claw slashed right down, vibrating at a high frequency.

Sylvia forced some energy out of her body, clenched her teeth, and raised her soft arm. The thin and tough silver alloy sword in her hands clashed with the claws, creating blinding sparkles.

Clank!

The swift yet strong mechanical combat jacket suddenly increased its power, and Sylvia suddenly became faster. She quickly changed her stance, spun her sword, and stabbed at the Thousand Beast Soldier from a tricky angle. Mechanical Force lightning appeared on the alloy sword for an instant, and a tint of yellow light circulated on the blade as it stabbed into the body of this Thousand Beast Soldier in an instant.

Bang!

A huge, yellow beam of light penetrated the Thousand Beast Soldier's body and shot out from its back, leaving a large bloody hole. The Thousand Beast Soldier was blasted away, fell onto the ground, and died. Around it were tons of Thousand Beast Soldier corpses and shattered artilleries.

This was the surface battlefield on one of the armed satellite fortresses of the Bloodshed Land's logistics transit station. A boarding team was difficultly moving toward the core energy furnace of this armed satellite fortress. Thousand Beast Soldiers came from all directions like waves, and the two sides fought intensely, leaving a path of corpses behind everywhere they went.

Sylvia had countless comrades around her. She was in the boarding team as well, responsible for one side of the team.

With the sword in her hands, she had been fighting for a long time. She could not even recall if she had killed a hundred or two hundred Thousand Beast Soldiers. Her combat jacket was damaged, and she was slightly injured. She was covered in sweat and exhausted.

Being on the battlefield, Sylvia could not hear any sound other than the explosions and roars. All she knew was that she had to follow the big team and keep marching forward, forward, and forward.

She looked up at the sky. Outside the armed satellite fortress was a magnificent galactic battle scene. Countless bright 'shooting stars' flew across the sky, braiding a net made of light. Those were the lights from countless ion cannons, illuminating the darkness and burning in silence.

Sylvia's vision was suddenly filled with a strong light. An ion cannon shot landed on the surface not far away, hitting the dense Thousand Beast Soldier army, blasting away a large number of people.

Boom!

The fleet could occasionally penetrate the protective shield of the satellite and provide supporting attacks, clearing the obstacles in the boarding team's path toward the energy furnace.

"That almost hit us." Fear lingered in Sylvia's heart. Before she could even catch her breath, several more light beams headed in her direction. She had no choice but to expand the shield on her arms and quickly block them.

Bang bang bang!

The beams shattered upon hitting the shield. Her arms withstood the impact. She felt a piercing pain in her arms and shoulders and could barely even move them. Sylvia clenched her teeth and endured the pain. There was only one thought on her mind.

I want to go back to studying!

At least my life wouldn't be in danger!

Three years ago, Sylvia had been able to reach Grade B. She had delightfully gone to tell Han Xiao the good news, and Han Xiao had been very glad. He had immediately thrown her into the advance team for real combat training.

At first, Sylvia had been rather happy, but now, she was full of regret.

That was especially so when the direct boss of the team was Lagi. Before every battle, Lagi would follow procedure and boost his subordinates' morale… and every time, it made her feel like she was definitely going to die.

At this time, a dark outline of a person suddenly flew in her direction from afar, landing heavily on the ground not far away. The huge impact created a dent on the metal ground like it was made of paper.

This person seemed to be rather hurt from the fall, only standing up and levitating after quite some time. He then turned to look at the boarding team which Sylvia was in.

Clearing seeing the look of this person, Sylvia felt her heart was half frozen. This person was the enemy Calamity Grade stationed at the logistics transit station. He was supposed to be fighting in outer space, but he had landed on the satellite surface, seemingly having been blown there.

The battlefield was constantly changing. The expressions on the people of the boarding team all suddenly changed as they immediately turned toward this new Calamity Grade enemy, preparing to guard against his attack. There were no Calamity Grades among them.

As everyone was getting extremely anxious, another meteor landed from the sky and heavily clashed into this Calamity Grade, pushing him dozens of miles away, creating a ring of sonic impact. The impact blew away the Thousand Beast Soldiers around, and the violent wind tipped Sylvia and the others off their balance.

"It's His Excellency Marian!"

"How timely! I almost thought we were going to die."

Sylvia heard the exclamations from behind. She regained balance and looked over. The 'meteor' that had blown the Calamity Grade enemy away was levitating. It was the Grade A Mechanical Pugilist that had joined the Black Star Army three years ago, Marian.

Marian was covered in a black Super heavy mechanical suit like a heavy armored knight. He turned and looked at the boarding team. He nodded to signal for the boarding team to continue going forward and not worry about anything else.

Then, he accelerated and disappeared, chasing the enemy Calamity Grade Super and focusing on his own opponent.

"I wonder how's the battle above going…"

Sylvia looked up at the sky again. Her vision seemed to be able to penetrate the darkness. She knew that her teacher was in the fleet overlooking the entire battle.

Meanwhile, Section Zero's fleet was attacking the logistics transit station aggressively, destroying the enemy battleships one after another.

Han Xiao was in the command room of the flagship, observing the real time battlefield projection, moving the troops, and overlooking the overall battle. A circle of staff sergeants stood around him.

Compared to three years ago, Han Xiao gave off a sturdier vibe. He had short hair, an angular face, and stubble on his chin. He wore a compressed orb necklace and a black windbreaker that could not cover his built body. The charm of a mature man was emanating from him, head to toe.

His current position was the top commander of this fleet.

This was a standard mixed team. Forty-five percent of the fleet belonged to Han Xiao, the largest force present. The rest were from a few other Section Zero members, all under Han Xiao's command.

Over the last three years, the Black Star Army had become the top member among Section Zero. A year ago, Purple Crystal had finally made the Black Star Army their long-term partner. The Black Star Army had then been the officially acknowledged leading organization of Section Zero. Therefore, Han Xiao had become the commander.

With Purple Crystal's arrangement, Han Xiao led this team that was responsible for destroying the Bloodshed Land's logistics transit station. He had been doing so for half a year.

As a commander, it meant that he could not easily join the attacks personally. Han Xiao no longer led the battle and let all his subordinates do their jobs. The new Grade A Supers that he had recruited three years ago were all very useful and reliable talents. This made up for the lack of high-level combatants under his command.

As long as they did not meet anyone whom they could not deal with, Han Xiao would not have to battle anyone personally.

He had to nurture his officers and give them opportunities to contribute. After all, if he attacked, his subordinates would have nothing to do.

At this time, a few staff sergeants were observing the battlefield projections and loudly discussing the battle.

"The enemies are still resisting and covering the logistics teams, trying to reduce their losses by transferring the resources in the transit station through stargates. If we don't stop them, the enemies will be able to retrieve most of their resources in about twenty-seven minutes and retreat through the stargate."

"Twenty-seven minutes? They can barely last ten more minutes. Their line of defense is already completely shattered."

"All we have to do now is destroy the stargate. That way, those enemies that have yet to retreat will be done for."

Listening to their discussion, Han Xiao caressed his stubble and did not say anything.

The logistics transit station's core facility was a stargate built by the Star Cluster civilization that led to the Seoul Star Cluster on the other side. The enemies had deployed protective shields and fleets to protect the stargate. When attacked, they retreated while guarding themselves.

As soon as the enemies retreat, Han Xiao would not be able to chase further. The other side of the stargate was the enemy's territory. If the stargate closed after they passed through, they would be heavily surrounded. Therefore, the victory condition was to destroy the stargate before the enemies successfully retreated.

The stargate was bidirectional, so the enemies' reinforcements could arrive through the stargate. The enemies would need time to gather reinforcements, so the attacking side had the upper hand. As long as they destroyed the stargate first, the battle would be decided.

The Black Star Army had received tons of resources over the past few years. Hence, Han Xiao had expanded his fleet, which was why the size of this expedition fleet was so huge. They demolished the defense team of the transit station. The battlefield projection showed that the enemies' line of defense had shattered, exposing the stargate.

A staff sergeant smiled and said, "The enemies have no chance. We've won."

As soon as he finished his sentence, the blue vortex at the center of the stargate rippled, spitting out one battleship after another. The Bloodshed Land's reinforcements had arrived and quickly joined the battleship, stopping the attack of Han Xiao's fleet.

Speechless, Han Xiao glanced at the staff sergeant that had spoken. That person coughed awkwardly, avoided Han Xiao's gaze, and stared at the battlefield projection, putting on a focused expression, as if saying, I'm analyzing the battlefield situation, don't disturb me.

"This is exactly why I don't like to talk when we have the upper hand." Han Xiao sighed.

The appearance of the enemy reinforcements caused chain reactions. On the other side, streams of light bolted over from the desolate region. An enormous armed fleet stopped at the edge of the battlefield, surrounding Han Xiao's fleet in the middle together with the reinforcements.

"An ambush‽" The expression on the officers' faces changed.

"Oh, it seems like this logistics transit station is a trap." Han Xiao raised his brows. He was calm and not at all surprised.

The battle had been going too smoothly, so he had noticed something wrong long ago. After so many logistics transit stations being destroyed by him, how could the Bloodshed Land not respond?

The battleship model of this ambush fleet was different from the Bloodshed Land—it belonged to another organization. Over the past three years, organizations that wanted him to die before he grew even stronger had joined forces with the Bloodshed Land secretly one after another, entering the secret war. Han Xiao had already met this kind of ambush set up more than ten times, so he was used to it. Any day that no one was attempting to assassinate him, he would feel that something was missing.

Beep beep!

This time, the flagship received a video message from the attacking fleet. A man with metallic skin appeared on the screen. He looked like his entire body was made of metal.

"Black Star, come and fight me!" he said with a strong desire to battle in his eyes.

"Tsk, this guy is here again." Han Xiao sighed.

This man was also a Beyond Grade A seed, Hadavy, a battle fanatic. One year prior, he had entered the secret war during a certain battle, specifically looking to fight with Han Xiao, then was defeated and escaped.

However, Hadavy did not give up. After escaping, he joined forces with the Bloodshed Land and used the chances during the war to keep fighting Han Xiao, treating Han Xiao as an opponent to better himself. He fought Han Xiao again and again, losing again and again. Furthermore, he escaped extremely fast when things were looking bad. In Han Xiao's eyes, he was basically a sh*t stirrer.

In the past three years, Han Xiao's network list had become longer, and his list of enemies had increased proportionally.

"I'll leave the commanding to you guys. I've got work to do."

Han Xiao casually stretched his neck with a calm face and walked toward the hatch with wide strides.

"Hopefully, they can give me some fun this time."

Chapter 693: Are You Eloping with Me‽

As the hatch opened, a strong vacuum suction force immediately stirred up a storm, wanting to drag him out of the spaceship.

Han Xiao activated the compressed orbs. Nanoparticles flowed out and covered his body like black sand, quickly transforming into the enhanced Mountain Ape mechanical suit.

He stretched his arms and legs before jumping out of the spaceship. The thruster sprayed out a blue flame as he turned into a meteoroid heading right to the back.

The expedition team was facing enemies from both the front and the back, fighting the Bloodshed Land reinforcements and the enemy ambush at the same time.

The assistant took over the job of the commander and ordered the ships at the back to fight against the ambush team while the ships at the front continued to attack the stargate. Destroying the stargate was still the key point of winning this battle.

Han Xiao’s goal was to deal with the high-level combatants of the enemy ambush. Through the repeated failures of attempted assassinations, he had proved how difficult that would be. Without a reliable strategy, the enemy would not have come to assassinate him. He wanted to see what new assassination scheme the enemies had prepared for him this time. He was even looking forward to it a little.

The galactic battlefield was filled with intersecting cannon shots everywhere. Han Xiao moved swiftly and dodged the attacks, arriving at the edge of the enemy ambush not long after. A stream of light flew over from within the enemies-it was Hadavy.

Hadavy was an old opponent who did not like talking. Not wanting to give Han Xiao any time to release his mechanical army, without saying a word, he dashed right toward Han Xiao like a mini meteoroid as soon as he saw him.

Han Xiao was not afraid of close-range combat. His arms turned into barrels and launched blue psionic rounds directly at Hadavy.

Hadavy did not even dodge and let the psionic cannon shots explode on his body. He was completely unharmed.

After fighting many times, Han Xiao knew Hadavy’s strength very well. He was not intending to damage him, just slow down Hadavy’s charge. Using this short amount of time, he activated the Army Boxes remotely. The space around him started to ripple, and Army Boxes arrived through hyperdrive one after another. The cases of those Army Boxes opened, and countless compressed orbs rapidly expanded into a machinery tide, almost filling up this small area in an instant.

The tightly packed mechanical army’s size had now reached three million!

In the past three years, the Black Star Army made a lot of money. Han Xiao had plenty of assets. He had enhanced and expanded his mechanical army multiple times. Currently, even the lowest level mechanical soldiers were made with high-level alloys, with much higher armor value and defenses compared to three years prior. As their basic attributes increased, the effects of the bonuses became more apparent.

Through many war missions, Han Xiao had obtained a lot of Purple Crystal Contribution Points and had received more Cutting-Edge Knowledges, one of them being the [Controllable Annihilation Weapons].

Annihilation weapons were a higher grade of regular weapons compared to energy weapons. As they used different technology, their destructive power was much greater than normal energy weapons. Furthermore, building them required knowing the [Abnormal State Energy] Cutting-Edge Knowledge, as psionic and antimatter energy were basically the only ones that could be used to build annihilation weapons.

With those two Cutting-Edge Knowledges, Han Xiao had switched most of the mechanical soldiers’ weapons into annihilation weapons. Together with (Legendary Battle Technique), their damage was significantly increased.

Even after three years, Han Xiao had yet to complete the Class Advancement mission. If this had happened to any other classes, their strength would be stuck. However, one of the Mechanic class’ advantages was that as long as he had money, even if his own strength was stuck, he would still be able to steadily increase his combat capability!

Han Xiao had never stopped building his mechanical army over the past three years. He realized that other than being rich, he also had another huge advantage-he had a lot more time than the players.

And the Mechanic class happened to be a class that required time to build all kinds of equipment.

With enough money and effort, increasing strength was as easy as drinking water for him. Of the five Super classes, only the Mage class could match up to the Mechanic in this respect.

With Han Xiao’s current strength, it was basically suicide for any normal Calamity Grade to fight him. After numerous failed assassination attempts with heavy repercussions, the various organizations of the Shattered Star Ring had finally learned their lessons. Those organizations that were secretly planning to assassinate him also stopped easily sending their high-level combatants to their deaths.

Therefore, Han Xiao was facing just Hadavy. This guy was a Beyond Grade A seed, which was not in the ‘normal Calamity Grade’ range. Furthermore, his abilities were the kind that gave Han Xiao a headache.

Hadavy was an Esper, and his Esper ability was Body Hardening. This was an Esper ability that could not have been more common. Yet, he was extremely talented and was able to develop this Esper ability to an extraordinary level. His defense was astonishing, and he had many Molding Talents. He was a boss-level character.

First, Hadavy had the (Low Strength Attack Immunity] Molding Talent. As long as the damage of the attacks did not exceed a certain value, the damage dealt by those attacks would be considered null. This value depended on his defense, and his Esper ability was the ‘Hardening’ type that remarkably increased his defense. Therefore, the focus fire strategy was close to completely useless on him.

Another thing that gave Han Xiao a hard time was Hadavy’s ‘True Damage Immunity’-type Molding Talent. Beyond Grade A seeds were all exceptionally talented. For a tank like Hadavy, it was not weird for him to have such a talent. This meant that (Legendary Battle Technique] was useless against him.

Focus fire hardly had any effect, and True Damage was useless-Han Xiao’s two trump cards were no threat to Hadavy. The only method left was to slowly reduce his health.

Every time they fought, it was basically two tanks bashing each other.

Han Xiao had defeated Hadavy every time but never killed him. It was not that he did not want to, but he just could not kill Hadavy before he escaped. Meanwhile, Hadavy seemed like he was comfortable getting beaten, so he kept coming to challenge him.

One year earlier, Hadavy had suddenly gone to fight with him. Han Xiao had no history or beef with him, so he had thought that this was definitely a result of the enemy organizations’ solution to him. So, you’re very tanky? We will just find someone even more tanky to annoy

you!

How the tables had turned. In the past, the Bloodshed Land felt like vomiting every time they saw Han Xiao. Now, Han Xiao felt like vomiting every time he saw Hadavy.

With no other enemy Calamity Grades joining the battle, Han Xiao had only one target. A part of the mechanical army followed the specially designed combat mode to fight with Hadavy. Those cuties were more than enough to hold him back; Han Xiao was only in charge of providing the Mechanical Force bonus. He had no intention of fighting with Hadavy at close range at all. It would be an absolute waste of energy

At the same time, Han Xiao controlled the other parts of the mechanical army to attack the nearby enemy fleets. Concentrated dark blue annihilation beams penetrated the shields of spaceships, leaving strange colors of energy erosion at the edge of the hole created. Battleships lost their defenses one after another, and their exterior armor was quickly dismantled and torn to pieces.

A vigorous fire snake splashed out from the broken hole on the spaceship, turning into a fire dragon for an instant before extinguishing

With their energy furnaces losing balance, the battleships exploded from within, turning into fireworks in the universe, lasting for just an instant before disappearing, too.

With the current combat capability of the mechanical army, taking part in a galactic battle was not a problem. He gradually helped his fleet to stabilize the situation.

After quite a long time, the enemies’ troops started to show signs of defeat. It was just a matter of time till the stargate was destroyed.

Hadavy seemed to intend to retreat as well. He started to try to get rid of the Mechanical Army and attempted to back away. However, he did not escape toward where the ambush was but headed right into the formation of Han Xiao’s fleet, intending to pass through it and retreat through the stargate while Han Xiao’s fleet had yet to completely obliterate the Bloodshed Land’s line of defense.

"Running away so soon?" Under the mechanical suit helmet, Han Xiao raised his brows in surprise.

He had thought that the assassination attempt this time would have something new, but it seemed even worse than the previous assassination attempts.

"It’s definitely not simple." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, thought for a moment, and turned around to chase Hadavy.

His fleet was in Hadavy’s route; Han Xiao was not going to watch him rush into his fleet. If Hadavy wanted to do something, no one else would be able to stop him.

Han Xiao gradually closed the distance between him and Hadavy, and millions of mechanical soldiers followed behind him.

They went all the way to the frontline of the battle, the edge of the battlefield that his fleet and the Bloodshed Land reinforcements were fighting in. Han Xiao had only just caught up with Hadavy, but seeing that Hadavy had already passed through his fleet, he stopped and did not intend to continue chasing.

This time, Hadavy suddenly stopped running and turned around, rushing right toward Han Xiao, trying to get close to him under the violent rain of attacks.

That’s strange. Han Xiao was alarmed. He was just about to dodge when a warning suddenly came from his mechanical suit’s radar, showing thirty high energy reaction sources around!

Suddenly, in the Bloodshed Land reinforcement fleet around, thirty Grade As appeared and all rushed toward Han Xiao. Han Xiao even saw the eight Vanguard Officials including Fosters. They had followed the reinforcement fleet through the stargate but never engaged with the Black Star Army’s several Calamity Grade, all for this moment!

Attacks from thirty Calamity Grades came from all directions, applying immense pressure. Han Xiao hastily controlled the mechanical army to block them, but Hadavy found an opportunity and bolted right into Han Xiao, crushing the mechanical soldiers in his path.

Han Xiao realized that Hadavy was tightly wrapping his arms around his body, and he could not escape from him. Hadavy hugged him and dashed toward the stargate.

The thirty Calamity Grades ignored the attacks from the mechanical army and attacked Hadavy time after time, giving him more speed.

The Bloodshed Land fleet around gave up all attacks and defended the stargate with everything they had from the attacks of Han Xiao’s fleet.

Han Xiao’s brain quickly processed everything, and he immediately understood the opponents’ entire plan.

Make Hadavy act like he was ambushing me to force me to fight, then fake a retreat and lead me to near the stargate. The other Calamity Grades secretly returned to the Seoul Star Cluster and waited in the reinforcements. The Bloodshed Land knew that I’d attack the last logistics transit station. This is a trap they deliberately exposed, to allow these Calamity Grades to follow the reinforcements through the stargate to arrive at this battlefield. Their target isn’t to kill me but strike at this moment and help Hadavy restrain me, sending me into the stargate!

The other side of the stargate was the Seoul Star Cluster, the headquarters of the Klent Kingdom and the Bloodshed Land!

Ha, I get it. You want to drag me to your territory so that I have no back up. Then you guys can slowly exhaust me. Even if you can’t kill me, you guys will be able to capture me alive easily.

Han Xiao was speechless.

These little b\*stards are quite imaginative. Are they trying to elope with me?

Hadavy’s body could easily withstand the attacks. Their flying speed rapidly increased. The Bloodshed Land battleships all opened up a path. The blue vortex at the center of the stargate enlarged in Han Xiao’s eyes very quickly as it got closer.

Seeing that the strategy was about to succeed, Hadavy could not help but send a voice message to Han Xiao.

"When we reach the Seoul Star Cluster, we will fight again. By the way, should I tell them to bring your mechanical army over? Then we will have a great fight." Hadavy’s tone was sincere.

Han Xiao’s mouth twitched. "You’re quite f\*cking honest. Since you love fighting with me so much, let me go if you have the guts. As long as you don’t run, I will fight with you all you like."

"No, fighting is one thing, but I don’t want to die."

Hadavy shook his head. He tightened his arms around Han Xiao’s waist and stubbornly flew toward the stargate.

"You think highly of me…"

Han Xiao was speechless.

Honestly, he had no hatred toward Hadavy. Hadavy had absolutely no interest in the secret war-he just wanted to fight with him. After fighting so many times, as fellow Beyond Grade A seeds, they even respected each other. Sometimes, they could even chat while fighting

However, that did not affect Han Xiao’s resolve to get rid of this sh\*t stirrer.

Chapter 694: Steady as Always

In the remote command room on Planet Heber, the staff sergeant chief Jorde and a few assistants were nervously looking at the situation of the battle through the remote video.

"It looks like we might succeed this time." An assistant gulped nervously.

"Don’t relax yet. Black Star has too many tricks up his sleeves. Before he enters the star gate, no one is to let their guard down," Jorde said with a heavy tone.

This kidnapping mission was his idea. Over the three years prior, Black Star had fought with the frontline troops of the Bloodshed Land dozens of times. He had come up with many ideas, but all had been foiled by Han Xiao. This enemy was both strong and difficult to kill, almost invincible in the Calamity Grade level, giving him a huge headache. However, Jorde was not discouraged, instead treating Black Star as a test for himself as the Tyrant intended.

In the past half a year, Black Star had been leading his team in destroying their logistics transit stations in the desolate region. With a burst of inspiration, Jorde had decided to set this trap and try to drag Black Star into the Seoul Star Cluster.

As long as they succeeded, even if they were not able to kill Black Star, they would be able to restrain him. The Seoul Star Cluster was their headquarters while Black Star had no help and nowhere to run.

As soon as Black Star fell into their hands, Klent would be willing to use all kinds of methods to control him. Purple Crystal would lose a Beyond Grade A seed, and the potential stock that they had invested in would become Klent’s.

This way, he would have dealt with a rising star of the Shattered Star Ring without His Excellency Tyrant’s help and would be filled with a sense of achievement. He would also become more important to His Excellency Tyrant.

SUCC

Of course, all of that was predicated on the successful kidnapping of Black Star. Jorde stared at the screen and was ready to send orders to the Calamity Grades anytime.

In his eyes, Han Xiao was already kind of a boss-type enemy. His current attitude was coincidentally similar to the players when they fought a boss in a group, waiting for Han Xiao to activate his ‘next stage’.

On the battlefield near the stargate, from when the thirty Calamity Grade attacked to when Han Xiao was hugged by Hadavy while flying toward the Stargate, it only took tens of seconds.

The attacks from Fosters and all thirty Calamity Grades landed on Hadavy’s back time after time, giving him a boost. His speed kept increasing, and they were getting closer to the stargate.

Suddenly, every cell in Han Xiao’s body started to behave like a reaction furnace that was operating at its maximum power output. They generated thick energy that turned into ice cold Void Energy, which quickly filled every corner of his body. His body felt like he was submerged in freezing water, but Void Energy was burning on the surface of his body, turning into gray energy flames.

Under the mechanical suit helmet, Han Xiao’s eyes turned into an obsidian color, and his pupils became the size of a grain of rice. In an instant, he entered the (Void Molt] state. His attributes increased, and the (Void) attribute of his energy was enhanced.

Suddenly, Han Xiao disappeared from within Hadavy’s arms.

"Everyone, focus. Black Star might appear in a nearby location anytime. Mages that have mastered Space-type spells, sense the dimension he’s in and the route he’s taking. The moment he appears, lock down his movements!"

Jorde immediately issued orders through the remote command channel. He was prepared for this.

After fighting each other for more than three years, Jorde knew Black Star very well. When he was designing the plan, he had already considered the various abilities Black Star had. Although he did not know that Han Xiao’s ability to sort of teleport was (Advanced Void Travel), after seeing it so many times and inquiring from many Supers, he more or less knew how it worked and understood how to limit some of Han Xiao’s abilities.

Among the thirty Calamity Grade in the ambush, Jorde specifically deployed a few Mages that were proficient in Space spells. These people had prepared for a long time. The magical items on their hands emitted a magic light, and within microseconds, they sensed the tiny ripples in reality from when Han Xiao stepped into the Void Dimension.

Their magic followed this energy ripple. The route Han Xiao took in the Void Dimension instantly appeared in the minds of these Mages like a conspicuous marking. The few of them turned to an empty location simultaneously. Without hesitation, the high-level space locking spells that they had already prepared before the battle were all launched toward this empty location.

The next moment, Han Xiao left the Void Dimension and appeared at this location. All kinds of high-level space locking spells were flying toward him, almost not giving him any time to react.

However, Han Xiao did not need to react anyway. Before using Advanced Void Travel, he already knew that he would be attacked the moment he came out. This was not the first time that had happened.

With his rocketing fame, every battle he fought would make the other organizations know more about him.

The instant that Han Xiao appeared, he bent his fingers into a claw shape and dragged the space like it was a cloth. Without hesitation, he used (Void Distortion).

Visible twists and folds appeared in the space around him. The universe coordinates of a small area around Han Xiao deviated slightly, yet the spells were deflected away following the folds and completely missed.

Disarming the Mages’ ambush easily, he was temporarily not in danger. Through his (Void] attribute energy, he applied Mechanical Force on his mechanical army directly.

With electrical sparks, the mechanical army became lively again.

Two thirds of the Calamity Grades had no choice but to give up trying to restrain and hastily dodged Han Xiao’s attacks. Other than Hadavy, no one present dared to take on the focus fire of Han Xiao’s mechanical army.

"Star Shaking Fist!" Still not giving up, Fosters’ arms swelled up and launched a scarlet beam right at Han Xiao before he was restrained by the mechanical army.

"This again? Don’t you Vanguard Officials have any other trump cards?"

Han Xiao curled his lips and deactivated Void Distortion. He drew a circle in front of him with his hands. The machine parts followed the track his hands moved in and formed a ring-shaped device, clashing directly with the Star Shaking Fist’s scarlet beam.

The mechanical ring was hollow in its center. The Star Shaking Fist should have easily passed through it. However, when it entered the hollow part of the ring device, it seemed to have lost its momentum and impetus, instead sucked in by the mechanical ring. It turned into a red stream of light and spun rapidly along the inside of the ring, as if it could not escape from the mechanical ring’s strange force field.

This was a new device that Han Xiao had built with the new Control Branch Cutting-Edge Knowledge (Advanced Space Application] Force Field Distorter!

The hollow part of the mechanical ring was actually covered with a special force field that changed the space within. It was set to make a closed loop. Most of the energy would be trapped in this force field space after being sucked in.

In fact, Star Shaking Fist was still ‘moving forward’, but because of the force field, it was now spinning in a closed loop.

On the other side, Hadavy once again rushed toward Han Xiao with open arms like he wanted a hug.

Disgusted, Han Xiao used his Mechanical Force to face the Force Field Distorter at Hadavy and released the captured Star Shaking Fist, blowing Hadavy far away.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the Mages. In his eyes, these Mages would cause him much more trouble than those muscular men. Seeing that these Mages were about to cast spells again, Han Xiao launched a compressed orb that expanded into a rectangular mechanical device.

The appearance of this device looked like a trapezoidal pyramid. It was completely black. Then, from top to bottom, dots of light started to appear, forming a complex magic engraving.

Ohm!

There was no sound in the vacuum space, yet those Mages felt they were in an ocean, surrounded by roaring, deafening, and violent waves.

This was the vibration of magic energy!

In the senses of these Mages, the magic energy around them suddenly became violent and difficult to control. Even their own magic energy felt slow and unresponsive. The expression on their faces all changed.

"Humph, this thing is enough to cause you people some trouble." Han Xiao chuckled.

The name of this mechanical device was Magic Tide Generator. It could disrupt the magic elements within a certain area, making it chaotic and violent. It was specially designed against Mages.

The Mages within the Magic Tide range would all be given the debuffs of ‘Slowed Casting Speed’ and ‘Weakened Spell Power’. Lagi had also accepted Han Xiao’s request and added magic engravings to it, making this device much more effective than the original.

Machines were extremely versatile. In the past three years, Han Xiao had fused Cutting-Edge Knowledges, High-End Knowledges, and Basic Knowledges many times, creating quite a few powerful new equipment.

Han Xiao had a ton of new machines in his hands, he easily broke out of the enemies’ encirclement. Now, Hadavy and the others were on the passive side.

Seeing that Han Xiao had escaped their control, Jorde punched the screen, knowing that this mission had basically failed. He inhaled deeply and immediately changed the orders.

"The mission has failed. Everyone, abort and immediately retreat through the stargate!"

Fosters roared with resignation.

Hadavy was regretful as well, but he quickly stopped and immediately rushed toward the stargate.

Han Xiao had already distanced himself from Hadavy earlier, so he had no intention of stopping Hadavy as he watched him disappear in the stargate. He had no way to kill Hadavy within such a short distance; that guy was way too tanky.

Han Xiao did not bother to waste energy on Hadavy. His target was the other thirty Calamity Grades.

He controlled the mechanical army to surround them and looked at the thirty Calamity Grades within the army trying to break out. He narrowed his eyes.

"Since you are already here, leave me some souvenirs."

This time, a teleportation gate opened beside Han Xiao. Lagi walked out of it and observed the situation.

Compared to three years ago, Lagi had not changed much. After all, languid people all looked much older, so he still looked about the same.

"Hey, you came at the right time. Help me stall as many of these Calamity Grades as possible."

Han Xiao patted his shoulder then pointed at the thirty Calamity Grades trying to get rid of the mechanical army and head toward the stargate.

Lagi sighed, took out his magic stuff, and floated toward the chaotic battlefield.

"Remember to collect my corpse."

As the high-level combatants retreated, the Bloodshed Land no longer sent reinforcements through the stargate. They completely gave up resisting, as well as the resources in the logistics transit station. The fleet covered the high-level combatants to retreat through the stargate one after the other.

Jorde had been commanding remotely the whole time. When the stargate was seized by Han Xiao’s fleet, his body finally relaxed, and he collapsed in his chair. With a very weak voice, he said, "Count the losses. How many people were unable to retreat, and how many high level combatants did we lose?"

"Re-Report, thirty-seven percent of the reinforcement fleet did not retreat in time. Out of the high-level combatants deployed, Hadavy and the eight Vanguard Officials successfully retreated. Out of the remaining twenty-two Grade A Supers, only seventeen managed to retreat. We have also lost contact with the two Calamity Grades stationed at the logistics transit station."

"This means that we lost seven high level combatants " Jorde could not help covering his face. Although the dead Grade A Supers were basically all new members that Klent had helped them gather from private organizations around the Star Cluster, they were still high-level combatants.

Jorde was hurting from losing seven high level combatants right away. At least forty to fifty Calamity Grades had died at Black Star’s hands. He was basically a Calamity Grade reaper.

Just thinking about Black Star’s battle record sent shivers down Jorde’s spine.

If not because many large organizations had formed alliance with the Bloodshed Land secretly in the last three years, which had brought them quite a number of high-level combatants, he felt that the Bloodshed Land troops would have had to avoid Black Star at all costs.

When Jorde was questioning life, the battle in the desolate area far away had basically ended.

The enemies that were unable to retreat in time lost all means to escape. Han Xiao ordered the fleet under his command to chase, and they easily eliminated the rest of the Bloodshed Land forces there. At the same time, they dismantled the stargate into parts and transported it away as spoils of war. A Star Cluster grade stargate could sell for quite a lot of money; bringing it back to study it was a rather good choice too.

Lagi’s spacetime secret spells helped the mechanical army retrain many Grade A Supers.

He had to admit, Lagi was very strong. Han Xiao was quite satisfied with this vice captain, though the morale of the division led by Lagi was consistently zero.

The Calamity Grades that were unable to escape were heavily surrounded. Their resistance was futile, and they were all captured by Han Xiao. He planned to throw them into his Happy Little House to squeeze some juice.

As the warfare ended, the fleet cleaned the battlefield and searched for spoils of war. Han Xiao did not need to do any of these things.

He retrieved his mechanical army and returned to the machinery modification room in the flagship. He then let the automatic mechanical arms repair the damage to the mechanical soldiers. He took off the Mountain Ape mechanical suit and started repairing it himself. He treated this as a postwar leisure activity.

Beep beep!

This time, his communicator rang. Han Xiao picked it up, and Ralph’s projection appeared.

"Your assistant has submitted the report. You guys have done a very good job this time. It’s another celebration-worthy victory." Ralph smiled, in a good mood.

Han Xiao glanced at him, then turned to repair his mechanical suit while saying with a casual tone, "The Bloodshed Land ambushed me again. This time, in order to kidnap me, they deployed many experienced Calamity Grades previously stationed in Westwind, Kaya, and Chaida. Their stronghold should be fragile at the moment. You guys can make use of the opportunity."

"We will seriously consider this suggestion." "Anything else? If not, I’m hanging up. Don’t distract me from repairing things," Han Xiao said without even turning around.

Through three years of contact, the two of them were now very close. When communicating privately, they were much more informal and casual.

Furthermore, Ralph was not considered his boss anymore. He had become the Purple Crystal Civilization’s long-term partner a year ago. Despite still being a Section Zero member, he was actually already an individual partner.

"Ahem, did you forget? This is the last logistics transit station. You have been battling outside for half a year. Now that the mission is complete, come back. There are no important missions that need you for now. I’m planning to give you a long holiday," Ralph said.

Han Xiao’s movements paused, and his eyes sparkled.

For this mission, he had led the fleet to battle in the desolate region for more than half a year and never returned to Colton. Quite a number of private matters had been stacking up. Now that he had some holiday, he would finally have the time to settle them.

Chapter 695: Army State and Holiday Target

After hanging up, Han Xiao did not continue to repair his mechanical suit. He left the workshop, went to the command room, and summoned all the officers of the fleet for a meeting

Cleaning the battlefield did not require constant monitoring from the officers. After the order was issued, the officers of the fleets came to the flagship one after another, gathering in the command room. As they entered, they all nodded at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao nodded to greet his own officers as well. The listless Lagi; the reliable Herlous; the grown-up Sylvia; the reckless Harmon; and Karmbe, Marian, and Misecech.

Other than the officers of the army, there were also a few other Section Zero members in the expedition fleet. Having fought alongside each other for half a year, they were all very familiar with each other.

When everyone had arrived, Han Xiao knocked the table. The sound of chatting suddenly disappeared completely as everyone looked

over.

"This time, I summoned everyone to tell you guys the next step of the plan. I’ve just received word from Purple Crystal. They are very satisfied with our results over the last six months, so they have decided to call us back and give us a long holiday. Our mission is complete; we can rest for a while now."

Everyone was overjoyed when they heard this.

"That’s great. I haven’t been back home in half a year. My wife has been asking me when I will return every day. Haha, this time, I can give her a surprise." A core member of another organization spoke first with joy.

"Maybe she will give you a surprise…" Lagi patted his shoulder to comfort him.

"Thanks." This person’s face was filled with gratitude. Now that you’ve said that, it will definitely not happen.

"Finally…"

Sylvia bit her bottom lip lightly and held her hands above her chest, almost yelling out loud.

Han Xiao glanced at her and nodded with approval in his mind. Over the past three years, Sylvia had been taking part in actual combat, walking at the edge of life and death. Her growth speed was much faster than before; she had entered her rapid growth period.

In Han Xiao’s previous life, Sylvia had reached Calamity Grade in Version 3.0 and earned the ‘Mechanical Lady Knight’ title. In the past three years, this potential of hers had gradually started showing. Back then, Sylvia had been jealous of Feidin’s extraordinary talent, but now she was showing a similar talent.

Han Xiao estimated that Sylvia might really be able to grow from Grade B to Grade A during the update. After all, there were still seven more years for her to grow.

Still, the biggest change in Sylvia was her appearance. In the past three years, she had gradually matured. She had brown and long curly hair, she was tall, and her skin was snow white. Her facial features were solid and pretty. Altogether, she had an innocent and pure yet alluring look.

Plus, she did not wear any bulky alloy mechanical suits. Instead, she mainly used thin, light battle suits that were focused on shields, which displayed her smoking body covered in the tight battle suit. The battle suit increased her Charm by at least thirty percent. Beauties were always a feast for the eyes.

Herlous turned around and said to Herlous, "Old Herlous, after returning, take over Reynold’s job and check on the business developments of the various Star Systems."

"Okay." Herlous nodded.

Herlous was always an important managing officer. In order to train himself, he had followed the fleet for the last half a year, while the daily matters had temporarily been given to Reynold and the other officers stationed in the headquarters to take care of. They would report the situation to Han Xiao every so often.

Han Xiao had more trust in Herlous’ ability to handle matters. Other than liking card games, old Herlous was reliable in most things. He had improved quite a lot in the past six months as well, becoming Grade B+ and finally starting to see the gate to the Calamity Grade.

In Han Xiao’s previous life, Herlous had passed away early under the beast tide of Planet Sunil, so Han Xiao did not know if he had the potential to become a Calamity Grade.

However, since he was a protagonist-type character with Luck Glow, although his talent could not compete with cheaters like Feidin, it was still much higher than normal people.

After giving a few orders, Han Xiao ended the meeting

The cleaning of the battlefield was also completed, so the fleet headed back to Colton.

Han Xiao locked himself inside the office to look at the current operation status of the Black Star Army.

In the past three years, the Black Star Army had been developing smoothly. The importance of the mercenary business had already dropped to being third. The Black Star Army’s business transformation gradually completed. It was no longer a mercenary group; it was now finally a large armed organization.

The mercenary business was separated and formed the Black Star Army’s mercenary division, which continued to accept hires as a mercenary group. Because of this, many freelance mercenaries were satisfied. Therefore, not only did the Black Star Army not lose many talents, but its appeal for mercenaries increased instead.

The Mercenary League of the Shattered Star Ring was in the process of forming but had yet to become official. It was decided that the Black Star Army would hold one of the high positions.

Sky Ring, Blades, and the other large armies had been borrowing Han Xiao’s name to recruit people all over the Star Field. At the same time, they also had to speak with the Mercenary Alliance, which was an enormous universe-level guild. The Shattered Star Ring was just a division of the Mercenary Alliance. In order for them to form a league, they had to get past the Mercenary Alliance.

The Black Star Army’s current main business was the long-term partnership agreement with Purple Crystal, to fight in the secret war for them.

The second most important business was mining. Dozens of Star System civilizations invited and supported him to build bases in their territories and allowed him to mine on resource planets. This was the most profitable and currently the biggest income of the Black Star Army.

Having built bases in dozens of Star Systems, the Black Star Army’s range increased to just under half of the Colton Star Cluster.

With so many Star Systems distanced so far away from each other, if he had used his own resources to build up these bases, the expenses would have been very high. This would make the cash flow of the army unhealthy or even broken.

Even though the contract fees these Star System civilizations gave were not little, it was better than those huge costs. Also, harvesting resource planets required a huge amount of manpower, as well as the building and purchasing of various harvesting devices, which would cost a lot of money.

Although the Star System would provide a certain amount of support, they would not go all out to help the Black Star Army harvest their own resource planet. At most, they would only provide some manpower and devices so that the Black Star Army could harvest the resource planet.

Harvesting resource planets required a huge amount of investment in the early stage; most organizations would not be able to afford it. If Han Xiao only used the army’s resources, the utilization of the right to harvest resource planets would be extremely low, even with the help of the Black Spirit Race. Although the Black Spirit Race was very good at mining, they were still very much behind in terms of development. After so many of them had been killed on Planet Sunil, their population size had yet to recover.

However, Han Xiao announced the Black Star Army’s harvesting contracts with the various Star System civilizations and made a public bidding, open to all financial groups of the Star Field. These financial groups understood the huge profit involved in resource planets, so they all looked to partner with Han Xiao.

Of course, Han Xiao was not allowed to sell the harvesting right given by these civilizations, but finding people to partner with would not be a problem. He let the financial groups provide the money needed to help the Black Star Army harvest many planets at the same time while the resources harvested were sold through the channels of these financial groups for them to make commission.

Han Xiao set the bids separately for the various Star Systems, clearly dividing the area each financial group was responsible for.

This way, although the profit margin would not be as high, the overall quantity was much higher.

With the huge income, the Black Star Army was able to expand its business to many Star Systems within three years. The sub-bases in every Star System were harvesting several resource planets, so the actual profit made was much higher than if Han Xiao harvested them without the help of the financial groups.

The number of financial group partners jumped from single digits to 127, all well-known large financial groups within the Star Field.

Therefore, in just three years, the size of the Black Star Army had already grown tremendously!

War, mining, and missions—these were currently the top three businesses of the Black Star Army. Due to its versatile business operations, it showed some signs of being a financial group. Its official member count had exceeded ten million long ago, and managers dealing with miscellaneous tasks also became important parts of the army.

Due to the rapid increase in size, the number of problems multiplied as well. There was a huge pile of problems that needed to be solved every day, which gave Han Xiao quite a headache. He had no choice but to let his subordinates deal with the details of these matters while all he had to do was monitor and control the overall development of the entire organization, also going out to fight people from time to time.

The three major businesses of the army are right on track, making a lot of money, and maintaining a virtuous cycle. I just need to ensure the stability of the army.

After receiving the first wave of profit from harvesting resource planets two years ago, he rarely looked at his savings… All he knew was that as long as he did not suddenly decide to give everything to charity, he would basically not even be able to spend it all.

This holiday was very rare; he did not want to worry about the trivial matters of the organization but decided to settle the Class Advancement mission.

Within the past three years, Han Xiao had found a mission in his memories that rewarded a level 180 silver legacy blueprint. The mission involved passing rounds of tests to finally gain the acceptance of the inheritor.

As this was a mission that rewarded a level 180 blueprint, it was extremely troublesome. Also, its mission location was in another Star Cluster.

Han Xiao had not had many holidays in the last three years, so he had only finished seven rounds of this mission and had yet to complete it. He estimated that he should be able to complete it during this long holiday.

Getting the blueprint was just the first step. He still had to build an orange-grade product out of it. Han Xiao did not intend to use a Mission Completion Card. In order to level up the Cutting-Edge Knowledges, he had spent quite a lot of Experience. Although killing Calamity Grades gave him some Experience, the Experience that he had at the moment was only enough for him to level up around ten levels at most.

There were still seven more years till the start of Version 3.0. Without enough Experience, reaching Beyond Grade A was basically impossible. Anyway, he was strong enough for the moment, so Han Xiao did not think it was necessary to look for a Mission Completion Card everywhere and complete the Class Advancement quickly. After all, the Promotion mission at level 200 was another obstacle he would need to break through.

While thinking, Han Xiao opened the interface and browsed through his mission list. There were quite a lot of missions stocked up.

The fourth round of (Prey) was still inactive. Due to reasons he did not know, Thousand Shadows had decided not to do anything for three years, which made Han Xiao very alarmed. He felt like this was the calm before the storm.

Han Xiao did not have the time to settle Godora’s Rank S (Bloodline) mission as well, as he felt that it would be quite troublesome and would rather use that time to strengthen the Black Star Army, which would give him much more benefits than the mission reward.

Aroshia’s mission was still on hold as well. However, Feidin’s hidden mission (Choice] was completed upon achieving the fourth ending. Feidin and Chen Xing fell in love-it really was self-lovemaking.

The mission reward was quite good-a lot of Experience, a random reward chance, and a huge increase in the Favorability of both Feidin and Chen Xing. It made Han Xiao feel like he was the matchmaker for the two of them.

By the way, doesn’t this count as self-loving?

Han Xiao could not imagine what the ceremony would look like if those two decided to get married, but he knew that it would definitely be difficult to look at!

Beep beep!

As he was looking through the interface, Han Xiao’s communicator suddenly rang.

He picked it up. It was a message from Aesop.

"Vilna… hmm? Is this a hint for me to hand over my job and groom my successor in advance?" Han Xiao muttered and narrowed his eyes.

Chapter 696: Handover

At the exterior tracks of the Planet Golden Gate, a metal fortress looking satellite was orbiting.

This was the Black Star Army’s current headquarters, which had moved away from the Planet Golden Gate surface and become a mobile satellite fortress. Its area was many times bigger and had far richer functions and facilities.

Inside the satellite was the body of this base, a space station similar to the Juberly Hub. The surface was filled with defense facilities and port passages.

In the past three years, Han Xiao had turned most of the base into a satellite fortress. Although its cost was high, he was a mine owner now, so he did not feel any heartache.

This time, at the large port inside the base, a tall purple-haired beauty was walking back and forth, glancing in the direction of the port frequently like she was waiting for someone. Her fingers were crossed tightly, and her pretty face was filled with apprehension.

It was Vilna.

About ten days ago, she had followed Aesop’s orders and gone to the Black Star Army headquarters to wait to meet with Han Xiao.

Today was the day that Han Xiao would return. Vilna had arrived early at the dock to wait. When she thought about how she was going to meet the man known as the ‘closest to Beyond Grade A in the Shattered Star Ring’, she could not but feel nervous.

Before this, Vilna had never seen Han Xiao with her own eyes, nor did she talk to him through communication. To this mysterious senior of hers, she could not help but imagine all sorts of things.

The Black Star Army has risen so quickly, so maybe Black Star is full of ambition? People say that many organizations he’s defeated all fell into his trap, so maybe he is a master of plot? He also has extraordinary battle records that shocked the entire Star Field, so maybe he’s an intimidating warrior?

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Vilna’s mind. Apprehensive, Vilna kept rehearsing what kind of attitude she should use to meet Black Star in her mind.

At this time, streams of light approached from afar and appeared outside the dock. An enormous Black Star fleet appeared and slowly entered the dock entrance.

The bottom of the battleships locked onto the tracks, entering the base to be parked at the various docks.

The flagship stopped at the large dock where Vilna was. The hatch opened with a hiss, and the gangway opened automatically and connected to the edge of the dock.

Wearing a black windbreaker, Han Xiao walked out with wide strides, casually looked around, and stepped onto the dock’s alloy floor. The people behind him swarmed out after him.

Vilna calmed herself and trotted over, standing in front of Han Xiao.

"Yo-Your Excellency Black Star, my name is Vilna. I’m Floating Dragon’s new officer. Aesop told me to find you…"

Han Xiao stopped walking and looked down at Vilna with his dark eyes, blatantly sizing her

up.

Vilna felt like her heart was at her throat. Han Xiao did not speak. She gulped, and her mind went black, not knowing what to say. The two of them looked at each other in silence.

After looking at her for quite a while, only then did Han Xiao smile faintly. "Aesop told me about it. He asked me to help you build the second Field Team. Don’t worry, I’ll help you."

Then, Han Xiao patted Vilna’s shoulder and said meaningfully, "Since you have joined Floating Dragon, do a good job. I believe in

you."

Vilna’s face was slightly red, and her tightened body relaxed a little. Han Xiao’s friendliness made her a little less nervous.

Black Star seems to be a very nice person. I don’t understand why Jenny keeps emphasizing that Black Star is a rude, antisocial, and evil \*sshole.

"Follow me."

Han Xiao snapped his fingers and walked off. Vilna regained her focus and quickly caught up with Han Xiao.

The others had all left; Han Xiao and Vilna were the only ones left. Turning down one corridor after another, they walked in silence.

Without turning around, Han Xiao suddenly asked, "Have you met Ames? What do you think of her?"

Vilna was stunned for a moment. She thought for a while, stared at Han Xiao’s back, and answered softly, "She’s very gentle, and I have always admired her. It’s an honor to work for her."

"Hmm… does she know that your job is to build the second Field Team?"

"Probably…" Vilna tried to recall. She then realized that Ames had never asked what her job was, so she added, "Aesop definitely told

her."

"What does she think then?"

"Er…" Vilna thought hard about it then said carefully, "She didn’t seem to react out of the ordinary."

Han Xiao touched his chin and stopped speaking.

He knew that finding his successor was most likely Aesop’s idea, since Ames would not be bothered about things like this. Nonetheless, he was completely okay with it. After all, Floating Dragon had helped him a lot in the past, so he wanted to return the favor and leave something for them.

He chose to end things on peaceful terms so that he could develop better. Thus, he did indeed plan to groom Vilna and smoothen her future path, using these seven years to complete the handover of his job.

Furthermore, Vilna was someone he knew. Without his presence, Vilna had been the authentic Field Team officer of Floating Dragon in his previous life.

… who also met her demise together with Floating Dragon.

As memories flashed through his mind, they arrived right outside the office. Han Xiao ended his thoughts and took Vilna into the room. Then, he called Reynold, Herlous, and Sylvia over.

"Let me introduce Vilna, a new officer of Floating Dragon. She’s planning to build the second Field Team, so she came to seek my help. You guys, forget about expenses and help her recruit people. Also, choose ten financial groups from the ones that are working with us and convince them to invest in the new Floating Dragon Field Team using my name. You have to take this job seriously. Help her to build a Field Team based on her plan and support her as much as possible."

Han Xiao spoke quickly. He planned to use the Black Star Army’s current resources and influence to build a new team for Floating Dragon without considering the returns.

"Understood." Reynold nodded solemnly. He shook Vilna’s hand and said, "Tell me what you need later. I will do my best to assist you."

"0–Okay." Vilna had yet to recover from the shock.

Han Xiao’s degree of help was way beyond her imagination. All she had to do was talk and not worry about anything else; the Black Star Army would settle all of it.

How generous!

Vilna was petrified. She started to blush. This completely abolished the negative image that Jenny had set for Han Xiao in her mind and built a new, tall image.

Friendly, steady, reliable, rich, strong, and handsome… It’s great to have such an amazing senior!

Why is Jenny always lying!

Vilna was secretly upset.

No wonder Black Star could build such an enormous organization in ten short years. Although Vilna did not want to admit it, after such short contact with Han Xiao, he already felt much more reliable than Ames.

"Go do your stuff then…" Han Xiao waved his hands.

Reynold nodded. He turned to look at the others and said, "Okay, you guys go out and wait for me. I have something I want to discuss with His Excellency Black Star alone."

Han Xiao was a little surprised. He looked at Reynold and saw that he clearly had something on his mind. Han Xiao thought about it and nodded at the others, signaling them to go out first.

The others took Vilna away, leaving only Han Xiao and Reynold in the room.

"What did you want to talk to me about?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked at Reynold.

"Actually… I didn’t want to bring this up initially because no one was able to help, but now you’re able to. I have something that I need your help with," Reynold said with a sincere tone and a solemn face.

Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled. He smelled a mission.

In the past few years, he had kept trying to trigger a mission from Reynold, which he sadly never did. He thought that Reynold did not have any missions on him. However, now that Reynold had brought it up himself, he was certainly surprised.

He did not expect to receive such good news as soon as his holiday started.

Chapter 697: Another Familiar Face‽

Reynold had very low requirements. Other than finding Han Xiao to learn blueprints, he was pretty transparent the rest of the time. Ever since joining the army, he had always kept a low profile. His business capabilities were as rigorous and reliable as his personality, never causing any trouble at all. He managed the logistics of the army extremely well. This was the first time that he had asked Han Xiao for help.

Seeing that Reynold had a lot on his mind, Han Xiao figured out what was going on. This matter was probably very difficult to deal with, which was why Reynold had waited until now to ask for his help. Since the start, Reynold had only come to learn, not for help. However, now that he had achieved so much fame in the entire Star Field, Reynold saw hope and felt that he had the ability to help, so he now was asking him.

Han Xiao felt that he had guessed most of it correctly and secretly focused more.

"Tell me about it first."

He did not immediately agree to help and decided to listen to the mission content first.

Reynold contemplated for a while on what to say.

"As you know, I come from the Hyde Star System. I'm sure you know about the situation in the Star System."

Han Xiao nodded.

The Hyde Star System was a Star System without a ruling civilization, connected with six Star System civilizations including Godora. All these civilizations stationed many troops in Hyde and divided this ownerless Star System. They expanded and confronted each other for many years, causing Hyde to become a chaotic land.

"I was born on a small place called Ceciris, located in an area occupied by the Hutt Civilization. Ceciris is ruled by a low-level galactic civilization that has six planets in total under its ruling. It's classified as somewhere between a planet civilization and Star System civilization. This civilization has many governments that compete with each other. As Hyde is always at war, the political situation of Ceciris is volatile.

"My father operated a machine research company, which later went bankrupt. When I was six, they died in a riot caused by a political parade…"

Han Xiao was slightly moved. This was the first time that Reynold had talked about his own story. Usually, he never even mentioned anything about it.

"I have a sister who's nine years older than me. Her name is Rossellin. After my parents died, I lived together with her for three years. When I was nine, she sent me on a long-distance galactic flight off Ceciris and abandoned me.

"When I left home, I was still a child that knew nothing. No one took care of me. I drifted in the galaxy and got through my tough childhood. I then finally had the strength to protect myself. After that, I once went back trying to find Rossellin. Then I discovered what she did."

Reynold shook his head and said, "After I left, her Esper ability awakened. The official saying is that she can manipulate people's minds, subtly rewriting people's perspective on the world. At the start, people did not know about her ability. She used this ability to gather countless believers and built a new religion. New ideology and culture were born in her hands.

"With her ability, in just a few years, she completed the missionary process that would take normal religions decades. More and more people became her followers. She became the pope of the new religion in the Ceciris civilization, loved and worshiped by countless people. Even many high-level officials across the various governments were her believers. She controlled half of the Ceciris civilization with religious methods. Her position was above countless people.

"However, those governments felt that she would threaten their reign, so they kept searching for clues. In the end, her ability was discovered. She became the most dangerous careerist to those governments. She was captured, and the religion that she had created was destroyed.

"Although her Esper ability can modify people's subconscious mindset over a large area, she can't brainwash anyone, can't make anyone a fanatical, and can't control the minds of the others. Therefore, although the society was shocked, no one spoke up for her. Nobody would like having their mind twisted. Her reputation went right down the drain, and she became a sinner spurned by countless people.

"Those governments tried Rossellin. She was convicted of high treason and given life in prison. However, they showed their true intentions very soon. In their eyes, Rossellin's ability was an outstanding tool to assist their ruling. Hence, whoever was going to imprison Rossellin became a problem. Every government wanted to have her, to use her ability to consolidate their rule and damage their opponents. They did not want anyone else to have this tool."

Reynold closed his eyes, pinched the bridge of his nose, and sighed. "On paper, she was locked in prison, but actually, she disappeared from the eye of the public after the public trial. These governments sent spies and special agents to get to her secretly. Even some rebel forces with ulterior motives joined the battle. She became a tool that kept changing owners."

Han Xiao could not help but ask, "So, you want me to save her from the Ceciris civilization? You're already a Calamity Grade—won't you be able to do that yourself?"

"No, she's not on Ceciris anymore." Reynold shook his head. "The Hutt Civilization took an interest in her ability and took her away. She's now a prisoner of a Star System civilization."

Han Xiao understood. No wonder Reynold asked for his help. It turned out that Rossellin had become an important prisoner of a Star System civilization, so getting her would be rather difficult.

To a Star System civilization, they had no obligation to give face to a Calamity Grade. Given how important Rossellin was, the Hutt Civilization would not give her away so easily. Even if Reynold was to attack the prison, he would not be able to fight against the entire Star System civilization alone. He could not save his sister by himself.

I see, so he's asking for my help because of my influence… Han Xiao thought.

"I know that this is very sudden, but there's nothing I can do to the situation Rossellin is in. I hope you can save her." Reynold bowed deeply.

"Hmm…" Han Xiao caressed his chin. "Your sister really seems to be a careerist. I feel that she did this to herself."

Psychics could change others' minds to a certain extent, but the range and efficiency was clearly far inferior compared to Rossellin's Esper ability. It was perfect for spreading religion, exactly what the Arcane Church loved the most.

"Maybe she really is an ambitious careerist; I'm not defending her actions. Although she abandoned me and I don't have much emotions for her anymore, she's still my family. She has already paid the price for what she did; I don't want to see her keep suffering."

Han Xiao was quite surprised. He had always thought that Reynold's heart was mechanical; this was a very rare occasion where Reynold showed any emotion.

After pondering for a while, Han Xiao slowly said, "I can help, but it won't be easy. Even I might not be able to make the Hutt Civilization give her to me just by asking. Rossellin broke the law after all. This isn't a really reasonable request, so they can totally not give me face at all…"

Reynold nodded then said with a solemn expression, "I understand. You don't owe me anything. I will continue to work for you and pay my debts for this."

That's what I'm talking about, brother… Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He smiled and said, "I'll try my best."

This time, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Reformer]!

Mission Introduction: You accepted Reynold's request and decided to save Rossellin from the Hutt Civilization.

Mission Requirements: Save Rossellin.

Reward: 18,000,000 Experience, +30 Reynold Favorability, +80 Rossellin Favorability, [Blank Character Summon Card—Reynold] x 1

Han Xiao glanced at it and was surprised.

The mission itself did not seem too difficult, but the prerequisite to trigger it was. It seemed its requirement was to have quite a close relationship with Reynold while having very high influence, only then would Reynold ask for his help.

The Experience reward was ordinary. The Favorability was common as well. What was most surprising was Reynold's Character Summon Card.

The Blank Character Summon Card of a certain character meant that he could choose any one of Reynold's abilities.

Among all the abilities Reynold had, the most valuable was undoubtedly the Mechanic class Molding Talent [Perfect Mechanical Sense].

Although Character Summon Cards had limited uses, it was better than nothing.

Most of the time, only random draw reward in combat missions had a possibility of giving someone else's Molding Talent. Other than Character Summon Cards, the players had absolutely no way of acquiring any Molding Talents. He had the NPC status, so his drawing range included the Molding Talents, but that was not the case for players.

Han Xiao was not disappointed. In order to get the true [Perfect Mechanical Sense] talent, he had to think of other ways.

A Character Summon Card is fine. I happen to have a use for it too.

The Class Advancement mission required him to build a piece of orange level 180 legacy equipment. It would probably not be possible to build orange equipment with his current Machinery Affinity, so he would have to look for ways to improve his building abilities. However, with the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] effects, he would be able to do it right away, saving him tons of trouble.

Pausing the flow of thoughts, Han Xiao returned to the topic.

"I'll leave in two days and visit the Hutt Civilization. Tell me everything you know. By the way, what does your sister look like?"

"I haven't seen her in many years, but when she was still the pope, I saved quite a few pictures of her. Here, look." Reynold took out his communicator and projected a few pictures.

This was a woman in a gorgeous red and white robe. Her hair was tied into a knot at the back of her head, decorated with a beautiful ornament. Her eyes were bright, and her teeth were pure white. Her face was gentle and beautiful, a little bit similar to Reynold's. Her skin was snow white, and she gave off a very noble vibe. In the picture, she seemed to be making a religious speech. There were many faithful believers below her listening with their heads lowered.

Han Xiao glanced at it, frowned, and glanced at it again. Then, he stared at the face of the woman in the picture and could not take his eyes off her.

Noticing that Han Xiao was staring, Reynold was a little confused. "What is it?"

Han Xiao regained focus and moved his eyes away. He covered his mouth with his fist and coughed twice. "Nothing, your sister is quite pretty."

Reynold gave Han Xiao a strange look.

Actually, when Han Xiao saw Rossellin's face, he was dumbfounded.

Vilna, whom he had met earlier, was someone he knew from his previous life, but he did not expect to see another familiar face on the same day!

Plus, this woman was on a completely different level from Vilna!

Chapter 698: Rejected

The Hutt Civilization was located in the Skywalker Star System, and the Black Star Army had one subdivision set up there. The Hutt Civilization had formed a diplomat team dedicated for the Black Star Army three years ago. The head of this team was an elite from their Foreign Affairs Department, Wolman.

The Black Star Army had set up an office for the Hutt Civilization’s diplomatic team in the satellite subdivision near the resource planet. Wolman and his team were usually there to monitor the harvesting of the resource planet as well as communicate with the Black Star Army’s subdivision.

This day was quiet as usual. Wolman arrived at the office early, gracefully greeted his team members, and sat at his desk. He appreciated the countless stars outside his window before taking out a book from his bag and opening it on the table. This was a book written in the Hutt language. He decided to finish chapter eight to chapter eleven that day, which would take him the entire morning.

Very quickly, he decided on his reading plan. If he was in a good mood later, he would consider reading one more chapter.

In the interstellar era, most of the entertainment and art books were electronic to save on unnecessary production and transportation costs. Physical books had become collectors’ items that only a very small number of people who sought elegance and refinement in life would purchase.

As an elite of the Hutt Foreign Affairs Department, a member of upper society, Wolman strictly required himself to live delicately. He took out a crafted can with green powder, scooped out precisely two spoons, and poured them into a crystal cup. As he poured cold water into the cup, the green powder inside dissolved and turned into a luminous turquoise dense liquid like stars were swimming within. It was beautiful.

This was a type of refreshing drink, a special drink loved by the Huttians. Of course, Wolman’s powder was not factory-made cheap stuff but the premium hand-ground type.

Wolman held the crystal cup in his hand and returned to his seat, sipped it, and picked up the book from the table. He adjusted his seat to lean on the window at forty-five degrees. As if he had completed some kind of ceremony, he finally started reading the book with satisfaction.

He did not hate being deployed to this quiet position, but he was not satisfied with his job either.

Wolman hoped he could be active on the diplomatic political stage between civilizations and display his abilities elegantly; that was how an elite like him should live. To him, dealing with the Black Star Army was a waste of his talent. After all, in his eyes, although the Black Star Army was a very strong armed force, it was just made up of rude, uneducated mercenaries.

This time, a team member hastily walked into the room and said loudly, "Sir, the Black Star Army just sent us a notice. Their leader Black Star will be arriving in the Skywalker Star System in seven days to visit our Hutt Civilization. The details are in this file."

Black Star visiting personally, what could his goal be? Wolman was shocked. Ever since he took on this position, the things that he had been dealing with were all trivial and unimportant. This was the first time that something rather important had happened.

Wolman took the file and read through it carefully. Then he said with surprise, "He wants to see Rossellin? Who’s Rossellin?"

Han Xiao had written his goal to notify the Hutt Civilization in advance. If it was just meeting her, given his position, the Hutt Civilization should not reject him.

Wolman immediately contacted the superiors. After a long call that lasted more than ten minutes, he exhaled deeply. The people above were not planning to settle this personally. They made him responsible for the welcoming and hosting of Black Star.

Seven days later, Han Xiao arrived in the Skywalker Star System in his spaceship, landing at the military port of one of their governance planets. The Hutt Civilization had received the notice long ago and basically cleared out the entire port. Wolman and others were waiting

The hatch opened, and Han Xiao and Reynold walked out. Wolman adjusted his clothes, approached with an elegant smile and reached out for a handshake.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I’m Wolman of the diplomatic team. On behalf of the Hutt Civilization, welcome."

"Yo, hello." Han Xiao shook his hand.

"Upon gaining knowledge of your arrival, my superiors were eager to welcome you personally. Unfortunately, your arrival is too sudden, and they just could not squeeze out the time during their hectic schedule. Therefore, I’m responsible for hosting you. Please understand," Wolman said with a very graceful tone.

Actually, this was just an excuse. The upper echelons of the Hutt Civilization did not want to meet Black Star. This was because when DarkStar was stirring chaos, the Hutt Civilization had secretly worked together with the DarkStar once. Once they heard that Black Star was visiting them personally, they felt somewhat guilty. Thus, they decided to let a unimportant official take care of Black Star in their place, while at the same time observing Black Star’s attitude, as well as why he wanted to see Rossellin.

However, of course, Wolman knew nothing about that. The way he saw it, this represented the Hutt Civilization’s attitude toward Black Star. Although they had followed the others and invited Black Star to build a sub-base there three years ago, they did not really take this nouveau riche too seriously. They kept their pride as a Star System civilization. Wolman was very satisfied with this attitude of theirs.

To Wolman, Black Star was just a nouveau riche.

Black Star was strong for sure, but he was not Beyond Grade A yet. He had just made use of the heated discussion three years ago and made the Black Star Army’s development grow rapidly. To him, this was exactly what a nouveau riche was. Technically, Black Star was just a native from a planet that lagged behind in all respects. Wolman, however, was an elite from a Star System civilization. With his sense of superiority, he did not think highly of the Black Star Army.

However, as a well-trained diplomat, this tiny belittling he had was perfectly hidden, and he maintained the basic respects.

"Don’t have to be so polite." Han Xiao waved his hand.

Wolman nodded. "We have received your notice. Rossellin is now locked up in the secret prison on this planet and can meet you anytime. Would you like to rest or see her first?"

"See her first."

"Okay, please follow me."

A hovering car with a government license was parked outside the dock. Han Xiao and Reynold followed Wolman in and headed to the prison Rossellin was in.

The inside of the car was stable and completely free of turbulence. Han Xiao chatted with Wolman on and off, while Reynold sat straight at the side.

Ralph had given him a super long holiday, so Han Xiao had more than enough time to settle his personal matters. Seven days ago, when he got Reynold’s mission and realized that Rossellin was someone he knew, he had immediately dropped all other arrangements and placed saving Rossellin at the top of his priority list.

Considering Rossellin’s identity, Han Xiao brought Reynold along as well. On the surface, it was so that the two of them could reunite, but it was actually to make Rossellin lower her guard.

Initially, although Reynold was rather important, Han Xiao did not see him as someone with any kind of extraordinary background. However, after seeing Reynold’s older sister, he knew immediately that he was going to treat Reynold like his brother!

"You’re about to see your long separated sister, nervous?" Han Xiao did not hide anything and spoke to Reynold with a voice that everyone in the car could hear.

"No." Reynold shook his head. "The impression I have of her is already very faint Even if we meet, there isn’t much to say between the two of us. Even after we save her, we will still just walk different paths."

"You want me to help you save Rossellin, but you’re not going to ask her to pay you back? It seems that your emotions for Rossellin are not as little as you say." Han Xiao smirked.

"Families should take care of each other. Even though she once abandoned me, when she’s in trouble, I should still help her," Reynold said with a serious face.

Ralph listened from aside and secretly memorized the information. Rossellin seems to be a family member of an important person under Black Star’s command. Maybe this is why Black Star’s here. I’ve got to report this to the superiors later.

After more than two hours, the hovering car entered a military base leading into an underground tunnel and stopped at the gate of an underground prison. The thick, bulky alloy gate was now open. The warden and the guards had been waiting there since long ago.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we’re here. Please let me lead the way for you."

Wolman got out of the car and opened the car door for Han Xiao. Then, he shared a few words with the warden before leading the way.

This prison was very technologically advanced. It used many galactic imprisonment measures. It was very quiet; the only sound was the buzzing made by the mechanical guards passing by. The ceiling was equipped with all kinds of automatic weapons that would lock on to any target with a heat signature. The security was tight.

Han Xiao appreciated the surroundings as he walked and learned quite a few things. He decided to go back and modify his Happy Little House after settling this issue.

After walking through many prison zones, they arrived at the deepest single person cell. They then stopped before the alloy cell door.

"The person you want to see is inside." Wolman nodded.

The warden opened the cell door and let Han Xiao and the others in. The space inside was not narrow. It was split into two areas with high strength transparent glass.

Compared to Reynold’s photos, Rossellin’s hair was now cut to centimeters short, and she wore a ragged prisoner uniform. However, her appearance was still as young; time did not leave any marks on her. With just one look, Han Xiao knew that this woman’s highest attribute was most likely Charm, maybe comparable with Feidin’s.

The cell was dark. As the strong light from outside the door shined in, Rossellin narrowed her eyes uncomfortably and looked at the few people on the other side of the glass. Although she was a prisoner, her face was extremely calm.

"Hmm, it has been 147 days since you guys last came to me. What do you want me to do this time?"

"Still recognize me?" Reynold asked.

Rossellin looked at Reynold. After looking for a while with narrowed eyes, shock appeared on her face.

"Are you possibly… my long dead dad?"

"I’m Reynold!"

"Oh, brother, so you’re still alive." Rossellin sighed with disappointment as if she was not surprised about Reynold appearing there at all. "What are you doing here?"

"I’m here to save you," Reynold said with a deep voice.

"After not seeing you for decades, you’re still just as stupid." Rossellin pointed at the warden on the side with her mouth and said, "Do you think he’s deaf?"

"His Excellency Black Star will try to get you out."

"Black Star?" Her brows raised slightly. "Never heard of him."

Han Xiao kept quiet at the side with a strange look on his face. The reunion of these two siblings was different from what he imagined. Shouldn’t they be hugging each other and crying?

Looking at Rossellin, he was still surprised.

He had not expected the future pillar member of the Silver Revolutionary Army to be a family member of one of his officers.

The Silver Revolutionary Army was the main storyline of a big version. The target of their revolution was not something small but the three Universal Civilizations. Since they were revolutionaries, they had to gain support from the people. Rossellin was an irreplaceable member known as the Preacher.

Even if he did not come, sooner or later, someone else would develop an interest in her ability and save her.

Rossellin was a key character of a major storyline, so she was of great importance to Han Xiao. Maybe he could interfere with the Silver Revolutionary Army storyline. According to the time, the Silver Revolutionary Army had not formed yet.

Even without Rossellin’s future identity, she still had huge potential. Although her Esper ability did not have much combat capability, she was an irreplaceable special talent in the fields of poisoning people’s minds and inciting the masses.

Her ability looked ordinary on surface, but the final form of this Esper ability was more than qualified to be listed in the Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty. It could turn an ideology terrifyingly contagious and conquer not with force but culture!

Although it had no lethality, it was a horrifying weapon that could overthrow any government!

Rossellin was born to be someone talented in revolution and religion!

Of course, it would also be useful in reinforcing the position of rulers or governments.

The people walked out of the cell, and the warden closed the cell door behind them.

"Your Excellency Black Star, do you have any other requests?" Wolman asked.

Han Xiao glanced at Reynold before touching his chin. "Indeed, I do have a favor to ask. I hope to bail Rossellin out. As you can see, she’s the sister of this officer of mine. According to my knowledge, she did not break the Hutt Civilization’s laws. You guys are just imprisoning her in place of the Ceciris civilization. As long as you’re willing to give bail, I can have a talk with the Ceciris people myself."

"Hehe, this is beyond my jurisdiction. I will have to report to the upper echelons. Please give me a moment."

Wolman was not surprised at all; he had already guessed Black Star’s intention earlier. He went to the side, took out the communicator, and called his superiors. After talking for a while, he hung up and went to Han Xiao with an apologetic expression.

"I’m sorry. This is an internal matter of our civilization. Rossellin is an important prisoner, and we cannot accept any form of bail."

Although Star System Civilizations treated Han Xiao with respect and wanted to establish a good relationship with him, they would not accept all of his requests. If it was just a normal prisoner, it would not be a big issue. However, Rossellin was an important chess piece even to the Hutt Civilization. Of course, they were not going to give her to Han Xiao just because he requested it.

"I see, never mind then." Han Xiao shook his head with disappointment.

"Thank you for your understanding."

Wolman had a bright smile on his face, but he was sneering in his mind.

You’re still not a Beyond Grade A, yet you want us to release someone with one sentence?

Do you really think you’re someone?

Chapter 699: This Leek Is Bleeding Internally

Since the Hutt superiors rejected him, he had no need to stay at the prison. Han Xiao expressed his intent to leave. Wolman asked him to stay longer for a few times but stopped at a suitable point. They took the hovering car back and headed to the dock.

The atmosphere in the car was silent; no one talked. Han Xiao closed his eyes and rested. Reynold sat at the side, wanting to speak but did not.

Wolman secretly looked at Han Xiao’s expression. He felt that Black Star was definitely unhappy since he had been rejected. However, he did not care about Black Star’s feelings. After all, all he did was convey the message from the upper echelons. If Black Star was unhappy about that, it would have nothing to do with him.

Furthermore, Wolman did not think that making Black Star unhappy was a big deal at all. Civilizations controlled the universe; no matter how strong Black Star was, he was not part of a government.

As a diplomat, he felt that he figured out what the superiors meant—the Hutt Civilization had no intention of wooing Black Star. Purple Crystal was already way ahead of them, and they had no chance to compete with a Star Cluster civilization.

So many Star System civilizations wanted to befriend Black Star, and they were just one of them. Godora had the closest relationship with Black Star among the Star System civilizations, while the Hutt Civilization was Godora’s competitor. No matter how they looked at it, Black Star would definitely not establish a close relationship with the Hutt Civilization.

Therefore, Wolman felt that the upper echelons knew that they did not have a chance, so they did not want to waste efforts wooing Black Star. They would not be able to get anything in return for Rossellin anyway, so why should they lower their heads and fulfil Black Star’s request? Like other Star System civilizations, they just had to give enough face to Black Star and treat the Black Star Army’s subdivision as a tie for a shallow relationship. That was all.

In Wolman’s eyes, Black Star wanting to take someone from him with just one sentence was a clear act of overconfidence.

Us Star System civilizations will indeed give you face, but we will not obey your every demand.

As Wolman was deducing the intention of his superiors, the hovering car finally arrived at the dock.

Han Xiao and Reynold got out of the car and boarded their spaceship with Wolman escorting them up.

Han Xiao stepped onto the gangway and was about to walk into the hatch. He suddenly turned around and looked at Wolman, who was standing on the dock.

"We will meet again very soon."

"We look forward to your next visit." Wolman had a sincere-looking but fake smile on his face.

The spaceship shook and quickly started. It followed the dock tunnel, turned into a high-speed stream of light, and disappeared.

As the spaceship left far away, Wolman wiped the smile from his face, pressed his stiff facial muscles, and turned around to wave at his team members.

"Let’s go."

Five days passed peacefully.

On this day, the delicate Wolman was spending his days in the Skywalker Star System Black Star Army subdivision as always when an urgent notification was sent to his email. A team from the Foreign Affairs Department was about to come to the Black Star Army’s subdivision. The email was to notify him to prepare the welcome.

"Strange, I wasn’t noticed beforehand about this. Why are they suddenly sending people to the Black Star Army subdivision?"

This notice did not follow the regular procedures, nor did it convey the purpose of these Foreign Affairs Department colleagues’ visit. Wolman was confused, but since it was a mission from above, he could only complete it.

Wolman brought along his team members, arranged the welcome, and arrived at the dock of the subdivision, waiting for the arrival of these colleagues.

This Black Star Army sub-base was built to be orbiting on the outer space track of the resource planet in order to monitor the harvesting team on the planet. The dock was a hovering galactic harbor built beside the sub-base. It was an independent space station.

After Wolman waited for more than half an hour, a government spaceship with the Hutt Civilization mark approached and stopped at the dock.

The spaceship stabilized, and the hatch slowly opened. A group of people in diplomat clothing accompanied a few Purple Crystal people down the gangway while chatting and laughing.

Wolman quickly went forward and introduced himself.

"This is the person in charge of the diplomatic matters with the Black Star Army subdivision, Wolman. These are Purple Crystal Civilization’s emissaries. We have just completed a handover task and are planning to rest here for a day," a diplomat said elegantly.

Purple Crystal Civilization emissaries! Wolman was shocked. Purple Crystal was the ruling civilization of Colton, and Hutt was just a Star System civilization under them. Purple Crystal specifically dispatching emissaries there meant that this was an important diplomatic task.

Wolman could not help but feel jealous of these Foreign Affairs Department colleagues of his who were chatting and laughing with the Purple Crystal emissaries. They had the opportunity to get in contact with the emissaries of Star Cluster civilizations, and they were active in the political stage between civilizations. Their job was more elegant and graceful, while he was made to take care of an armed force.

I will be transferred back sooner or later… Wolman comforted himself. Back when his superiors sent him to be in charge of the Black Star Army subdivision, it was definitely because they believed in his capabilities. A diplomatic elite like him would definitely return to the Foreign Affairs Headquarters in the future.

Just as he was about to invite the Purple Crystal emissaries to stay, a few armed officers escorted someone off the spaceship. Wolman turned to look and was instantly stunned.

The woman escorted there was the person whom he had just met together with Black Star a few days prior, Rossellin!

Wolman was shocked. He nudged one of his colleagues that accompanied the Purple Crystal emissaries and softly asked, "Why is she on your ship? Why did you bring her here?"

"You know her? This is a prisoner the Purple Crystal emissary specifically sent people to take charge of. She’s called Rossellin."

Wolman immediately thought of Black Star.

Could it be…

At this time, another spaceship landed. Wolman recognized this battleship; it was Black Star’s ride.

The hatch opened, and Han Xiao and Reynold walked down. The Purple Crystal emissaries instantly smiled and approached the two of them.

After chatting for a while with smiles on their faces, the Purple Crystal emissary waved his hand. A few armed personnel escorted Rossellin over to Han Xiao, opened the various constraints, and released her on the spot.

Rossellin rubbed her wrists, glanced at Reynold, and gave Han Xiao a deep look, not saying anything. Reynold then took her up onto the Blacklight Stealth.

Han Xiao turned around and noticed the stunned Wolman who was standing at the edge of the crowd, so he smiled and walked over.

"As I said, we meet again."

"You…" Wolman suddenly did not know what he should say to deal with this situation.

"It’s actually not that big a deal. Since your Hutt Civilization doesn’t allow bail, I had no choice but to let a civilization that does allow bail take over." Han Xiao raised his brows.

Wolman’s lips shivered, and he forced out a rigid smile. There were thousands of curses in his heart, but he did not dare say any of them.

From the side of his vision, he saw that his colleagues were smiling brightly as if they had known all along and he was the only one that did not.

At this moment, he felt that his most precious sense of superiority was shattered into pieces, by the Hutt Civilization government who had gifted it to him in the first place.

Han Xiao did not look at him anymore. He turned around and shook hands with the Purple Crystal emissaries, chatted for a while, boarded his spaceship, and left with Rossellin.

Wolman clenched his fists and forced out a smile to face the Purple Crystal emissariesdoing his job was more important.

After finally settling these emissaries down, Wolman returned to the office. He was the only one there.

Sitting in his chair, Wolman exhaled deeply. He wanted to suppress his thoughts and continue to read his book, but he realized that he could not concentrate on it at all.

Every time Wolman thought of Black Star, he felt unpleasant. He comforted himself that this was a matter for the superiors and had nothing to do with him.

There were no conflicts between him and Black Star. Fortunately for him, he had maintained his diplomatic etiquette. No one knew how he had ridiculed him in his mind, and no one would know that he felt embarrassed.

Beep beep!

This time, Wolman’s communicator rang. He opened it, and to his surprise, it was a message from his direct boss.

"His Excellency Black Star specifically told us that he’s very satisfied with your services and that it made him very comfortable. He also hopes to see you again next time. Therefore, your transfer request is temporarily postponed. You will continue to be in charge of the diplomatic tasks with the Black Star Army’s subdivision…"

Clank!

A few team members outside were just about to push open the door when they suddenly heard sounds of someone smashing things coming from the office.

The few of them hastily pushed the door open and saw Wolman’s usually calm face filled with rage. The floor beside his table was in a mess. The crystal cup that he always used was shattered into pieces, scattered around the floor, and the green drink had spilled over the physical books that he had always taken very good care of.

In the Blacklight Stealth’s main hall, three people sat on a circular sofa in a triangle. Rossellin’s eyes kept moving between Han Xiao and Reynold. Reynold was sitting straight and looking directly ahead. Han Xiao leaned back with one hand on the back of the sofa and the other carrying a wine glass, sizing Rossellin up with an interested look on his face.

"What do you want me to do for you for saving me? Come on, don’t be shy, tell me."

Rossellin broke the silence first.

Reynold frowned. "I just wanted to save you…"

"Enough. Keep those lies for yourself." Rossellin interrupted Rossellin, crossed her legs, and said with a mocking expression, "I don’t know who this ‘Excellency Black Star’ is. In order to get me out, you guys even contacted Purple Crystal, so the cost is probably quite high. I don’t believe that such a big price paid would just be to fulfil an idiot subordinate’s wish. Hehe, you probably told this Black whatever about my ability… Sorry, your nickname is too stupid. I’m too lazy to say it."

Is this woman’s zodiac animal hedgehog? Stabbing whoever she wants…

Han Xiao remembered that Rossellin’s personality was not like this during the Silver Revolutionary Army era in his previous life.

Reynold said with a deep voice, "I asked His Excellency Black Star to save you in exchange for myself. Know your place!"

"Oh." Rossellin curled her lips and raised her tone. "So, you thought I’d be grateful to you?"

"You!" Reynold was exasperated.

"I’m quite curious, what made this Black whatever guy accept this kind of request? Which part of you is so important to him?" Rossellin sized Reynold up.

"I’m a Calamity Grade now!"

"Oh, you’ve grown up, I see." Rossellin opened her mouth wide with exaggeration before clapping a few times without any signs of being sincere. She shrugged and said, "So, you’re saying that you’re very important to him?"

Reynold could not reply. Han Xiao was right beside him. He could not praise himself and say that he was important to him.

"Ahem." Han Xiao stopped the conversation between the two of them and said, "Contacting the Purple Crystal Civilization isn’t difficult for me. You’ve been imprisoned for too long, so you’ve never heard of me."

Without a doubt, he was not going to use force. Even with his current position, if he actually attacked a civilization, he would still receive punishments.

In terms of retrieving the sub-base to express his attitude, it would give him a bad name. The other partner galactic civilizations would feel that he was forcing a government. He was not a Beyond Grade A yet, so he should not be too domineering. That would not be beneficial to maintaining stable partnerships.

Resolving this matter was actually very easy. Since the Hutt Civilization could take Rossellin from Ceciris, the Purple Crystal Civilization could also take her from them. It was just a handover.

Purple Crystal took him much more seriously than Hutt as he was a partner of Purple Crystal. Hutt, however, knowing that they had no chance to compete, were unwilling to woo him, so they did not want to give him face.

However, proving their loyalty to Purple Crystal was so much more beneficial. Therefore, when Purple Crystal took over the matter, the Hutt Civilization immediately agreed.

Efficient and effective, this was Han Xiao’s solution. If a player had to do this mission, they would basically have to break into the prison by force.

"I see, you seem to be someone very important." Rossellin raised her brows. "It looks like I need to study the history of the past decade or so."

Rossellin stood up and came before Han Xiao. She snatched his wine class and gulped it down. Then, she casually threw the empty cup away. She sat back down, burped, waved her hands, and said, "I’m thirsty, so I drank some. For such an important person like you, I’m sure you won’t mind."

Han Xiao turned to look at Reynold. "Your sister has quite an interesting personality, like a rascal."

"Ever since she was little, she has been willful, caustic, and mean, never considering the feeling of the others!" Reynold could not hold back anymore and started to complain. "Therefore, when she became a careerist that toyed with an entire civilization, I wasn’t even surprised!"

"That’s right, I’m a careerist, a caustic rascal. Countless people are going to suffer now that you’ve let me out. Are you regretting saving me, my dear little brother?" Rossellin made a funny face.

"No." Reynold disdained quarreling with her.

"Tsk, I’m a little touched. It’s really true that no matter how you hurt your family, your family will still be willing to be taken advantage of." Rossellin stretched lazily. "Since you guys aren’t going to make use of me, does that mean I can leave anytime I want? If you reject, it means you are planning to use me. Of course, you don’t have to be shameful about your hypocrisy; I’ve seen this kind of thing way too many times."

Reynold turned to Han Xiao. He only wanted to save Rossellin. As for where Rossellin would go in the future, he did not want to care about it at all. Han Xiao was the one that could make the decision to let her go.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and suddenly said, "You built a new religion in your hometown and brainwashed countless people, making them worship you. Anyone would think you’re a careerist."

"Hmm, you have such sharp eyes, just like every normal person in the world, and you like to repeat obvious things." Rossellin’s face was filled with mockery. "What, are you planning to judge my actions? Tell me then, I will try my absolute very best to repent for one minute."

"I don’t think you’re a careerist; you’re a reformer." Han Xiao leaned forward and stared into Rossellin’s eyes, speaking with a calm and normal tone.

The moment he spoke, Rossellin’s expression stiffened, and a tint of anxiety flashed through her eyes. She was stunned.

Chapter 700: Rossellin Compound Fertilizer

"Interesting, this is the first time someone has used an outright lie to praise me." Rossellin barely squeezed out a sneer to cover for the panic inside.

"You can disguise yourself with ambition, but you can't fool everyone. You didn't create a new religion and modify people's faith because of ambition. You have other motives." Han Xiao smiled.

Han Xiao had limited knowledge of the Rossellin before his eyes, but the players had gathered quite a lot of her information during the Silver Revolution version in his previous life. When Han Xiao recognized Rossellin, he recalled that information. Some of it was Rossellin's past experiences. It seemed like she had told others about her past before. Although she did not tell the players where her home was, she did talk about what she did in her home and what her motive was.

According to that information, Han Xiao knew that Rossellin's real motive had nothing to do with ambition. She did not control the faith of others for power. Han Xiao knew Rossellin better than herself.

Anyone who could become the backbone of the Silver Revolutionary Army, apart from having special skills, had a heart not satisfied with the status quo and a unique aspiration.

Rossellin was shocked. This was the first person to see through her disguise. She quickly held down her surprise then stabilized her mind with alertness and vigilance—this had been her habit for many years.

Black Star has only seen me twice. He definitely has a reason for saying these things... He must be exaggerating. How could he know what I'm thinking?

The real motive for creating a religion and gathering believers had always been Rossellin's deepest secret. She had never told anyone, and she did not believe that Black Star could guess correctly.

Reynold turned his head and looked at Han Xiao with suspicious eyes—did his sister really have some other motives?

"Your ability is to subtly rewrite people's mental outlook. Its impact isn't very strong, and you can't completely manipulate others to your likings. However, you can put all kinds of ideas in their minds," Han Xiao, with a confident look on his face, said slowly. "The mind is intangible, but it's like the strings that manipulate puppets, affecting every aspect of an individual. Whether one is loyal or rebellious, sincere or hypocritical, optimistic or pessimistic, depends greatly on one's mind. The reason that the same environment creates different people is because of the mind, too."

As he was speaking, he pointed at Rossellin, who was forcing herself to stay calm, and smiled. "Using your Esper ability, you are able to give them new ideas that are very contagious. In the eyes of your home government, your idea is a virus. But in my view, your idea is a seed, a seed that can turn around the thousands of ways in which the entire race can develop toward."

"You..." Rossellin's expression changed drastically.

Without waiting for her to respond, Han Xiao continued.

"The racial personality of a civilization depends partly on its nature and partly on the traditional ideas that have been passed down from ancient times, which cannot be controlled by future generations and will change independently at the various stages of the history as it develops.

"These ideas left over from history will dissolve into the blood of this race and become their spiritual identity. History only happens once, and a race doesn't have a second chance. It can even be said that there is no opportunity for them to choose. From a macro perspective, the culture and character of this civilization is almost random; they're not necessarily optimal results out of the infinite variables. Or maybe there's no such thing as an optimal result.

"I call you a reformer because I know that you didn't set up a religion in your hometown for power but to reform your own race. To be honest, I am a little impressed by your aspiration. Your goal isn't to reform a government or system but the cultural ideology and spiritual goal of the race, thus changing the spiritual identity of the entire race!"

This information was like a hurricane that struck Reynold. He opened his mouth wide and stared at Rossellin, dumbfounded. If what Han Xiao said was true, his sister's goal was indeed unbelievably huge.

As if Rossellin had been struck by lightning, she was petrified, and her face was covered in disbelief.

Han Xiao smiled in his mind. Those were the motives as Rossellin explained them in his previous life. Using them to trick her was extremely effective.

After a pause, he went on and said, "Whether it's reforming the system or reforming the government, its effects won't last as long as reforming the spiritual identity of an entire race. Many of the problems are because of the people. Character determines destiny. Without external influence, this law applies to a civilization.

"History has been established. In the course of a civilization's development, there is basically no opportunity to change its character. What you have been doing is implanting new ideas and giving them the opportunity to change through the form of your Esper ability and religion. This is your 'Race Transformation Plan.'"

Han Xiao touched his chin. "Hmm, however, you're just an individual in this race. In the eyes of others, you have absolutely no right to change the minds of everyone. Through growing up, everyone has created their own history. You can't impact the deep-rooted traditions that have been around for thousands of years. Therefore, you became a heretic, a sinner."

In his view, Rossellin's actions were basically leading her to become a saint!

Han Xiao could not help but think, You denied history and the racial spirit that has been passed down. No wonder they locked you up—your ideas are way too dangerous.

Nonetheless, this woman's thinking was not wrong. Assuming that there were no Confucius or Mencius in the history of his previous life, the ideas passed down by the people of the world would be different after thousands of years, and the logic of people would change to a certain extent as well.

"The easiest way to change the spiritual outlook of a group is religion and education, so you chose to establish a religion, gathering faith and subtly changing people's character. This is your real motivation," Han Xiao said, looking at Rossellin. "Am I right?"

Rossellin's hands were shaking. She took a deep breath and looked at Han Xiao with great complexity.

"You're... right." Rossellin's voice became low. Her cynical tone from earlier had completely vanished. Now, Han Xiao finally felt a faint aura of a religious pope in her.

She looked straight into Han Xiao's eyes and said, "I am not noble. The parents of Reynold and I died during a political parade. The Ceciris Civilization disappointed me again and again, so I wanted to change something. You're right, I don't have the right to change the spiritual identity of the whole race, and they don't necessarily need me. But if no one did anything extraordinary under all that pressure, nothing would change. I created a religion that lasted many years, and I only changed the character of a small group of people. Through the religion and my Esper ability, I made them positive, I made them grasp the present, and I made them better. As long as the religion continued, even without my Esper ability in the future, these ideas would have become more and more popular. Unfortunately, it provoked a backlash..."

After so many years of suffering, Rossellin had become deeply wary of everyone. Her harsh words and cynical attitude were her protective disguise—too many people lied, too many wanted to use her. She promised herself to never open up to anyone ever again. Even if she was misunderstood, she would not defend herself.

But now, for the first time, Rossellin had spoken out.

She gazed at Han Xiao, her heart filled with complex emotions. There was shock, relief, and a hint of happiness of meeting someone who understood her. Those were the deepest secrets of her heart that she had never told anyone else, but Black Star had seen through her so easily. This was the first time that Rossellin had met someone that knew her so well; she almost lost her cool.

Speechless, Reynold looked at Rossellin with disbelief. He looked at her from head to toe again and again, seemingly wondering if his sister had been swapped. He could not imagine Rossellin having such huge aspirations and dreams.

Seeing that Rossellin had admitted he was right, Han Xiao was secretly excited.

This fertilization method is just as good as it used to be. This is probably how the Silver Revolutionary Army fooled her in my previous life!

"Ah-choo!"

On Planet Aquamarine, Bennett sneezed all of a sudden.

When Rossellin finished, the room became quiet. The few of them did not speak for a moment. Han Xiao knocked the table and spoke first.

"So, what do you plan to do in the future? You can't go back to Ceciris, and you're still considered Purple Crystal's prisoner. I bailed you out, so I can't just let you run around wherever you like."

Rossellin turned and glanced at Reynold. She then smiled lightly. "I see. After saying so much, you still want me to stay."

"You're a talent. I like talent."

Han Xiao, of course, did not have to deny it.

"Since my brother works for you, even if you want to use me, you won't do anything excessive. Okay, you used your connections to save me, so I owe you one. My brother is my brother; I won't use him to repay you. Also, I don't have much combat capability, so I certainly won't be a match for such an important person like you..."

Rossellin stretched and went back to her cynical attitude. She deliberately gave Han Xiao a vaguely seductive wink and said, "Since I won't be able to run anyway, I don't have a choice. I will lend my body to you as a tool. Use it as you will, don't be shy."

"Okay." Han Xiao nodded normally, but inside, he was screaming, Still putting on a show? You think I can't see that huge +80 Favorability? Would it kill you to be honest about how grateful you are? Would it‽

The biggest problem was settled. Han Xiao let Reynold take Rossellin to rest, eat something, and replenish her energy. After spending so many years in captivity, her body was rather weak, and she was in need of recovery.

After the two of them left, Han Xiao stayed in the hall alone. He tapped the sofa with his fingers, pondering how to utilize Rossellin's special talent.

Rossellin's Esper ability was a perfect fit for ideological construction. He felt that it could be used to strengthen the Black Star Army's corporate culture, to create a few slogans like 'Let the light of Black Star shine on every corner of the universe' and 'May Black Star rise as usual'. The Bloodshed Land also had special talents for ideological construction.

That means, Rossellin can take on the job of political commissar?

Han Xiao touched his lips with excitement.

To make the leeks grow healthily with spiritual construction...

That would be a strong compound fertilizer!

Also, her ability is very special. The Silver Revolutionary Army will still target her in the future, and I can't keep someone with such enormous aspirations forever. Since that's the case, if she will still become a core member of the Silver Revolutionary Army like in my previous life, maybe I can build and maintain good relations with them and not be their enemy.

As the Silver Revolutionary Army was the main storyline of a major version, they were, of course, very powerful. Although Han Xiao did not have any intention of joining them and trying to overthrow the three Universal Civilizations, he did not want to be their enemies.

Maybe through Rossellin, he would be able to discover the Silver Revolutionary Army's tracks before they completely formed, thus being able to respond in advance.

Mr. Han pondered over the idea and did not see an issue with it. He then opened the interface.

In the mission list, the mission [Reformer] was completed, and he had already received the reward. He now had a complete Reynold Character Summon Card.

Character Summon Card - Reynold—[Perfect Mechanical Sense]

Total Machinery Affinity multiplied by 1.4. (Includes basic value, bonuses from passive abilities, and talents. This effect applies to the total value.)

When enhancing machines using Mechanical Force, the Grade of the machine will be temporarily increased by one or two Grades, up to Pink Rare Grade.

+4 levels to all Mechanic class active abilities. This effect can exceed the level limit.

Duration: 16 hours

Usages: 0/3

Remark: In your senses, every machine is a world of ecological balance.

Three usages, sixteen hours duration each. Quite long lasting. It seems that this type of Character Summon Card also takes into account the time to build machines. It can be used both for combat and for building.

Han Xiao was quite satisfied. With this Character Summon Card, there would basically be no problem in making a piece of orange equipment. All he had to do was complete the blueprint mission and obtain the silver legacy blueprint.

Looking at its effects again, Han Xiao was increasingly envious of Reynold.

I want the real [Perfect Mechanical Sense] talent...

...

After rescuing Rossellin, Han Xiao split up with those two and let Reynold take Rossellin back to their headquarters and settle her down. While piloting the spaceship and leaving the Colton Star Cluster, he headed to the location of the blueprint mission.

Be it the Black Star Army matters, Vilna, or Rossellin, none of them were as important as his Class Advancement mission. He had to become stronger to develop his organization and position even further. Since he was close to completing the Class Advancement mission, he dropped everything else and focused on completing the Class Advancement.

As Han Xiao left the Colton Star Cluster, a pair of eyes were staring at his whereabouts from a dark place that he could not see.

Chapter 701: Fangs

Taralam Star Cluster, 0358 Wormhole Sector.

Big and small blue-black wormholes with fluctuating space coordinates existed in this area, tearing the space around them. A small spacetime carefully travelled in this unstable space area. It was Han Xiao’s ride.

In the central area of the Shattered Star Ring was a huge wormhole group that was under the Taralam Star Cluster area. This dangerous area was called the Wormhole Zone. There were very few people around. The various Star Cluster civilizations had stationed people there and built wormhole observation stations, classifying the Wormhole Zone into hundreds of sectors.

The Wormhole Zone in the Shattered Star Ring connected to many places around the universe. The job of the wormhole observation stations was to measure where some of those wormholes led. However, due to the wormholes being extremely unstable, old wormholes disappeared regularly, and new wormholes appeared just as frequently. Therefore, the progress of the measurements was very slow.

According to the official data, till this day, they had only completed the measurement for 1 in 2,400,000 of all the wormholes.

Han Xiao current target was the observation station of 0358 Wormhole Sector. The distributor of the level 180 silver legacy blueprint mission was the Mechanic that maintained this wormhole observation station.

As he passed by a bunch of wormholes, a small space station appeared in his vision under the wormholes’ orbits. Han Xiao sent a landing request to the space station, which was very quickly approved. He piloted the spaceship to dock at the space station and entered the port passage. After sliding on the magnetic tracks of the space station for a while in a narrow passage, he finally entered the port.

Han Xiao disembarked from the spaceship and greeted the maintenance personnel of the port.

"Your Excellency Black Star, have you come to look for Professor Harrofal again?" a maintenance officer asked.

"Hmm, where is he now?" Han Xiao nodded.

"You came at the right time. Professor Harrofal followed the measurement team out to collect wormhole data some time ago and only returned two days ago. He’s now inside the research lab, conducting experiments."

"Thanks." Han Xiao smiled and left the dock, heading toward the research lab of the wormhole observation station.

This wormhole observation station did not belong to Klent or Purple Crystal but another Star Cluster civilization of the Shattered Star Ring that did not take part in the secret war and was semi-neutral.

Harrofal was a research-type Mechanic that was not good at combat, a professor of a government-owned mechanic education institution of this Star Cluster civilization. He had always been on the frontlines of technology, studying all kinds of subjects. In order to study the wormhole group, he had deliberately requested to do maintenance at an observation station. He was the distributor of the blueprint mission.

Han Xiao had already completed the blueprint mission up to the seventh round. He had come to this observation station many times, so the people there were already familiar with him.

Arriving at the research lab smoothly, Han Xiao announced his identity outside the locked door. After waiting for a while, the door opened, and Harrofal walked out. He gave Han Xiao a stare and said unhappily, "You again, you’re disturbing my experiment."

"Experiments can be done anytime, but you don’t get to see me every day." Han Xiao laughed.

Harrofal was an old man with claret skin. His hair and beard were all white. He was very old, but his back was straight, and he looked more fit than some younger men. This was a tough old man.

To the Mechanic class, knowledge was power. Harrofal had studied the various mechanic theories very deeply and was quite talented. Furthermore, he had studied them for so many years, so it was very normal that he was a Grade A Mechanic. However, Harrofal had always been researching and studying technology; he rarely fought anyone.

Although his level was not low, he had many subclasses similar to (Scholar]. His combat capability was among the lowest in Grade A.

A Star System civilization would have dozens of government Grade A Supers. Thus, the Star Cluster civilizations naturally had dozens of times more Grade A Supers. After Han Xiao entered Calamity Grade, he had basically only come into contact with people of the same level, so it looked like there were many Calamity Grades. Actually, compared to the huge number of Grade B and Grade C Supers, the number of Calamity Grades was still very low.

The Star Cluster civilizations had relatively more Grade A Supers, so they could afford to have some talents that were not required to fight, such as Harrofal, who had low combat capability and focused on research and developments.

Although Harrofal always focused on research, he knew that Black Star was also a master Mechanic, so he had respect for him. He temporarily paused his studies and invited Han Xiao to the guest room to chat.

After chatting for a while, Han Xiao moved the topic to the blueprint mission. This silver legacy blueprint was Harrofal’s personal belonging. Han Xiao had made an agreement with him long ago that as long as he helped him do some stuff, Harrofal would be willing to teach the blueprint to Han Xiao. The mission was at round seven.

Harrofal thought for a while before giving his request. A notification popped up on Han Xiao’s interface.

He looked at the new round for the missionit was not difficult, just cumbersome.

Han Xiao delayed no longer. He ended the chat and bade farewell to Harrofal. He left the observation station and immediately headed to complete the mission.

The level 180 silver blueprint mission had ten rounds in total. To Han Xiao, it was not dangerous at all; he could complete them as long as he spent the time.

In the next month, Han Xiao travelled around, returning and leaving the observation station, and focused on completing one mission requirement after another. Ralph had given him a very long holiday this time, so he had plenty of time.

While he was doing the missions, he did not meet any accidents; it went very smoothly. In just over ten days, the blueprint mission in the mission list was finally shown to be ‘Completed’. Han Xiao immediately returned to the observation station and found Harrofal.

Harrofal took Han Xiao to his private room, dug through a bunch of stuff, and took out a square-shaped mechanical safe. He inserted his own Mechanical Force as the password, and the mechanical parts of the safe started to move like a Rubik’s Cube. After a while, the safe opened.

Harrofal took out a thick deck of blueprints from inside, shook it a bit, and placed it on the table.

"Alright, according to our agreement, this blueprint is now yours. It’s weird; you’ve been busy fighting the war these few years, yet you squeezed out the time to do things for me. Does this blueprint have some sort of important use to you?"

"You can say that." Han Xiao nodded.

Harrofal saw that Han Xiao was not planning to explain further, so he did not continue asking. He flipped the blueprints on the table and said, "This is what you asked for. I got this from someone else, so it’s not really a secret. Although it’s interesting technology, it’s not very advanced. It seems to be a blueprint passed down by a Mechanic from many years

ago."

"Let me take a quick look."

Han Xiao scanned through the blueprint. A progress bar for reading instantly popped up on the interface. His Intelligence was extremely high, so his reading fast was speedy.

In less than a minute, he had read through this complex blueprint. With the interface, as long as he had a high enough Intelligence, the efficiency of learning a blueprint would be hundreds of times faster than regular Mechanics.

Standing at the side, Harrofal thought that Han Xiao was just looking at it briefly. Never would he know that Han Xiao had already mastered the knowledge of this blueprint in just less than a minute.

You have received [Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon Blueprint] x 1.

You have learned a new blueprint, [Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon)!

Finally… Han Xiao took a deep breath and looked at the blueprint introduction on the interface.

Legacy blueprints all had rather lame names. The Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon was a level 180 machine. It was a planet-level strategic weapon for Cannon Masters. As a Mechanic, he could use it as well.

Most energy cannons fired burning high-energy particle streams while the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon’s attacks were extremely cold. According to the blueprint introduction, at the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon’s highest power output, one attack could send an entire planet into the Ice Age. Although its destructive power was not as high as actual Planetary Destroyers, it was still a very strong weapon.

Maybe because the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon was very old, it did not have a very high knowledge requirement. Among the Cutting-Edge Knowledges, it only required [Abnormal State Energy) and (Controllable Annihilation Weapons). Fortunately, Han Xiao knew both, so he did not have to find new Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

"Hmm, this thing needs quite a lot of rare materials. I’ll have to go back to build it.

Glancing at the cost of it, Han Xiao tutted. The cost of this cannon was probably even higher than proper Planetary Destroyers.

The development of technology was meant to build high power weapons with low costs. The older blueprints basically had high power and even higher costs. After all, the technology back then had not been as advanced.

However, is a problem that can be solved with money even considered a problem?

I’m rich!

Putting away the blueprint, Han Xiao nodded and said, "I shall get going."

"Don’t you want to stay a while to chat before leaving? I still want to discuss some technology with you."

"Probably not, I have some things to do."

"Sigh, alright then. I’ll send you off to the dock. If you have the time in the future, feel free to chat with me anytime. You have my communication number.

Harrofal felt a little sad. He quite liked chatting with Han Xiao. Both of them were master Mechanics, and they had infinite topics to talk about.

However, the moment they left the room, the lights in the corridor became red warning alarm lights. A piercing alarm echoed in the entire observation station.

Ohm!

"Enemy attack! Enemy attack!"

Harrofal’s face drastically changed. Before he could speak, the entire observation station trembled violently, and Harrofal almost staggered.

Right after, a deafening sound of explosion came from far away.

Boom!

The vigorous flames quickly expanded in their direction, filling the corridor.

Han Xiao frowned. Nanoparticles climbed on his palm and turned into armor. He flipped his hand around, and a blue oval shaped psionic shield appeared, easily blocking the flames. He then turned and looked at Harrofal.

"The enemy is definitely bombarding this place from outside. Let’s leave the observation station first."

Harrofal had very little experience against enemies, but he was not so inexperienced that he would panic in such situations. He equipped his own mechanical suit and crashed through the corridor, penetrating the exterior armor of the observation station and flying out. Han Xiao activated the Mountain Ape mechanical suit and followed him.

The two of them finally saw what was happening after leaving the observation station. Their expressions changed.

A fleet had surrounded the observation station from all directions. It had at least five hundred battleships, and they were all firing at the observation station. The protective shield was almost torn apart instantly as high energy beams penetrated the observation station.

The next moment, the fire expanded, and the observation station exploded, shattering into pieces.

"No, my research lab!" Harrofal’s expression changed drastically as he yelled with heartache.

"Sh\*t, my spaceship!" Han Xiao’s eyes twitched.

Reynold had flown the Blacklight Stealth back, so he was just using a normal small spaceship. Nonetheless, Han Xiao had still stored some Army Boxes in it. It would be a huge loss if they were destroyed too. Although he was not short of money at all, wasting was still shameful!

Han Xiao raised his hand. The space around him rippled, and Army Boxes arrived one after another through hyperdrive. Han Xiao counted them and was relieved.

The outside of the Army Boxes had suffered some damage, but the compressed orbs inside were undamaged. The Army Boxes not only had hyperdrive devices equipped but also protective shields. This was originally to prevent the enemy from attacking the Army Boxes, but it had come in handy this time.

The entire observation station turned into scrap; only a few Supers survived. The attack was too sudden. The people inside the observation station could not react at all.

As this was a space station for research, it had limited defensive measures. After all, not many people would deliberately attack a wormhole observation station set up by a Star Cluster civilization. Furthermore, this was the Wormhole Zone. The unstable wormhole group was a natural line of defense. Almost no one would battle there.

"Who are these people? Why did they attack us?" Harrofal was shocked and furious.

Han Xiao was very curious too. He instinctively felt that these enemies were there for him-he had almost developed a habit of being assaulted throughout the years.

He frowned and looked at the fleet. As he was about to speak, he received a message on his mechanical suit.

"We finally meet again, Black Star!"

This voice, it’s a little bit familiar!

Han Xiao looked over.

His vision passed through the universe and locked onto a person from the fleet. After clearly seeing this person’s appearance, Han Xiao was shocked and surprised.

This person was his old enemy that had been missing for many years—the DarkStar leader!

How did he appear there?

Chapter 702: Lord of Fallen Ark

Ever since Godora's pursuit for the DarkStar leader ended with no results, Han Xiao had not seen the DarkStar leader. No one knew where he was hiding. But now he had suddenly appeared, even bringing a fleet. It seemed he had risen from the ashes.

Han Xiao frowned. The DarkStar leader definitely knew his whereabouts and had an exceptional intelligence channel. He should be working with a very strong organization.

DarkStar will only have a chance to target Godora if I'm eliminated. As for the organization working with DarkStar, it's probably an organization that has attempted to assassinate me before. Their goal is the same, so they easily came to an agreement…

Han Xiao thought quickly. From this, he deduced that the DarkStar leader only appeared to attack him because he was absolutely confident of succeeding. With so many failed assassination attempts, they would definitely be very cautious.

This small fleet around him was basically no threat to him. After all, his mechanical army was not for decoration. However, Han Xiao did not let his guard down even a bit; rather, he was very wary. He felt that the DarkStar leader definitely had an unknown trump card.

Han Xiao had no intention of chatting. The Army Boxes opened one after another, and an enormous mechanical army expanded like the tide, overwhelming the DarkStar leader's fleet with its size.

Without hesitation, Han Xiao struck. Countless cannon fire lights seemed to have illuminated the universe. His storm of counter attacks tore dozens of battleships into pieces in an instant!

With his mechanical army that had millions of machines, as well as his various talents and Mechanical Force bonuses, Han Xiao was a one-man galactic army. He could destroy an entire fleet alone.

Countless mechanical guards surrounded Han Xiao, forming layers and layers of shields. The fleet's attack could not penetrate the shield at all.

Harrofal was protected inside too. He looked around at the mechanical army that filled his vision and could not help but think, How rich!

Within a short while, these hundreds of battleships were almost wiped out, but Han Xiao was frowning.

The battle being this easy made him even more alert. He did not believe that the DarkStar leader would attack him without any preparation.

How could such a small fleet eliminate him, someone that even gave a Star Cluster civilization headaches?

At this time, the DarkStar leader suddenly gestured at Han Xiao from far away in the midst of dodging attacks from the mechanical army. A few strange magic waves landed on Han Xiao in an instant.

You have been attacked by the DarkStar Leader's [Chain of Pain—Secret]. Judging MYS… failed. Your MYS is lower than the opponent. This spell is effective!

[Chain of Pain—Secret]: When the opponent takes damage, your health will decrease as well. For every 1% health the opponent loses, you will lose 0.55% – 0.7% health.

You have been attacked by the DarkStar Leader's [Life Absorption—Transfer]. Judging MYS… failed. Your MYS is lower than the opponent. This spell is effective!

[Life Absorption—Transfer]: When you recover health, the recovery effect decreases by 30%. The opponent will gain the 30% recovery you have lost. When you should recover 1,000 health points, you will only recover 700 health points, and the opponent will recover 300 health points.

You have been attacked by the DarkStar Leader's [Heart Malediction—Collapse]. Judging MYS… failed. Your MYS is lower than the opponent. This spell is effective. You have entered the [Mental Collapse] state!

[Mental Collapse]: -40% Psychological Resistance. You have lost control of your body and are unable to move. Duration: 6.2 seconds.

The Mechanical Force all over Han Xiao's body suddenly became still. He could not move his entire body. Han Xiao suddenly recalled that he still had the DarkStar leader's Character Summon Card, and its effect was also this [Heart Malediction—Collapse].

As he could not move at all, the mechanical army lost the Mechanical Force bonuses temporarily. The pressure on the DarkStar leader was immediately reduced. He quickly escaped the encirclement. In the process, his magic shield was focus fired and shattered time after time. He lost some health, so through [Chain of Pain—Secret], Han Xiao's health decreased as well.

Han Xiao looked at the combat information and quickly calculated in his mind.

Chain of Pain reduces health by percentage. The amount of health I lose is about 60% of the DarkStar leader's on average. However, my total health is more than double his, and the health recovery of Life Absorption relies on health points. For every 700 health points I lose, he recovers 300 health points, but our recovery speed is about the same in terms of percentage…

Thus, as long as he recovered health, the health of both sides would reduce at about the same speed with his health reducing at a slightly slower speed at most.

It did not seem difficult to break this cycle—he just had to not recover any health.

This time, the DarkStar leader raised his hand. A warm light shone on his body. His wounds healed, and his health went up slowly.

Han Xiao frowned. If the enemy healed himself, he would not share that healing. This way, in order to kill the DarkStar leader, he would have to take some risks…

Of course, it would be much easier to just capture him.

The DarkStar leader's style was clearly a Mage focused on Curse-type spells. No matter what, he was one of the boss characters in Version 2.0. This ability of his was more difficult to deal with than Ember's. It was more suitable for duels, too.

Capture him first, think later.

Han Xiao decided not to act recklessly.

No matter how strong this cycle was, the DarkStar leader did not have infinite energy. Both Chain of Pain and Life Absorption required energy to sustain. The millions of mechanical soldiers would be able to make him run out of energy easily.

The effect of Heart Malediction quickly disappeared, and Han Xiao regained control of his body. He controlled the mechanical army to surround and intercept the DarkStar leader. The DarkStar leader began struggling once again.

Due to Chain of Pain, Han Xiao did not plan on killing him but was reducing the DarkStar leader's mana, which was the reason that the DarkStar leader could barely hang on. Otherwise, he would have been obliterated by the rounds of True Damage.

Han Xiao did not plan on using the DarkStar leader's Character Summon Card. The DarkStar leader's main attribute was Mystery, so his Mystery was way much higher than Han Xiao's. The judgment would definitely fail.

Did he feel that he's become stronger and felt confident in killing me alone? Is he that reckless?

Although the DarkStar leader's abilities shocked him, it was not very threatening. Looking at the DarkStar leader, who was being heavily surrounded, Han Xiao could not stop guessing what his trump card was.

Suddenly, a sense of alarm appeared in his heart. The DarkStar leader took out a black bead from his wrist. Its texture was like a crystal. The bead was filled with dense black fog, and in the center was a red dot of light.

The next moment, the DarkStar leader crushed the bead. A lump of black fog splashed out together with the red dot of light, quickly turning into a completely black, human-shaped creature. Black smoke was oozing from all over its body. It had no face, and the middle of where its face was supposed to be was a blinking red dot.

A creepy and strong aura swept out. Han Xiao felt all his hair stand on end as if he was targeted by some evil being.

This was a pressure generated from the difference in the hierarchy of life!

"What is that!" Harrofal had been watching and doing nothing, but he was so shocked that he could not help but exclaim in the communication channel. Subconsciously, he entered his rusty battle posture.

Han Xiao did not answer him, but his face became extremely grave.

With his strength right now, only one type of being could give him this kind of pressure…

Beyond Grade A!

The mechanical army fired another round of attacks at the DarkStar leader and the human shaped black fog beside him. The black fog silhouette moved. It grabbed onto the DarkStar leader's shoulder, and with a flash of red light, the two of them suddenly teleported and appeared at another location, dodging the attacks.

"This bead is indeed useful!" The DarkStar leader immediately felt relieved.

This black fog silhouette was an Esper doppelganger of the Lord of Fallen Ark. In order to fuse the Esper abilities on the Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty, he absorbed countless Esper abilities that all became his.

The DarkStar leader had witnessed the Lord of Fallen Ark in combat before. He was basically almighty. He only had one word to describe everything he saw…

God!

The Lord of Fallen Ark's doppelganger was his biggest trump card!

The organization that planned this assassination was the organization that had always been behind DarkStar—the Klent Kingdom!

Helping the DarkStar leader fight the Godoran Civilization was one of the projects in Klent's plan to mess up the security of the Colton Star Cluster. DarkStar was just one of the chess pieces used to weaken the various Star System civilizations of Colton. For a very long time, the Klent Kingdom had been secretly causing trouble to their 'friendly neighbor', the Purple Crystal Civilization.

After DarkStar was destroyed by Han Xiao, it was Klent that found the way to send the DarkStar leader away and to the Fallen Ark.

Klent secretly had a close relationship with the Fallen Ark. They did not bet everything on the Tyrant. Due to the Fallen Ark's reputation, there was no way that they would expose this secret partner of theirs.

After the DarkStar leader returned with his fleet, he had always been hiding in Klent's territory and tracking Han Xiao's whereabouts through Klent's intelligence channels. The Bloodshed Land did not know about this.

Han Xiao was the common enemy of the DarkStar leader and Klent. The two of them observed Han Xiao's actions like patient hunters and had noticed that Han Xiao had periodically been going to the Taralam Star Cluster's Wormhole Zone to visit Harrofal in recent years.

Therefore, Klent thought of a plan—Black Star had already proved that it was extremely difficult to kill him, so why not banish him?

Some time earlier, the Bloodshed Land's strategy to drag Han Xiao to the Seoul Star Cluster happened to agree with Klent's idea.

In order to complete this plan, Klent had secretly made a deal with the Lord of Fallen Ark and obtained one of his Esper doppelgangers. Since they could not command the Tyrant, they found another Beyond Grade A that they secretly worked with to help.

Although the Lord of Fallen Ark's doppelganger had the strength of a Beyond Grade A, it had limited energy. Unless he personally came, Black Star would not be killed by just one of his doppelgangers.

Klent's plan was to use this doppelganger to suppress Black Star and send him into a wormhole, banishing him from the Shattered Star Ring. The Wormhole Zone not only connected to the explored universe but also the desolate unexplored universe!

Under these circumstances, the DarkStar leader had accepted Klent's assignment. He had taken the Lord of Fallen Ark's doppelganger, followed Han Xiao to the Wormhole Zone, and attacked!

He was willing to do things for Klent because it would only be possible to build a new home for the hybrids if he had help from a Star Cluster civilization.

Initially, he thought that Klent would let him build a home for the hybrid Godorans in Klent, but the reward that Klent promised to give this time made him unable to reject it.

If Black Star was successfully banished, Klent would build the hybrid Godorans a civilization of their own in the future Flickering World!

The DarkStar looked at Han Xiao, who was on full alert, and then looked at the black fog silhouette beside him that was giving off a terrifying vibe. He smiled faintly.

The end was decided!

Chapter 703: Surprise, I'm Back

The mechanical army surrounded the entire region and countless cannons were pointed toward the black fog silhouette and the DarkStar leader. The cannons were charged up without being fired, and Han Xiao sized up the silhouette of the Beyond Grade A individual, which gave him immense pressure. Frowning, Han Xiao rapidly looked through his memory of Beyond Grade A experts.

A Beyond Grade A Super was far rarer than Calamity Grade Supers, and every one of them was a top expert in the galaxy. Han Xiao could clearly remember the details of every expert.

Black fog silhouette, red light spots…

A figure then flashed in Han Xiao’s mind.

Could it be that this fellow is (EsGod]? The ‘God of Espers’ and infamous Beyond Grade A Super?

This black fog silhouette was extremely similar to the EsGod doppelganger in his memories. After searching through his memories once, Han Xiao realized that it was extremely likely that his guess was correct.

If that was the case, it could barely be considered good news. Han Xiao’s eyes narrowed.

EsGod was one of the final bosses in the neutral-evil faction. His name was a secret, and people only knew him by his title of ‘EsGod’ or ‘Lord of Fallen Ark’. He had a few other nicknames, such as the Guide of the Crazy Believer, Tide of Extinction, and Butcher of Life.

Among the Beyond Grade A Supers, the combat capability of EsGod was ranked at the very top. His battle record was stunning, and he had not suffered a single loss before. His worst battle record was a draw, and he even had the record of killing another Beyond Grade A Super!

Even the three Universal Civilizations were extremely wary of him.

If the main body of EsGod descended, Han Xiao was certain that no one in the entire Shattered Star Ring would be his opponent. Even the Tyrant, Magus, and Dragon Emperor would not be a match for him.

But if it was only a doppelganger, even if he could give off the pressure of a Beyond Grade A Super, his actual combat ability was definitely weaker than his main body.

Furthermore, the battlefield was advantageous to Han Xiao! Han Xiao looked at the wormholes all around and came to a conclusion.

I can give it a shot!

All these thoughts flashed past in an instant, and Han Xiao already had a grasp of the situation. He took a deep breath to calm himself down and increase his concentration.

This was his first time fighting a Beyond Grade A Super head on, and Han Xiao would give it his all. Suddenly, he seemed to have thought about something and began talking to Harrofal in their communication channel.

"Professor, both of us are in danger right now, and this isn’t the time for you to hide anything. Tell me what kind of machines you have. I need to gather all of our strength."

Harrofal only hesitated for a second before whispering to Han Xiao through the communication channel. After listening to what Harrofal said, Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled, and he immediately came up with a plan. He then gave Harrofal a series of instructions, and Harrofal handed something over to him.

Right at this moment, the doppelganger of EsGod made a move. His figure disappeared in an instant and arrived within the formation of the mechanical army.

Before the mechanical army around him could open fire, he disappeared again, and his figure flashed around the mechanical army rapidly before appearing in front of Han Xiao. He had managed to break through the defensive line of Han Xiao’s mechanical army in an instant.

The moment the doppelganger of EsGod made his move, Han Xiao reacted. He first got Harrofal to leave the battlefield before he retreated swiftly. At the same time, he released a large number of compressed orbs and nanoparticles, which transformed into a hundred six-sided alloy plates. The exterior of the alloy plates looked like solar panels with an intricate mechanical design on the plates that was much more complicated. These metal plates were used to stabilize spatial coordinates.

These alloy plates were dispersed and formed a loose sphere structure. The space within the interior of the sphere was stabilized, and the undulations of space were flattened.

This was a product of the Cutting-Edge Knowledge (Advanced Space Application), a product to stabilize space.

When the doppelganger of EsGod appeared in front of Han Xiao, he also fell into the region within the sphere, and his instant movement skill was restricted. However, EsGod did not pause and charged forward at an unbelievable speed instead

Just when the thought of retreating surfaced in Han Xiao’s mind, his vision suddenly darkened, and EsGod’s figure was already right before him. The speed displayed was almost no different from instant movement, and his Dexterity was at least three thousand points!

Esper ability, Divine Speed!

"Dammit, isn’t he too damn fast?" Han Xiao was startled and gritted his teeth to activate his Mechanical Force.

The psionic furnace of his Mountain Ape suit immediately revved up, and bluish lightning bolts flashed over the surface. Psionic energy exploded from his mechanical suit and formed a bluish energy blast at EsGod’s doppelganger.

However, the psionic energy blast passed through EsGod’s doppelganger as though he were a holographic projection. The energy blast only had a miniscule effect.

Esper ability, Dimension Crack!

The next moment, EsGod’s doppelganger regained its physical form, and a palm drifted toward Han Xiao’s chest.

Han Xiao immediately felt his hair stand on end, and he deactivated the space stabilizing device without hesitation. He used his Advanced Void Travel and escaped into the Void Dimension to avoid this fist.

He had a feeling that he would definitely be in huge trouble if he suffered such an attack!

The world before him then quieted and slowed. Everything around him seemed to be covered with a screen of water. After entering the Void Dimension, Han Xiao immediately attempted to retreat.

Right at this moment, the black fog that represented EsGod’s doppelganger suddenly trembled and escaped from the state of being silenced. He had also entered the Void Dimension!

EsGod then spread out his fingers before clenching his fists tightly. Han Xiao could clearly see a gigantic crack appearing in the space around him, and before he could even react, the Void Dimension world around him shattered like a broken mirror. Han Xiao was kicked out of the Void Dimension and brought back into the physical world.

His Void Travel was interrupted!

At the same time, EsGod’s figure appeared before Han Xiao again with his palm descending.

Han Xiao took a deep breath, and the danger alarm in his head went off loudly with his heart almost stopping. This was an instinctive reaction that he could not control at all. He could only watch helplessly as EsGod’s palm approached him.

Since he could not avoid the attack, he could only tank it!

Han Xiao gritted his teeth and immediately adjusted the power output of his mechanical suit to the maximum. All his buff skills were activated without hesitation, and he even activated a few Character Summon Cards to increase his Strength, including Nagakin’s [Muscle Is Truth] card.

Mechanical components sprung up on the surface of the Mountain Ape suit, and a surging force was generated.

Han Xiao’s arm folded to form a blocking posture, and he activated his shield to welcome the incoming blow.

Despite the palm pressing down on the psionic shield as though there was not the slightest bit of force being exerted, Han Xiao could feel as though a tsunami crashed down onto him.

Esper ability, Star Toss!

Thankfully, there was no sound in space. If there was, the soundwave from this attack alone could have killed all life forms below Grade C instantly!

Han Xiao blacked out, and he lost consciousness for an instant. When he regained consciousness, he realized that his body had been sent flying uncontrollably, destroying any mechanical soldiers in his path.

EsGod’s doppelganger became a small dot in Han Xiao’s vision, and Han Xiao did not know how far away this blow sent him.

The scales beneath his mechanical suit tried to dissipate the force of this attack, but they overloaded and were instantly reduced into scrap.

Han Xiao hurriedly summoned his interface to take a look and saw that this palm strike alone had taken out twenty-four percent of his suit’s armor and ten percent of his health. If he did not have his armor and shield, this palm strike would probably have taken forty percent of his health.

"This is the strength of a Beyond Grade A Super…" Han Xiao was dumbfounded.

The most frightening part of EsGod was the fact that even if he absorbed a simple Esper ability, he would be able to evolve the ability and allow it to unleash the force at the Beyond Grade A level!

The basic forms of Divine Speed and Star Toss were actually extremely common low grade Esper abilities, giving a speed boost and strength boost respectively!

Even if it was only a doppelganger, it still had the strength of Beyond Grade A!

Han Xiao tried to stabilize his body while releasing the space stabilizing equipment to prevent EsGod from using his instant movement ability. During that short exchange, he had already gotten his mechanical army to aim at EsGod and open fire.

Rainbow colors lit up the universe!

Thousands of light balls swallowed EsGod’s doppelganger, but the next moment, a black hole seemed to have formed, and the energy of those balls of light were sucked into EsGod’s body. As though he had eaten a great supplement, EsGod’s face, which was originally dim, began to light up again.

Esper ability, Black Hole!

The energy capacity of his doppelganger was limited, and the Lord of Fallen Ark would not inject too much energy into it. Thus, EsGod’s doppelganger was like a three-minute man. However, this wave of attacks had resupplied it with energy again.

"What kind of a hack is this?" Han Xiao finally managed to stabilize his body and cursed as he witnessed such a scene.

He could not tank the enemy’s attack or initiate an attack.

You are a bigger rascal than me!

"Hahaha!"

The DarkStar leader who was hiding at the side burst into laughter upon witnessing such a scene.

He had originally worried that EsGod’s doppelganger would not be able to suppress Black Star. However, it seemed like his worry was unnecessary. In his eyes, EsGod’s doppelganger fighting Black Star was like an adult bullying a child!

This time, Black Star definitely would not be able to escape!

The next moment, Han Xiao turned around to escape and charged toward the wormhole zone.

Upon witnessing that, the DarkStar heaved a sigh of relief, and a satisfied smile could be seen on his face.

It seems like EsGod’s doppelganger can threaten Black Star’s life, so Black Star wants to escape through the wormhole. Hahaha, you are going to be exiled in order to save your life.

EsGod’s doppelganger easily weaved through the mechanical army and gave chase to Han Xiao. Both figures transformed into rays of light and charged straight into the unstable wormhole zone.

Despite the wormholes being unstable, the wormholes with the most intense energy fluctuations tended to connect to further places. This had not been verified, but it was from the experience of the galactic residents.

The speed of EsGod’s doppelganger was extremely fast, and he chased closely behind Han Xiao. His objective was to send Han Xiao into the largest wormhole of this wormhole zone and exile Han Xiao away as far as possible.

Han Xiao could feel the terrifying suction force from the largest wormhole next to him. Turning back to look at EsGod, who seemed to be teasing him, he gritted his teeth and operated his thrusters to avoid the wormhole.

Right at that moment, a chuckle sounded by Han Xiao’s ears as though it was telepathically transmitted.

"Stop struggling. Come and take the risk together with me. Entering wormholes is one of my hobbies."

EsGod said those words through voice transmission, and the next instant, he appeared behind Han Xiao and grabbed onto Han Xiao’s arm. At the same time, the red dots on his face shook slightly as though they were forming a smiling face.

It turns out you know how to talk!

Han Xiao felt his balls ache.

The next moment, EsGod’s doppelganger dragged Han Xiao into the wormhole, and both of them disappeared.

The mechanical army lost their source of Mechanical Force and all froze in midair.

"Success!"

The DarkStar leader was overjoyed and could no longer suppress his excitement.

They had finally exiled Black Star, and Klent’s mission for him had been completed. There was hope for a new country for the mixed blood Godorans!

"It’s over. It’s finally over," the DarkStar leader muttered to himself with tears welling up in his eyes. Amid the tears, he seemed to be able to see a future full of hope.

As long as the mixed blood Godorans had their own home, they would be able to lead a happy life together without any discrimination from the purebloods. While every mixed blood Godoran looked different and came from a different tribe, the DarkStar leader believed that they were all the same. They were the new Godorans.

The DarkStar leader wiped away his tears and put aside such thoughts. Just when he was about to turn around and leave, he suddenly thought about something and turned around to search for Harrofal.

He still remembered this Calamity Grade Super who did not participate in the battle. He had seen Harrofal’s information before, and Harrofal seemed to be a researcher for a Star Cluster Civilization. The DarkStar leader felt that he could catch Harrofal for an additional reward.

After looking around for a while, he finally saw Harrofal’s figure in a region far away from the battlefield. Just when he was about to go forward to capture Harrofal, Harrofal suddenly stopped moving

Harrofal took out a compressed orb, and the compressed orb transformed into a strange looking machine. It looked a little like a music box, yet it did not have that many layers of complicated construction. Compared to a weapon for battle, it looked more like a delicate research tool. Eight arms then appeared from the machine, and the arms got to work as though it was painting, leaving behind a bluish mark of light.

The light marks became darker and darker and suddenly ballooned up to become a blue teleportation door. Following which, the blue light door spat out a figure before closing up.

"This thing is truly useful. Here, you can have it back." Han Xiao stabilized himself and threw a beacon back to Harrofal.

"Humph, I am a researcher. The things I develop are naturally useful. However, if you fly into other wormholes that haven’t been measured before, this machine won’t be able to find you."

Harrofal looked at the beacon with heartache and stored it back in his mechanical suit. This was something that he had given to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao then cracked his neck and looked toward the shocked DarkStar leader. Crossing his arms, his lips curled up with mockery as he sent a message.

"I bet you didn’t expect to see me again!"

Chapter 704: Scapegoat

Less than a minute earlier…

Han Xiao was dragged into a dark, creepy wormhole. The moment that he entered, countless indescribable images appeared in his vision.

The side of the wormhole looked blue but was actually black. When the two of them entered, they were separated and could not see each other anymore.

The EsGod doppelganger did not even have to control him. The vortex in the wormhole dragged the two of them along and confused Han Xiao’s senses. Sometimes, he felt he was going forward, sometimes backward, sometimes falling, and sometimes rising. It strangely felt like he was being flushed down the toilet.

The screen inside the mechanical suit displayed that the space coordinates became undetectable, and his thrusters had stopped working. He could not move, and the images around him quickly changed as if many things flashed past him. When he looked closer, it all became black. At the end of the wormhole that was an unknown distance ahead, a tiny light shone as if that was the exit.

At this time, the square-shaped mechanical beacon that Han Xiao placed in the mechanical suit started to operate. This was a Wormhole Probe Beacon that Han Xiao had gotten from Harrofal before the fight with EsGod started.

Harrofal studied wormholes deeply. As they had to collect the various parameters of wormholes, the teams of the observation station had to get close to the wormholes from time to time. Occasionally, someone would get sucked in accidently. Through many experiments, Harrofal had invented a device that could retrieve a person from a wormhole. It had two requirements-first, the person had to carry a Wormhole Probe Beacon on them; second, the wormhole entered had to be one that had been measured before and had data recorded.

Han Xiao knew how strong EsGod was too clearly, even if it was just a doppelganger. As soon as he recognized the enemy, he knew that he would not be a match in a direct battle. He was never arrogant.

Therefore, when Han Xiao heard of this device that Harrofal had, Han Xiao had a flash of insight. He decided to use himself as bait and lure the EsGod doppelganger into the wormhole. Then, Harrofal would pull him out.

Although Harrofal might not be trustworthy, he had no choice but to take the bet. The worst ending would at most be spending a honeymoon with the EsGod doppelganger.

As a Mechanic, Han Xiao knew very well that compared to Mechanics that were good in combat, those in research and development usually had more tricks up their sleeves.

Han Xiao breathed a sigh of relief and figured out the enemies’ plan.

The DarkStar leader wanted to use the wormhole to banish him. However, using this Wormhole Zone as the battlefield ended up being to his advantage.

He had banished the EsGod doppelganger instead!

Han Xiao glanced at Harrofal and murmured, "Luckily, Harrofal was here, or I would have been in great danger."

This time, the distant DarkStar leader who was petrified finally regained his focus. Without saying a single word, he turned around and started to escape. His expression was twisted and ferocious, filled with shock and rage.

He had just been thinking about the bright future ahead of him now that the mission was completed, yet in less than a minute, his fantasy was shattered mercilessly by the reality. Black Star had escaped from the wormhole, but the EsGod doppelganger did not return. He was completely dumbfounded.

The sudden change in situation almost made him lose his sanity, but the next moment, endless horror drowned that emotion and made his mind shiver.

Without the help of the EsGod doppelganger, Black Star is going to kill me!

The DarkStar leader did not dare to stay for another second. He escaped, only having one thought in his mind… I can’t die now; the hybrid Godorans need me!

However, the mechanical army was activated by Han Xiao once again and chased after him like a nightmare. Millions of mechanical soldiers rushed to him like a wave of metal. In the eyes of the DarkStar leader, these mechanical objects with no life seemed to have become ferocious and evil pureblood Godorans.

A battle between Han Xiao’s mechanical army enhanced by his Mechanical Force and a Calamity Grade that did not excel in fighting masses had absolutely no uncertainty. Han Xiao easily took care of him with just his mechanical army.

Without the EsGod doppelganger, the DarkStar leader had no more trump cards left. In order to not alarm the enemy, he had only brought a tiny fleet. The other troops and battleships that he had received from the Fallen Ark were all stored with Klent.

Two Oathkeepers brought the DarkStar leader, who was on his last breath, before Han Xiao. The effects of Chain of Pain and the other spells had stopped long ago. Healthy and vigorous, Han Xiao sized the DarkStar leader up.

"I thought you had already left the Shattered Star Ring. I didn’t think you would dare come back. You escaped years ago. This time, I finally caught you."

Han Xiao tilted his head. The armor plate on his left shoulder slid open and exposed a ring-shaped device emitting a blue light. It vibrated and released a field of air like a bubble and shrouded the three of them, allowing them to speak directly.

The DarkStar leader stayed silent. All life in his eyes was lost, only leaving despair.

The helmet of Mountain Ape folded and retracted back to the ring-shaped armor on Han Xiao’s neck, showing his face. He sized the DarkStar leader up with an interested look.

"Since you can summon EsGod’s doppelganger, it means that you established a relationship with the Fallen Ark, which should’ve happened in these years you’ve been away. Let me think… the fact that you were able to attack me today means you have a very powerful intelligence channel that can lock onto my whereabouts. I did not tell anyone about coming here, nor did I stop at any other planet along the way. This means that the intelligence channel you have started monitoring me before I even left Colton, and they also knew that I would come to this particular wormhole observation station. It seems like they know me quite well…"

Han Xiao scratched his head.

"Hmm, Klent’s people are probably the only ones that like to stalk me this much. They’re the ones that initiated this mission, right?"

The DarkStar leader kept silent with no emotions in his eyes, as if he was submerged in his own world and did not hear what Han Xiao said at all.

Han Xiao pushed the DarkStar leader’s head, but still, he did not react, not even looking at him. His eyes looked like they had no focus, and his eyeballs did not move at all.

"Why aren’t you talking? Do you think imitating an ostrich will work?"

Harrofal could not help but cough softly. "Should I excuse myself?"

"No need, you can be my witness," Han Xiao replied before turning around to look at the DarkStar leader. He frowned.

Strange, all he did was beat him up. Why did he seem broken?

Han Xiao, however, did not know that the DarkStar leader had lost all hope. He felt that everything had ended now that he was in Black Star’s hands. He did not want to say anything at all.

"Come on, has your mind collapsed just like that?" Han Xiao stared at the DarkStar leader’s eyes and curled his lips. "Your mental resilience is too low, yet you call yourself the leader of a galactic terrorist organization? Even the native leader of a rebel organization in my home has more backbone than you. You’re so weak."

Han Xiao contemplated for a while. He then called two Phantoms. They shapeshifted and turned into layers of restraints, locking the DarkStar leader in his place. He then took out his juice extractor and extracted a dozen or so Genetic Medicines.

When the DarkStar leader saw the Super-Gene Extractor, emotions finally appeared in his eyes. "So, the Secret Message Bead did end up in your hands."

"That’s right." Han Xiao recalled that his first contact with DarkStar was because of the Secret Message Bead mission. "By the way, where is Ember?"

"He’s dead." The DarkStar leader lowered his head.

"Oh, that’s great." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. The Destiny’s Child’s Character Summon Card was right.

About how Ember died, he was not interested at all. In fact, when he saw the EsGod doppelganger, he already roughly knew what had happened.

Capturing the DarkStar leader was a pleasant surprise. Klent was most likely supporting DarkStar, and they were connected to EsGod. This made him feel that he needed to be more cautious and alert.

The DarkStar leader’s use was not only to generate juices; he could give this war criminal to Godora. That should trigger a Legendary Point and Dungeon Creation Rights, representing that the DarkStar organization was completely eliminated.

Godora would heavily promote it, which might be also helpful to the (Bloodline) mission.

However, Han Xiao was not satisfied with just the reward from a Star System civilization. With his current position, Star Cluster Civilizations were the most suitable partners. Since he had discovered DarkStar and Klent’s connection, he felt that he could make something out of it. Purple Crystal would definitely be willing to share this inside information.

The effect that would bring was very obvious —with Klent having a history of funding a terrorist group to disrupt a Star System civilization, it would be more than enough to make the civilizations of the Westwind, Kaya, and Chaida Star Systems more alert toward Klent. This could indirectly cause Purple Crystal’s control in the areas of these three border Star Systems to recover, decreasing the efficiency of the Bloodshed Land.

Furthermore, the Lord of Fallen Ark was notorious throughout the entire universe, known as a brute extremely hated by the three Universal Civilizations. As soon as Klent and EsGod’s relationship was exposed, the pressure they faced would increase drastically. At the very least, the Crimson Dynasty would be unhappy with Klent.

Not mentioning the pressure that Klent would receive externally, there was also a chance for things to happen internally—their ally Heber the Tyrant might not like sharing his spouse with EsGod.

Of course, he might be wrong, and Klent might not be the mastermind behind DarkStar.

But it did not matter.

The DarkStar leader is in my hands. If I say you’re the mastermind, you are!

Han Xiao was firm on sending this gift to Klent.

Putting away all the medicines, Han Xiao flipped his palm, and a compressed orb shot out from the tubes inside the mechanical suit. Activated with a little bit of Mechanical Force, this compressed orb quickly expanded into a single person aircraft about ten meters long. It was very small.

The small standard spaceship that he had originally taken was destroyed. Although he could use the Mountain Ape’s Traveling Mode to leave, it was not convenient when he had a captive with him. He could only take out a single person aircraft and leave the Wormhole Zone first.

"Profession Harrofal, let me take you to the nearest planet."

"Sure."

Han Xiao retrieved his mechanical army, and the two of them entered the spaceship. He told Harrofal to help monitor the DarkStar leader while he sat in the pilot seat.

At this time, Han Xiao seemed to have recalled something

"By the way, where does the wormhole I just entered lead to? The EsGod doppelganger did not escape, where would he get teleported to?"

Harrofal shook his head. "The other side of that wormhole isn’t stable. We’ve measured the data, and the other side of that wormhole changes constantly, so I don’t know where that guy went. However, based on probability, there’s a bigger chance that he will have arrived in an unexplored region. After all, that wormhole is huge, and its energy turbulence is very violent."

"I see…"

The EsGod doppelganger had limited energy, so it would disappear on its own after some time. As long as he did not come out in any densely populated area, it would be safe.

A dark blue flame shot out from the end of the aircraft. It slowly accelerated and gradually turned into a stream of light, disappearing from the Wormhole Zone.

In some unexplored region of the universe, a wormhole was slowly spinning. Suddenly, a silhouette flew out from the wormhole covered in black fog. It was EsGod’s doppelganger.

Stabilizing his body, the EsGod doppelganger waited outside the wormhole. After waiting for quite a while, he still did not see his little friend Black Star come over and meet him.

The red dot of light on the face of the EsGod doppelganger shone brightly, giving off a sense of hatred.

The main body had a mental connection with the doppelgangers. The main body could see the doppelganger’s actions and could either control the doppelgangers or just watch. EsGod always liked to be the observer and let his doppelgangers do the work. Seeing doppelgangers make their own choices was like watching a first-person movie.

Because he had this ability, he liked to enter wormholes for the fun of it and let fate decide what happened to the doppelganger.

This time, attacking Black Star, the original body of EsGod was still just watching as the doppelganger acted out of his own will. He did not really take Klent’s request seriously. As he saw that Black Star seemed to have escaped, he was a little curious and remembered this person. He then forgot about the mission and looked at where his doppelganger had landed.

The EsGod doppelganger looked left and right before choosing a random direction and starting continuous long-distance teleports.

The energy consumption of teleporting was low, but the energy inside his body still decreased quite a lot after it went on for a very long time. The red dot of light became dim. This time, the EsGod doppelganger finally saw a planet.

A strange planet.

Looking at it from afar, the planet surface was covered in green and was very lively, as if there were no tracks of any manual modification. Yet, the EsGod doppelganger’s detection ability sensed countless highly intelligent lives living on the planet surface.

The most special part of this was that there were thick, long roots growing on the surface of this planet that extended all the way to outside the atmosphere and into outer space. The ends of these roots then reached into a stable wormhole.

The EsGod doppelganger focused on it and suddenly realized that he was looking at it upside down.

These enormous roots did not grow out from the planet but extended out from the wormhole and connected to the planet surface This meant that these roots did not grow from the ground but inside the wormhole. The planet was the end of these roots.

Lights of all sorts of colors appeared at the end of these roots and entered the wormhole as if these roots were nutrient pipes sucking the energy of this planet.

Having seen this through the doppelganger, inside the Fallen Ark’s hall, the hooded man on the throne, EsGod, opened his eyes.

"Interesting."

Chapter 705: Transfer

In the Seoul Star Cluster was a Klent military fortress planet that supposedly repaired and manufactured battleships, but in reality, this was the headquarters of the Klent Confidential Strategy Department. The Confidential Strategy Department was Klent’s secret department that executed missions that were not exactly suitable to be made known to the public.

Those sensitive operations such as funding DarkStar, contacting the Fallen Ark, and the like were the Confidential Strategy Department’s job.

The authority level of the Confidential Strategy Department was extremely high. Even its internal members were just allowed to access information about their own mission and not the data of the other operations from the database. The garrison on this planet was not just for disguise but also to prevent the Confidential Strategy Department members from betraying and leaking the secrets.

The secret war was run by the Bloodshed Land, which did not take commands from Klent. Although Klent did not interfere with the war on the surface, without the Bloodshed Land knowing, they carried out secret missions to influence the secret war privately.

Sending the DarkStar leader to take the EsGod doppelganger and banish Black Star was their plan. They thought that it would almost definitely be successful, but they received information that they had lost contact with the DarkStar leader and were shocked. Regretful, they quickly hosted a meeting to discuss how to deal with it.

"The banishment mission failed. The worst outcome is that the DarkStar guy fell into Black Star’s hands and exposed his relationship with us. We must immediately erase any traces of us ever having contact with DarkStar."

"Black Star might not be able to find out the truth. We have already instructed the DarkStar guy that no matter what situation he gets caught in, he has to take full responsibility, saying that everything was his plan, his alone, and that no one was behind him. He won’t rat Klent out; he knows the consequences."

"We can’t rely on luck. We have to prepare for the worst. Black Star is very alert and skeptical. He will connect the DarkStar guy and the EsGod doppelganger to us. Furthermore, it’s not the first time he’s used us as the scapegoat. Even if the DarkStar guy doesn’t say anything, he can still fabricate a verbal confession to make us take the blame. I know him too well!"

"Yes, there’s a very high chance that Black Star will do this. He doesn’t have any morals and is a dangerous man who will do anything to achieve his goal. We must let the Foreign Affairs Department people insist on this being a slanderous act."

"One more thing, temporarily stop all assassination attempts on Black Star. The success rate is way too low. Even the EsGod doppelganger wasn’t able to get rid of him. Without a Beyond Grade A, Black Star will probably be impossible to deal with. Also, after this, Black Star will definitely be more careful. It will be very difficult to find a chance like this again.

The people quickly decided on the report and handed it to the superior. This attack failed, but there was no point in them feeling regretful. All they could do was their best at recovering the situation.

Who would have thought that even EsGod could not get rid of Black Star!

On Godora’s mother planet, Serbia the Fifth was finalizing some files. This time, his private communicator received a communication request.

Serbia the Fifth took a look, and his eyes sparkled it was from Black Star.

Only very important people could contact him through his private communicator, and Han Xiao was one of them.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what is it?" Serbia the Fifth cut to the chase. He had to deal with tons of issues every day, so he did not think that Black Star would call him just to chat.

"I caught the DarkStar leader. I plan to hand him over to you guys, but I need to see you personally," Han Xiao said.

Stunned, Serbia the Fifth suddenly stood up and exclaimed, "You caught him?"

The DarkStar leader, who had escaped, had always been an issue in his mind. Every day, he worried about DarkStar rising again. He did not expect Han Xiao to suddenly bring him such a huge surprise.

About ten days later, Han Xiao returned to the Black Star Army’s headquarters in the Garton Star System. Harrofal left halfway and went back to report what had happened back at the observation station.

At this time, the large dock of the Black Star Army’s headquarters was filled with throngs of people. Serbia the Fifth had been waiting with his guards, and beside him was a Purple Crystal emissary. Countless reporters surrounded them from outside the guards and kept taking photos, and further away were the rubbernecking mercenaries who heard about the news.

The reporters chatted among themselves.

"Purple Crystal and Godora are welcoming Black Star together. What does this mean? Why did the people above tell us to come here? Is there some big news?"

"Who knows? I heard that this is a press conference invitation announced by Purple Crystal. Although they did not state the reason, who’d dare reject it? There is definitely something important to be announced that will make our trip worth it."

All the reporters there were invited, and they did not know what they had to report, but no one would reject Purple Crystal.

Furthermore, the location was at the Black Star Army’s headquarters. They had a feeling that as long as Black Star was involved, it would definitely be newsworthy. Therefore, although they knew nothing, they were passionate and curious about what was going to happen.

Inviting the reporters was Han Xiao’s request. He planned to make the handover of the DarkStar leader sensational news in order to increase his influence. Also, this would make the scapegoating more effective. After contacting Godora, he had contacted Purple Crystal.

Purple Crystal had been shocked by the information about EsGod doppelganger, only to feel relieved when they saw that Han Xiao was okay.

After hearing Han Xiao’s plan, Purple Crystal had immediately agreed. They fully supported any plan to cause problems for Klent. Hence, they had invited various galactical media outlets to attend the handover ceremony of the DarkStar leader. Only, they wanted to create some suspense, so they did not tell them what was this about.

Han Xiao’s spaceship stopped at the dock, attracting everyone’s attention. They subconsciously held their breath, and the place became silent.

Under the attention of everyone present, the hatch opened, and Han Xiao walked out. Only then did the blaring noise come back.

Serbia the Fifth and the Purple Crystal emissary quickly approached to welcome and talk to Han Xiao. The reporters started to video everything.

Brock was mixed in the crowd. His eyes kept looking over to Serbia the Fifth. As a DarkStar spy, he suppressed his hatred for the current highest leader of Godora so that others would not notice.

Han Xiao and Serbia the Fifth spoke a few words. Then, they looked around at the reporters and smiled.

"Let’s get down to business."

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the hatch. Two Oathkeepers escorted the unkempt DarkStar leader out.

Everyone looked at the DarkStar leader. Confusion, perplexity, and similar emotions appeared in their eyes—most of them did not recognize the DarkStar leader.

This time, Serbia the Fifth spoke at just the right time and loudly announced, "This man is the DarkStar leader who has been on the run for years. Godora has spent a huge amount of effort but never managed to catch this evil man. This time, thanks to His Excellency Black Star’s help, this criminal has been captured. On behalf of Godora, we sincerely thank you!"

Then, he bowed slightly toward Han Xiao.

As the highest leader of a civilization, he represented the entire civilization in showing gratitude to Han Xiao. This instantly sparked shock among the crowd!

"That’s the DarkStar leader?"

"So, today is about the handover of this fugitive. No wonder we were invited to report it."

Serbia the Fifth continued. "The DarkStar organization has been a menace to Godora for a very long time, causing the deaths of many civilians. We will have a public trial for this evil monster, giving justice to all the people of Godora. I hereby announce, the DarkStar organization is no more!"

There were some Godorans among the crowd, and they started cheering loudly.

Brock, however, was stunned. He looked at the unkempt DarkStar leader blankly. His legs turned wobbly, and he almost fell. His entire body shivered, unable to believe what was happening right before his eyes.

He had been waiting for the DarkStar leader to contact him, waiting to advise the leader not to mess with Black Star. But never would he have thought, when the leader finally appeared for the first time after so many years, he had already become Black Star’s captive.

Then what was the point of me hiding in the Black Star Army?

Everything is wasted!

As if struck by lightning, Brock was petrified and bewildered.

The galactic reporters were elated. Godora’s highest leader personally announcing the end of the DarkStar meant that Godora had completely eliminated their archenemy. It was indeed big news.

However, they did not know that this was just an appetizer. There was more shocking news afterward.

"Me meeting the DarkStar leader wasn’t an accident. Everyone, please watch," Han Xiao said as nanoparticles turned into a tiny hovering sphere above his palm and generated a projection in the air.

Everyone looked over. It was the video of the battle between Han Xiao and the DarkStar leader.

The tactical analyzer of the mechanical suit had recorded the entire battle. Han Xiao felt that the video would be more effective than words, so he played it.

Everyone was shocked as they saw the DarkStar leader summon the EsGod doppelganger in the video. This time, Han Xiao spoke. "According to the data, the creature that the DarkStar leader summoned was the Lord of Fallen Ark’s doppelganger."

Fallen Ark!

Every Star Field knew about this organization. DarkStar was connected to this extremely notorious organization?

Everyone was dumbfounded.

Suddenly, many reporters realized something. Stunned, they looked at Han Xiao.

Black Star was assaulted, yet he was standing right there unharmed. Did that not mean that Black Star had survived the attack of a Beyond Grade A?

Having noticed this, the entire place became silent. Countless eyes filled with shock focused on Han Xiao.

Although Han Xiao being a Beyond Grade A seed had become known by everyone in the Shattered Star Ring over the past few years, everyone knew that he was not really a Beyond Grade A yet. He was still extremely far from Beyond Grade As such as the Tyrant and Dragon Emperor.

Every organization only acknowledged how dominant Black Star was among the Calamity Grades and his future potential, but no one felt that Black Star could be viewed on the same level as those actual Beyond Grade As.

Now, however, Han Xiao had played a video of him fighting with a Beyond Grade A and surviving!

The reporters present were shaking with excitement as they quickly videoed the video that Han Xiao was playing. The Black Star Army members that had gone to rubberneck were also thrilled—the stronger their leader was, the brighter they felt their future would be.

Han Xiao did not play the complete video. He cut out the trip to the wormhole at the end and some parts showing his key abilities, but this was more than enough to boost his reputation.

Seeing the reporters’ faces were filled with excitement, and Han Xiao gave a look to the Purple Crystal emissary.

Understanding what Han Xiao meant, the Purple Crystal emissary took a step forward and said, "According to our investigation, we have discovered that the DarkStar leader was not acting on his own, and there were people behind him. Through our thorough investigation, we have discovered that Klent has been in contact with DarkStar secretly since long ago. We suspect that Klent might have been supporting DarkStar secretly to disrupt the safety of the Colton Star Cluster. Hence, on behalf of Purple Crystal, I announce that Purple Crystal will get involved in this matter. We will be holding the trial on the DarkStar leader together with Godora!"

The entire place was in an uproar!

The galactic reporters were not even excited anymore but completely stunned. This last piece of news was much more sensational than the previous two!

If what Purple Crystal said was true, this meant that Klent had been funding DarkStar to destroy civilizations all along. Furthermore, Klent would also be suspected of having contact with the Fallen Ark!

That was a taboo within the three Universal Civilizations!

Who would have thought that the DarkStar being caught would expose so much information!

At this moment, those reporters knew that this story would definitely cause a sensation in the entire Star Field!

Klent was going to suffer heavily!

Chapter 706: I've Become Black Star's Shape

The three pieces of news were each more sensational than the last. Many galactic reporters were dizzy. Han Xiao smiled. He had achieved his goal.

He had used the DarkStar leader to gain some Faction Contribution Points, used his new combat record to gain reputation, and then made Klent a scapegoat again… no, this time, they were really responsible for it.

Looking around at the shocked reporters, Han Xiao nodded with approval.

"With these public opinion channels, in less than an hour, the Shock Department should already be coming online."

Han Xiao, Godora, and Purple Crystal finished announcing the news and proceeded with the handover. Han Xiao officially passed the DarkStar leader to the people that Serbia the Fifth had brought along. A chain of notifications popped up on his interface. His Godora Favorability had already reached its maximum and had no space to even grow any more. His relationship with them had been fixed at [Reverence) since a few years back when he received the Golden Gal Badge.

The Favorability with Serbia the Fifth, however, was very close to the upper limit. Han Xiao felt that Serbia the Fifth looked at him with praise, trust, appreciation, and many other positive emotions.

As Han Xiao expected, he received something in terms of Legendary Points as well; however, it was not a new Legendary Point but the upgrade of an old one. The original Star System level (DarkStar Destroyer) had now become Star Cluster level, giving much higher bonuses to all kinds of Mission Reward Quotas.

Mission Reward Quotas had always been very important. This was a function of the NPC Interface that would not use his own Experience. Han Xiao had always been using the quota to give out rewards to the players and later earning those rewards back through various methods.

In Version 2.0, however, Han Xiao’s Faction Reward Quota had been too low. At that time, the size of the Black Star Army had yet to reach seven digits, and its territory was also limited to Godora’s land.

It was different now. In only three years, the Black Star Army had expanded dozens of times, Han Xiao’s Faction Reward Quota had also increased tremendously. If this growth speed continued to the start of Version 3.0, not to mention one million players, he would even be able to afford three million players.

Version 3.0 also happened to be the exploding stage of player count in his previous life.

Han Xiao had always felt that the Reward Quota was an overall evaluation of himself. The stronger he and his faction were, the higher his Reward Quota. It was somewhat like an evaluation to his overall influence.

The handover ceremony was brief. Han Xiao invited Serbia the Fifth into a private room. The two of them left the dock, and the press conference thus came to an end. The galactic reporters were very satisfied with what they got and felt that this trip was more than worth it. The crowd gradually dissipated.

Spiritless, Brock followed the crowd without a destination like a walking corpse.

The DarkStar leader was the last hope of the organization. Seeing that the leader had been captured, Brock knew that it was the end of the organization. He became lost.

The calling to hide for the sake of DarkStar’s rise was his direction in life, his motivation to work hard. Now, the organization that he had been fighting for had been destroyed, so Brock did not know what he would do in the future. He had lost his purpose.

Maybe the leader’s goal should be inherited by me. The hybrid Godorans’ future… shall be my responsibility!

Brock’s heart suddenly started burning. He felt like he seemed to have found a new purpose in life.

His numb eyes started to become vibrant, and a firm expression appeared on Brock’s face.

That’s right. I’m the last DarkStar member. As long as I’m still alive, it…

Before he fully regained his faith, Herlous happened to be walking toward him and spotted him. He recognized this motivated employee who was praised by the entire army, so he said, "Brock, the army is going to promote a batch of trainees. Quickly set up a large test for the training camp. All those who pass will become official members."

"Understood!" Brock’s brain had yet to react, but his body moved out of instinct. He subconsciously stood straight and listened to the order.

After Herlous left, Brock returned from his beautiful dream to the cold reality. His back that only stayed straight for a few seconds bent again, giving off a lifeless vibe from all over his body.

Inheriting DarkStar’s mission isn’t bad, but Godora isn’t the same as it was. They’re under the Black Star Army’s protection.

Having thought of that, Brock’s ambition and aspirations suddenly disappeared.

Sigh, why revolutionize anymore? I’m not tired of living yet… I’m already Black Star’s shape anyway. Might as well just continue my work…

Maybe this is all fate.

Brock sighed. He was determined… to resign to his fate.

Inside the private guest room, Han Xiao and Serbia the Fifth sat opposite each other.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you have really given me a huge surprise. Without its leader, DarkStar is gone forever. The pureblood and hybrid conflict within the nation will be reduced as well."

Serbia the Fifth spoke in a respectful and sincere tone. Han Xiao’s position in the Shattered Star Ring was now completely different from before; even he did not want to be too casual.

Han Xiao nodded. "I have eliminated a serious problem for you guys, so I have a small request. I hope that during the trial, you guys can support the Purple Crystal’s people as much as possible. This is a good opportunity to damage Klent politically. Although the secret war has nothing to do with you, I still hope that you can cooperate."

"Of course. That’s what we should do!" Even if Han Xiao did not request this, Serbia the Fifth would also give Purple Crystal support. After all, Purple Crystal was their boss.

"Hmm, I actually have one more important matter." Han Xiao touched his chin. "The news of DarkStar being eliminated can somewhat reduce the internal conflict between Godorans, but it won’t solve the root of the problem. The conflict between pureblood and hybrid won’t be resolved because of this. There will be extremists who inherit DarkStar’s will in the future."

Serbia the Fifth sighed. "I know that, but the sense of superiority born from blood is an illness much more difficult to eradicate than the system. This is a tradition that has been passed on through countless years. So many leaders in history were unable to solve this problem. All they could do was alleviate the symptoms, not cure it."

"That might not be the case." Han Xiao smiled faintly. "I have a solution that might reduce your bloodline conflict even further. Are you interested?"

"You have a solution?" Serbia the Fifth was skeptical. "Of course, I’m interested, but this isn’t a problem that can be solved easily."

"Hehe. So, I made a friend recently. Her name is Rossellin…"

Han Xiao explained Rossellin’s experience and abilities. Although he was subtle, Serbia the Fifth understood what Han Xiao meant between the lines—he was suggesting using Rossellin’s ability to slightly brainwash the Godoran populace and twist their views. Rossellin was an extremely good tool to be used against deep rooted traditions.

Serbia the Fifth opened his mouth wide and looked at Han Xiao with shock, unable to believe how daring his suggestion was—he was basically telling the leader of a civilization, "I want to brainwash your entire civilization."

As the highest leader, such an outrageous request almost did not require any consideration. Serbia the Fifth was just about to reject it when he suddenly thought of something. He then shut his mouth and started pondering.

Although brainwashing the entire civilization was outrageous and sensitive, it did indeed seem to be able to quickly solve the deeply rooted bloodline conflict. Serbia the Fifth was both tempted and in denial. By regular means, the bloodline conflict might never be eliminated. But with this extreme method, if something went wrong, it would be a huge shock to all Godorans.

If anyone else had made this request, Serbia the Fifth would have rejected them without hesitation. But the person that made this request was Black Star, who he deeply trusted, which was why Serbia the Fifth did not reject immediately and was conflicted.

"That’s too risky…"

"Do you not trust me?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "How about this? We can request the Purple Crystal Civilization to be the private notary, to prevent the possibility of me having any ulterior motives."

"But can you ensure that Rossellin won’t mess things up on purpose?"

"From what I know about her, she won’t." Han Xiao shook his head.

(Bloodline) was the only Grade S mission in his interface. Initially, he did not have any clue on how to complete it, but now that he had Rossellin, he had a way to complete it that was worth a try despite being controversial.

Discussing the issue with Serbia The Fifth directly was a must. If he brainwashed a Star System Civilization protected by the Peace Treaty, the consequences would be very clear for him. It was not a must for Han Xiao to complete this mission, so he would only carry out this plan if he received official approval. Furthermore, brainwashing openly would be much more efficient than secretly.

Seeing that Serbia the Fifth was still hesitating, Han Xiao added, "I know what you’re worried about. Despite being the leader of a civilization, you’re helping an outsider brainwash your own people. Even though your goal is virtuous, this act is very sensitive, and it’s against your duty. However, you don’t have to make the brainwash compulsory or anything; you can give the Godorans the right to make a choice."

Serbia the Fifth pondered. He was indeed worried about this.

"You can directly announce this to all your people. Of course, don’t use the word ‘brainwash’; make it sound better, such as maybe ‘enhancing the people’s belief of equality’ and the like. Emphasize on the fact that it’s to solve the bloodline conflict and reduce the chance of bad things happening.

"Then, introduce all kinds of related benefits, such as those who accepted the brainwash will have new privileges, and those who don’t will have to pay more taxes. You can also make the bloodline conflict into a new problem, using the public opinion to your advantage and promoting how those who don’t dare accept the brainwashing are stubborn and conservative. You can even re-plan the layout of your planets, forcing those who don’t accept the brainwash to live together, building a spiritual slum, and so on. Anyway, there are tons of methods. You’re a professional leader, so you should know much more than me."

Han Xiao kept tempting Serbia the Fifth. In his eyes, he just could not reject him. This man’s suggestion was too damn good.

Like his many predecessors, if Serbia the Fifth could not solve the bloodline conflict, no one would blame him.

However, he also saw an opportunity. If he accomplished something that his countless predecessors failed to do, his name would go down in history as one of the wisest leaders. It would be an achievement that no one had ever made!

Serbia the Fifth clenched his teeth. "Le-Let me go back and consider this. This is too big a matter. I can’t make a decision now."

"Of course." Han Xiao smiled.

He did not expect to convince Serbia the Fifth this quickly. Even if he lured Serbia the Fifth’s personal desire out, he would not dare bet the entire civilization on it. He definitely had to gather the other relevant officials to brainstorm. He would not agree to it without thorough consideration.

Sending off the troubled Serbia the Fifth, without resting, Han Xiao headed right to the machinery modification room and started to build.

"After slaving for the silver legacy blueprint for so long, I can finally reap the reward!"

Having obtained the ability to complete the Class Advancement mission, Han Xiao did not want to delay it any further. It was time for his Class Advancement.

Chapter 707: Planetary Obliteration Grade Weapon and Apostilization

The framework of the semi-finished Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon was two stories tall. Accompanied by the buzzing of electric currents and the clanking of the mechanical parts, it was slowly getting finished.

Dozens of mechanical arms moved and assembled the parts. Two Watcher Instruments took care of the welding, while waves formed by nanorobots flowed around the framework, finishing up the details. Blue Mechanical Force lightning chains connected those machines, building the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon under Han Xiao’s control.

Han Xiao stood below the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon, continuously adjusting the details and carefully building this enormous cannon. In order to build orange-grade equipment, he was fully focused. He had activated Reynold’s Character Summon Card long ago and received the Perfect Mechanical Sense bonuses.

The effects of [Perfect Mechanical Sense) were apparent. The strength, control, and range of his Mechanical Force all increased tremendously. He became more sensitive to his Mechanical Force and controlled them as smoothly and accurately like an extra limb. Through this, he also gained a deeper understanding of the Perfect Mechanical Sense talent.

Other than these numerical bonuses, Perfect Mechanical Sense had another hidden effect, as written in the remarks, "In your senses, every machine is a world of ecological balance."

The term ‘Mechanical Sense’ did not just mean understanding of machines but close to a new sense, refreshing his knowledge of machines. As if the machines were no longer just objects, when his Mechanical Force flowed through the mechanical structures, he could almost feel a lively sense of touch like he was running his fingers down the body of a beautiful woman. Han Xiao’s senses to the machines were enlarged countless times, allowing him to easily notice tiny details that he had not been able to notice before.

This hidden effect was the cause of the bonuses this talent gave, and the players who just waited for progress bars to fill up were unable to feel this.

No wonder anyone who had this talent was a Mechanic genius; the Perfect Mechanical Sense was so pleasurable…

Han Xiao wanted it so badly.

Be it building machines or combat, [Perfect Mechanical Sense) had a huge effect; it was a god tier talent for the Mechanic class.

Sadly, he could only temporarily enjoy the effects of the (Perfect Mechanical Sense) through the Character Summon Card.

"I have to find a way to get Reynold’s talent in the future."

Han Xiao took a deep breath and focused his mind back on building.

Under the bonuses of Perfect Mechanical Sense, the process was very smooth. He successfully built it in less than a day.

Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon, legacy orange equipment, as powerful as Planetary Obliteration Cannon-this was currently the highest grade machine that Han Xiao had and the most powerful.

The two-story-tall enormous cannon retracted part by part and folded into a compressed orb with a blue and white appearance. Under the Mechanical Force, it floated above Han Xiao’s

palm.

Han Xiao held onto the compressed orb, and the item details popped up on his interface.

Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon (Legacy)

Grade: Orange/Silver

Type: Planetary Obliteration Grade Annihilation Weapon

Requirements: Lv180, Mechanic Class, >25,000 Energy, >2,500 INT.

Basic Attributes:

– Attack: 14,500 – 48,300

– Armor Value: 26,000/26,000

– Energy: 15,000/15,000

– Power Output: 12,170

Energy Furnace Forced Cooldown: 360 seconds

Power Output: Minimum power output consumption: 3,000 energy per attack. Maximum power output consumption: 12,000 energy per attack.

Energy Source: Psionic Reaction Furnace, recovers energy at 25/s.

Additional Ability: Extreme Frost-Deals 50% extra Frost Damage.

Additional Ability: Psionic Frost-Turns psionic energy into ice energy. High chance of freezing the target. Core Impact Area Frozen Effect Trigger Rate: 80%. Other Impact Area Frozen Effect Trigger Rate: 60%.

Additional Ability: Expansion Explosion-A second round of explosions will occur after hitting the target, creating an impact wave and mushroom cloud. Damage: 75% of the first round. +350% Damage Range.

Additional Ability: Reaction Furnace Ray-The attack mode can be changed to ray form. Depending on the power output, energy cost 60 – 240/s. Two damage ticks per second. Damage: 8% of the initial attack. The attack direction can be adjusted.

Special Ability: Freezing Wind—When the power output of an attack exceeds 6,000 energy consumption, changes the environment within 50 miles around the target area. The temperature of the area will be reduced to -50 degrees.

Special Ability: Ice Age-When firing at the maximum power output, changes the environment of the area within 200 miles around the target area, freezing this area and turning it into a glacial area. The temperature of the area will be reduced to -100 degrees.

Special Ability: Frozen Star-When the power output of an attack exceeds 6,000 energy consumption and (Reaction Furnace Ray) is used for more than 90 seconds, this effect will be triggered. This will cause chain reactions and bring the surface of a planet into an Ice Age within one month, destroying the lives on the surface.

Remark: The Ice Elementals are overjoyed and are trying to mate with you.

Legacy: "According to my investigation, freezing a Fixed Star can indirectly destroy all the civilizations on the planets in its orbit." – Peter ‘Flame Extinguisher’ Drate.

"A total of seven Additional Abilities and Special Abilities, certainly fits being orange equipment."

Han Xiao was very satisfied. The destructive power of the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon was extremely strong. Its theoretical damage could even reach the hundred thousands with his Mechanical Force bonuses applied.

Usually, this kind of enormous cannon would be deployed in outer space to attack from above, and it would be difficult to apply Mechanical Force bonuses to it. However, due to his Mechanical Force having the (Void) attribute, he could overcome the distance through the Void Dimension and apply Mechanical Force bonuses to it.

This was Han Xiao’s first Planetary Obliteration Grade weapon; it was now his trump card.

He looked at the interface. The Class Advancement mission was now completed.

Finally!

Han Xiao took a deep breath and initiated the Class Advancement with a solemn expression.

Class Advancement requirements completed!

You have received a new class, (Apostle Mechanic Lv.1).

+240 Energy, +3 STR, +4 DEX, +5 END, +10 INT.

You have received 8 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

The moment the Class Advancement was completed, a huge amount of information appeared in his brain out of nowhere. Han Xiao gained new understandings of machines, and his body started to undergo marvelous changes.

A ton of notifications popped up on the interface.

You have received the talent (Mechanical Force Ascension-Apostle Body]!

You have acquired the ability (Apostle Machinery Affinity)!

You have acquired the ability (Machinery Apostilization)!

The effect of all your Virtual Technology related abilities and talents has increased by 20%

It took Han Xiao quite some time to digest the various abilities that he had gained through the Class Advancement. Feeling the new power flowing in his body, he was delighted.

Finally, I’ve reached this milestone.

Apostle Mechanic was a major milestone for high-level Mechanics. As the saying went, ‘the end of technology is the study of God’. The reason for such a ‘God’-related term, ‘Apostle’, was because the path of the Mechanic class was gradually stepping into the ‘study of God’ territory in the eyes of common people.

The knowledge that he had learned did not change, but the way of using that knowledge had ascended to a completely next level. He would have new understandings and new technology that would seem like acts of God to normal people.

The level limit of (Apostle Mechanic] was thirty, five levels higher than (Truth Mechanic). Usually, the increase in the level limit of the main class also meant the start of a new stage.

Unlike all the Mechanic classes before this, the Apostle Mechanic class allowed one to gather great powers within oneself, making one strong in every respect.

[Apostle Machinery Affinity) was, of course, the core talent passed down through the Mechanic class. Han Xiao immediately leveled it up to the max level. Its effect was +105% Machinery Affinity, a total of 30% more than (Master Machinery Affinity)

The talent (Mechanical Force AscensionApostle Body) and the ability (Machinery Apostilization) were set abilities.

[Machinery Apostilization] allowed him to absorb the energy of machines through the Mechanical Force link instead of the other way round, increasing his own attributes and giving him bonuses.

From the beginning, machines had just been external objects, but Apostilization turned the power of these external objects into his own power. Like Mages receiving bonuses by praying to their Gods, machines were Mechanics’ God. Through becoming an apostle of the machines, he would receive the gifts of these machines.

The actual effect was easy to understand. For example, if he used ‘Apostilization’ on one mechanical suit, the energy of this mechanical suit would be turned into his own energy through the Mechanical Force link, increasing his Energy Rank; giving him dozens points of Endurance, Strength, and Dexterity bonuses as well as a part of the mechanical suit’s bonus effects.

At the same time, by using the mechanical suit’s energy furnace, he would be able to use the abilities of the mechanical suit without wearing it.

Any machinery could be ‘Apostilized’, and different machines would provide different bonuses. ‘Apostilization’ would also put a burden on the machines, depending on each machine’s level.

(Mechanical Force Ascension-Apostle Body] was an ability that worked together with this. It would turn his body into an Apostle Body through Mechanical Force so that he could use the energy of the machines. This was the prerequisite for [Machinery Apostilization) to take effect.

At the same time, this talent determined the number of ‘Apostilized’ machines that his body could endure. The Judgment depended on the total of Intelligence and Endurance. The burden that a machine could bear depended on its Power Level. The stronger the machine, the higher the burden it would be able to bear.

For every ‘Apostilized’ machine, the health point limit would decrease temporarily by 2,500, which would be lifted once the Apostilization ended.

These two abilities were the signature abilities of an Apostle Mechanic. Allowing one to control stronger powers through sharing the energy of the machines. The players in Han Xiao’s previous life did some research, and they believed that the ability to gather external powers into oneself was one of the prerequisites of stepping toward Beyond Grade A.

The other four classes would also gain similar abilities at this stage, as if they were starting to evolve into a higher level being. The players believed that this was proof that Beyond Grade As were new, high-level beings.

To the players, the appearance of Apostilization was very simple; it was basically similar to putting machines into their inventory to receive the bonuses. Han Xiao, however, had real senses, so he had no idea how it would feel.

True knowledge was gained from experimenting. Han Xiao decided to directly test the effects of Apostilization. He held the compressed orb of the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon in his hands, and Mechanical Force lightning shrouded and entered the compressed orb, activating Apostilization.

The next moment, Han Xiao’s expression slightly changed. The Mechanical Force seemed to have become straws that absorbed the energy of the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon. An enormous wave of violent psionic energy entered his body through the Mechanical Force link!

Originally, he could only control the energy generated by his cells. Now, the psionic energy had mixed with the Mechanical Force inside his body and become controllable as well.

The compressed orb was buzzing and vibrating. The surface of the orb was filled with blue energy circuits.

You have Apostilized [Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon). Your load has increased by 379 points.

Your health point limit has decreased by 2,500 temporarily.

+78 STR, +43 DEX, +35 END.

You can now release energy attacks from your body or consume the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon’s energy to recover your own energy.

You have received an Additional Ability. Your attacks will enjoy the bonuses of (Extreme Frost), dealing 50% extra Frost Damage.

You have received an Additional Ability. Your attacks will enjoy the bonuses of (Psionic Frost). You have a chance to freeze the target.

Han Xiao raised and shook his other hand. A blue lump of psionic energy appeared on his palm.

With just a thought, the attribute of this lump of psionic energy started to change and turned into a blue and white frost energy lump. He raised his hand and launched it. A white beam of light landed on the weapon testing alloy wall not far away.

Boom!

The moment it hit, the white light expanded and turned the alloy wall into frozen pieces scattered on the ground in an instant.

Han Xiao looked at the interface. His own energy had close to no loss, and the energy of the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon decreased by a bar.

Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled, and he got quite a few new ideas.

By using Apostilization together with his various abilities, it might have surprising effects.

For example, he could absorb the machinery’s energy to recover his own energy, which meant that he did not have to get damaged to recover health.

Or he could use his Mechanical Force to connect with the machines from far away, so he could use Apostilization remotely without having to summon his machines.

"It’s a very powerful ability. It helps with the Mechanic’s flaw of having a very weak body."

Han Xiao was delighted. His body was already extremely strong, but this ability was still a huge enhancement!

Chapter 708: Spending Money Brings Me Joy

After testing all his new skills, Han Xiao was extremely satisfied.

The load of his machinery was 100 + X. 100 was the basic load that it could take, and X was 3% of a machine’s Power Level. Han Xiao was able to obtain more than 1,000 Attribute Points from the Machinery Apostilization skill, which would be spread out evenly among his Strength, Dexterity, and Endurance.

As long as he could think of a way to increase his Intelligence and Endurance, the upper limit of the load that he could take would also increase.

Han Xiao had just received the (Machinery Apostilization) skill, and when his level increased, the effect of this skill would also become more obvious. Han Xiao wanted to take the path of the Army Style, and the boost from the Machinery Apostilization skill would provide him with a new Support Style, allowing his body to become stronger. He would no longer have to walk the path of getting beaten up in the future.

Opening his interface, Han Xiao first raised the levels of his two new skills to the max and received two Potential Points. He then used his experience points to level up.

At this moment, Han Xiao was level 195, and after leveling up five times, he reached level 200.

The amount of experience required to level up became greater and greater toward the end, and his large stash of experience points was rapidly being used up. He did not have much experience left from Version 2.0.

[Apostle Mechanic] was raised to level five, and the level limit was thirty. This would last him to level 225.

Han Xiao pondered to himself about his future plans. Because he had spent a large amount of experience gambling for blueprints and raising the level of his skills, the remaining experience was only enough to bring him to level 206. At that point, the experience that he had saved up would be completely spent.

If he wanted to increase his level quickly after this, he could only wait until Version 3.0.

Now that he was at level 200, he would have to face a new Promotion Mission. After glancing at the Promotion Mission, Han Xiao had a helpless look on his face. This time, he would have no choice but to use a Mission Completion Card.

Han Xiao’s Promotion Mission was an ordinary mission this time, but it was one that Han Xiao could not complete. It required him to clear a high-grade dungeon within ten levels from him with a rating of Grade A.

To the players, they would be able to obtain such a level only at the later versions. At that time, they would have gone through many different Main Storyline Missions and resolved many troublesome storylines. Thus, high-grade dungeons would basically be in surplus. However, it had not even reached Version 3.0, and unless he could create a dungeon of his own, it would be extremely difficult for him to find a high-grade dungeon.

Most importantly, Han Xiao had never used Dungeon Crystals, and it would thus be impossible for him to challenge a dungeon. His only other option was to use a Mission Completion Card. One of the usages of the Mission Completion Card was to help players skip these difficult but compulsory missions.

"Talking about a Mission Completion Card…" In the past three years, Han Xiao had received a few Random Rewards from the various missions that he had completed. However, he had never used them in order to save them for a rainy day such as this. As such, there were two chances for him to roll a Random Reward on the interface.

Thankfully, it seemed like the Grade S mission (Bloodline) had a chance of being completed, and there would definitely be the chance to roll a Random Reward. Furthermore, the Random Reward of a Grade S mission would definitely give him more choices.

"Compared to Version 2.0, my strength and the scale of the Black Star Army have completely transformed. When the players return, I will be able to harvest a new round of experience. Before that, I must use the remaining seven years to accumulate a few Mission Completion Cards. When I get enough experience, I will be able to increase my level rapidly."

Han Xiao decided on his plan.

After packing up his new equipment, Han Xiao left the Machine Modification Room and went to his office. He then summoned Rossellin and Reynold.

When both of them entered, Han Xiao went straight to the main point.

"Rossellin, what do you think about the Black Star Army?"

"How so?" Rossellin asked.

"You just need to tell me your overall feeling."

"You want me to praise you, right?" Rossellin rolled her eyes before adding on with a tone of helplessness, "Alright then. Even though I am an extremely picky person, I have to admit that I do admire you. I underestimated you when I first saw you and never thought that you would be a legendary character."

After being locked up for so many years, Rossellin did not know about the changes in the outside world. She had only started looking through what happened over the past few years in the Shattered Star Ring after returning to the Black Star Army base with Reynold. Only then did she understand the position of the Black Star Army in the Shattered Star Ring and everything that they had accomplished.

After looking through the accomplishments of the Black Star Army, her first reaction was to suspect that the documents in her hands had been falsified.

What shocked her the most was not the size of the Black Star Army but the speed at which they grew. After all, the Black Star Army had only been around for about a decade.

Black Star had only taken ten years to grow from a Grade C Super to become a Beyond Grade A Super seed. Furthermore, he had survived a battle with an actual Beyond Grade A Super!

In the past ten years, the Black Star Army that he led had become the largest armed force in the Colton Star Cluster with the Purple Crystal Civilization as their backing and their bases all around dozens of Star Systems!

This was an unbelievable miracle.

Rossellin had never imagined that Han Xiao was actually such a bigshot.

After seeing those files, she was truly filled with admiration toward Han Xiao but was too embarrassed to show it on the surface.

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao said, "Hmm, I would like to ask you for help and be a temporary officer of the Black Star Army."

A teasing look could be seen on Rossellin’s face. "You also want to make use of my ability?"

"More accurately, it should be a mutually beneficial agreement. You are a special talent, and I am willing to give you appropriate compensation."

"What if I don’t agree?"

"Don’t worry, I said that you will have a certain degree of freedom, and I will not force you like the Hutt Civilization. You can choose to reject me."

The corner of Han Xiao’s lips curled up slightly, and he continued. "However, even if you have the ambition and want to accomplish something, you won’t be able to do that without money. Furthermore, I will give you attractive compensation that will allow you to build up your capital."

"With my ability," Rossellin replied, "it would be an easy task for me to accumulate capital. Why do I have to help you?"

Han Xiao chuckled in response. "Don’t forget that you have a criminal record. Since I bailed you out, I will not allow you to run around freely and do as you wish. If you do, you will become a wanted criminal. Thus, working for me temporarily is the best opportunity for you to earn money."

"Humph, you are bundling both threats and benefits. Do you think that I will definitely agree to your request?" Rossellin snorted. "I like to deal with those who overestimate themselves the most!"

"Actually, it is possible to remove your criminal record entirely…"

"What do you want me to do?" Rossellin took a step forward without any hesitation and hugged Han Xiao’s arm with a fawning look on her face.

As Reynold looked at the fawning Rossellin, he was completely speechless.

He had talked to Rossellin privately and knew that Rossellin was willing to stay behind and help. However, she just could not put aside her face to do so. Now that Black Star had taken the initiative to mention this, it gave her the opportunity to accept it.

Han Xiao was also certain that Rossellin would not reject him. The eighty Favorability points that he had with Rossellin were not just for show. When facing Rossellin’s venomous tongue, he also knew how to deal with her. As long as he gave Rossellin an excuse, she would definitely agree to his request.

"You will take up the role of a Culture Instructor and lecture the members of the Black Star Army. You will lecture the members of the Black Star Army about our history so that they will understand our Black Star Army better and have a greater sense of belonging. You should research the history of the Black Star Army and come up with lecture material for it. Find a suitable incision point to set up their faith in the Black Star Army. I will check the material after you have prepared it."

Han Xiao wiggled his arm out from Rossellin’s embrace as he spoke.

For his faction to develop healthily, the loyalty and identity of the members had to be developed. This would require a culture to be established. Organizations such as Bloodshed Land and Hidden Red Robe Abbey each had their own unique culture.

Han Xiao felt that he did not only have to cultivate a sense of belonging and acknowledgement with the players but also the other members of the army.

Rossellin accepted her job and left the room. Reynold then thanked Han Xiao.

"Thank you for giving my sister a job…"

"You are someone of great importance to me. There isn’t a need to say such pleasantries."

Han Xiao waved his hand indifferently.

Even with Reynold’s silent and serious nature, he could not help but feel touched at this moment.

Having such a boss is truly great.

After a casual chat, Han Xiao said, "I asked you to help Vilna set up an army about a month ago. How are things going?"

"I mobilized a portion of our resources and funds, amounting to about 70,000,000 Enas, to purchase battleships and hire manpower in the name of Floating Dragon," Reynold replied. "However, a portion of them didn’t wish to join Floating Dragon’s Field Team and wanted to join the Black Star Army instead."

Han Xiao fell into deep thought.

A wise individual would be able to tell that Black Star Army’s growth was due to Floating Dragon’s influence.

Currently, the Black Star Army was Floating Dragon’s most powerful force. Joining the Black Star Army meant that they would enjoy Floating Dragon’s influence as well, and it was akin to killing two birds with one stone. Thus, the majority only wanted to join the Black Star Army.

Furthermore, the rumors of Floating Dragon and the Black Star Army splitting up had been spreading. Compared to Floating Dragon, most people felt that the more ambitious Black Star Army had a brighter future.

Even if Han Xiao was not a Beyond Grade A Super yet, the scale of the Black Star Army was larger than Floating Dragon. After all, Ames did not work together with any Star Cluster Civilizations and did not have as many connections as Black Star.

"How large a force do you think 70,000,000 Enas should be able to create?" Han Xiao asked.

"Hmm… it’s difficult to say. According to the current speed at which I am burning through the funds, I will be able to finish the funds within half a year, and the army will end up being slightly smaller than the large mercenary groups."

"It’s too small," Han Xiao immediately replied. "I will give you three months to finish all the funds and invest another 150,000,000 Enas."

Reynold was startled. "Would the cost be too high?"

"It’s alright. I’m not short of money."

Han Xiao smiled. Floating Dragon had given him plenty of assistance when he started out, and he did not plan to save any money when helping Floating Dragon create another Field Team. Furthermore, he gave Jenny a sky-high amount of money every month; he was not bothered about this small amount of money.

The Black Star Army was working together with more than a hundred financial groups and had mines on dozens of planets.

After deducting their monthly expenses, the profits from the mining would be at least 200,000,000 Enas every month.

As long as he had connections in the various governments, earning money was an extremely easy task.

Of course, his wealth still could not be compared to a Star System Civilization, but it was enough to maintain an armed force.

The word ‘poor’ had been struck from his dictionary.

Chapter 709: The Crimson Dynasty: What the Hell, Klent?

"By the way, the report on the DarkStar leader is out today. Take a look," Reynold suddenly said.

Han Xiao took out his communicator.

After just one day, the news about the handover of the DarkStar leader was already spreading all over. The focus of the reports was on Klent being suspected of having connections with DarkStar and the Fallen Ark.

Klent had prepared for this long ago; they wanted to suppress it when the public discussion had just started. Hence, they immediately denied it publicly with a very strong attitude, absolutely refusing to admit to anything, and claimed that this was slander completely made up by Purple Crystal.

"Not admitting it is useless. Purple Crystal definitely have a way to make the DarkStar leader talk." Han Xiao smiled.

Klent’s frequent assassination attempts really annoyed him. Now that he had gotten the opportunity, he was more than happy to cause trouble for Klent.

The secret war was at an impasse. Plus, it could not hurt Klent itself. This DarkStar leader matter, however, would be able to hurt Klent politically.

…

For the next month, Han Xiao waited for Serbia the Fifth’s reply while paying attention to the DarkStar leader incident as it developed. Purple Crystal was determined to blow up this incident, to attract the attention of organizations from everywhere and cause a sensation in the Star Field.

There was no absolute definition on how serious the crime of funding DarkStar and working with Fallen Ark was. If it was not exposed, no one would even care. The development of things like this really depended on the environment at the time. However, it was now a sensitive period during the Crimson Tide, and Klent had shown a weakness. The other Star Cluster civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring were like sharks that had smelled blood, all wanting to make use of this opportunity to bite a piece of meat off Klent and damage their political power.

Klent’s ambition to expand had always made many uninvolved Star Cluster civilizations feel alarmed. Not only did this b\*stard join the Crimson Dynasty to target the Flickering World, Klent also did not want to give up their position in the Shattered Star Ring. They wanted to rule two entire Star Fields. Their appetite was outrageous.

Hence, these Star Cluster civilizations hoped to weaken Klent’s political position in the Shattered Star Ring so that their plan would not go so smoothly.

They could not stop Klent from going to the Flickering World in the future, but they could weaken their reputation in the Shattered Star Ring.

You want to develop in two Star Fields at the same time? You don’t look pretty, but you sure dream big!

As soon as the force of one of them was growing too large, the other civilizations would not mind targeting that civilization together. It was both to damage the competitors as well as to protect their own benefits.

Han Xiao’s acts happened to hit Klent where it hurt, giving a great opportunity to the other Star Cluster civilizations. Suddenly, Klent was facing a situation where they were being targeted by everyone. This caused them a tremendous amount of trouble.

Klent absolutely hated Han Xiao’s guts; this incident had affected their entire strategy.

Yet, after so many failed assassination attempts, Klent had no way to deal with Han Xiao. They had no choice but to solve this issue from a political perspective.

For the last half a month, Purple Crystal and Klent had constantly been fighting verbally. One side was strongly accusing, and the other side insisted on admitting nothing.

To put it simply, this was the situation.

"You’re ruthless, you’re cold-blooded, and you’re unreasonable!" Klent exclaimed.

"No, you!" Purple Crystal retorted.

This kind of conversation kept repeating.

This incident even affected the Crimson Dynasty. The Crimson Dynasty sent an emissary to head to Klent and investigate this thoroughly.

The Crimson Dynasty was negotiating with the Federation of Light on the rights to the Flickering World. At such a crucial moment, Klent happened to get involved in a scandal of them being connected to the Fallen Ark.

That guy was a criminal wanted by all three Universal Civilizations; his identity was extremely sensitive. Klent was the Crimson Dynasty’s new henchman, so the scandal affected the Crimson Dynasty and sent a free political negotiation chip to the Federation of Light.

This made the Crimson Dynasty very irritated. Their stance on this was very clear.

What’s wrong with you, kid!

Some of that intelligence reached Ralph. He shared the inside information about this incident with Han Xiao. On this day, he called Han Xiao once again to speak about this, telling him what had happened.

"The Crimson Dynasty has interfered. They’ve made an agreement with us on Klent’s behalf. Klent will give up a part of their rights in the Shattered Star Ring. In exchange, we have to quickly suppress this incident."

"Did you agree to that?" Han Xiao was curious.

"After all, now that a Universal Civilization has interfered to negotiate, we can’t keep pushing. There are some civilizations that contacted the Federation of Light in private though, hoping that the Federation of Light would speak for us. They probably thought that as the Federation of Light are now fighting for the Flickering World, they won’t give up this chance to hurt the Crimson Dynasty. However, for some reason, the Federation of Light has not done anything. Thus, we can only stop here."

Han Xiao nodded. This was the drawback of being a henchman-the Crimson Dynasty gave up profit on Klent’s behalf in order to reduce their own loss. Of course, the Crimson Dynasty was not yet willing to lose this chess piece, so they definitely promised Klent something in return.

Since Klent wanted to be involved in the Flickering World, they could only take the hit and not say anything.

"So, this incident has ended?"

"Yes, we can’t continue anymore."

"What price did Klent pay?"

"That’s confidential, and I don’t know. The other Star Cluster civilizations will all split the profits that Klent has given up."

"Then, the secret war…" Han Xiao raised his brows.

Ralph sighed and said, "Alas, it has to continue. The Crimson Dynasty refuse to speak about anything regarding the secret war, and the other Star Cluster civilizations stopped caring after they got the profit that Klent gave up. Clearly, they hope that we will continue to fight and harm each other. It is more beneficial for them that way."

"No friends last forever; only profit does. How realistic." Han Xiao shook his head with resignation.

In the original storyline, the Crimson Dynasty would only represent Klent to negotiate at the end of the secret war. Now, however, they had no choice but to clean up the mess that Klent had made. This was because of him.

This was something that had not happened before. It would definitely change the direction of the entire storyline.

Han Xiao pondered. He felt that because Klent had bled quite badly, in order to heal up, they might put more focus in the secret war and fight more passionately.

He shared this thought with Ralph, who smiled strangely.

"Did you know that because of this, Heber has become unhappy with Klent?"

Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled, and he started to speculate.

Originally, the Tyrant was Klent’s only Beyond Grade A ally. Since Klent was flirting around with EsGod and was caught by Heber in the act, it was like a wife who discovered the mistress.

Looks like the secret war will be in even more of a stalemate. It should last till the start of Version 3.0.

Han Xiao was quite satisfied with this result. Creating both internal and external problems for Klent was his return gift for Klent’s constant assassination attempts.

"One more thing, Serbia the Fifth told us that you want to borrow Rossellin’s ability to help Godora clear their bloodline conflict."

"That’s right." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"This matter is a little bit sensitive, so he wanted to invite us to be the notary and carry out this plan under Purple Crystal’s name. What do you think?"

Han Xiao was stunned. Then he figured it out. Serbia the Fifth had made a choice and decided to take his suggestion.

Serbia the Fifth had even found a better excuse of using Purple Crystal’s name to carry out the plan, so it would look like it was a higher-level civilization helping Godora.

As a Star Cluster civilization was involved, the Godoran government would receive much less disapproval, and its people would accept it more easily. Many would feel that the higher-level civilization was more reliable than their own government.

Han Xiao thought about it, ended the call, and called Serbia the Fifth. It was picked up right after one ring. Clearly, Serbia the Fifth had been waiting

"Your Excellency Black Star, I plan to use your method, but I hope that this can be done under the Purple Crystal Civilization’s name. Maybe we won’t be able to announce that this is your plan." Serbia the Fifth went straight to the point. "But I’m willing to pay a bigger price in private. What do you think?"

Han Xiao scratched his eyelid and said, "Alright then."

His main goal was to settle the (Bloodline) mission, so he did not really care about whether this relatively small achievement would be announced or not.

Serbia the Fifth was relieved. He explained, "That’s great. It’s not that I don’t trust you, but this matter is too important. I have to find a gentler method so that the people of Godora will be more willing to accept it…"

Actually, this was just one of the factors. Serbia the Fifth was still not very assured as Han Xiao was not an official force after all, so he had pulled the Purple Crystal Civilization in as insurance. Of course, he would not voice this reason.

"Since you agreed, I shall bring Rossellin over to discuss the details."

"Okay, I’ll have Nagakin fetch you. Come to our mother planet directly."

"… Nagakin again?" Han Xiao suddenly realized that every time he interacted with the Godoran Civilization, they seemed to send Nagakin to host him.

"Er… aren’t you guys friends?" Serbia the Fifth wondered. He threw this unimportant issue aside and said, "Anyway, I’ll be waiting for you on our mother planet."

Han Xiao nodded and hung up the communication before calling Rossellin.

"Pack up and get ready, I have a job for you."

A few days later, on the mother planet of Godora, a spaceship landed on the military dock. Han Xiao and Rossellin walked out of the hatch with Nagakin leading the way.

They took the hovering car and arrived at the government affairs building. Han Xiao and Rossellin went straight to Serbia the Fifth’s office.

"You’re finally here." Serbia the Fifth had been waiting for quite some time. He quickly stood up and welcomed Han Xiao.

After a few greetings, they sat down. Serbia the Fifth sized Rossellin up from time to time.

At this point, Rossellin showed the look of the pope that she had once been-noble and elegant with calm eyes. Serbia the Fifth could not figure her out. He only felt that this woman had a vibe of being someone very important and not simple.

The two sides had worked together for many years and were very familiar with each other, so Han Xiao directly asked, "Cut to the chase, what plan do you have?"

With his position now, a Star System civilization was not as important as before. He planned to quickly settle the (Bloodline) mission and get the Grade S mission reward.

He still had some time before his holiday ended. Plus, Klent was troubled by internal conflicts, so he was not needed in the war for the time being. He did not want to spend too much time on (Bloodline]. He planned to use the rest of the holiday to do missions and get more Random Rewards.

It was best to have more Mission Completion Cards in stock before Version 3.0 arrived.

"Hmm, according to Rossellin’s ability, we have prepared a few plans to choose from…"

Serbia the Fifth took out a few files and gave them to Han Xiao.

Chapter 710: Confused DarkStar Leader

In two minutes, Han Xiao read through Serbia the Fifth’s plan. He passed the files to Rossellin then nodded. "Looks like you don’t plan to seek the opinion of the Godorans."

"Although this plan is beneficial to the future of the civilization, the free will of most people will only be a burden. This plan can only be carried out without seeking approval from everybody." This meeting was off the records, so Serbia the Fifth was more direct.

Rossellin read through the file very quickly. With a calm and reserved look, she slightly nodded and said, "I understand your request. Are you sure there’s no need to plant something else in the minds of your people?"

Serbia the Fifth wiped the cold sweat from his brow and said, "No, no, eliminating discrimination is enough."

"Okay, if it’s just eliminating discrimination, it’s easy for me."

Rossellin gave Serbia the Fifth a mysterious smile that made his heart shake a little.

To outsiders, Rossellin was not as casual as when facing Han Xiao. On the way, Han Xiao had told her to maintain her standard and not scare Serbia the Fifth with her real colors. Rossellin looked at Serbia the Fifth with an elegant smile and explained her plan.

"Black Star has already told me the situation. To my understanding, there are three fundamental causes to the bloodline conflict of Godora.

"One, the pureblood traditional concept passed down through the years. In the galactic environment, only a small fraction of the purebloods still firmly believe in this concept. I call these people the Diehards, and their minds are the hardest to change.

"Two, discrimination caused by biological differences. This comes from the instinctive disgust of an intelligent life when seeing a deviant form. Many of the purebloods don’t want to discriminate against the hybrids, but when they see them, they still uncontrollably feel a sense of disgust. This is the cause of discrimination for most people. In order to change this, I think the key point is the aesthetic sense.

"Three, the hatred accumulated from the large number of conflicts caused by many years of discrimination. This is considered a historical problem. Plus, due to discrimination, the average societal position of purebloods is higher than the hybrids, so the purebloods have more power in various industries. This can be seen as a class conflict. I can temporarily suppress this type of hatred, but if you people don’t change the current situation, after a long time, these conflicts will happen

again."

Serbia the Fifth had a headache just from hearing these problems.

In his eyes, every single one of these issues was close to unsolvable. He could see how extremely difficult these problems were just from listening to Rossellin talking about them. He once again started to doubt the feasibility of this plan.

As if Rossellin saw through his worries, she calmly said, "On a more positive note, it would take at least decades to make these problems less severe with normal methods. However, now that I’m here, I can make this process thousands of times faster. The first two points are the main causes, and as long as the problems with the Diehards and the aesthetic sense are resolved, the class conflicts will gradually be reduced."

Serbia the Fifth took a deep breath, stood up, and bowed deeply toward Han Xiao and Rossellin.

"I’m counting on you!"

It was a normal morning. The warm yellow sunlight woke up the asleep city.

In a commercial square filled with tall buildings on the Godoran mother planet, hovering vehicles shuttled between buildings. People that equipped flying runes rose and landed on the open-air platforms that extended from the tall buildings. It was a boisterous and hectic scene.

This time, at a hovering public bus station on an open-air platform, there was a long queue. It was rush hour for the working class in the morning. These Godorans heading to their jobs were waiting for the public transport.

The production of a Star System civilization was more than enough to feed lazy shut-ins, but as the capital of a civilization, the mother planet had maintained vigorous vitality. Those that resided on the mother planet were all willing to work hard, unlike those at the edge of colonial planets that all stayed at home and had no concept of ‘working’.

Rudy was in the middle of the queue. His outfit looked decent, like an elite of society. However, unlike the Godorans around, he did not have protruding ears, and his ears were spiral shaped holes. He also did not wear a ponytail or any ornaments on his hair because he did not have hair. His facial organs were also further apart from each other.

He was the only hybrid in the long queue.

Rudy could feel the strange looks with suppressed disgust coming from around him. He had a normal expression on his face and looked straight ahead, as if he was unaffected. But in his heart, he wished that the hovering public bus would reach the station soon so that he would no longer have to endure this treatment of being watched by so many people like an animal in the zoo.

Rudy was sixty-three years old this year. By Godoran standards, he was middle-aged. He was a very senior employee of a huge business, and his income was rather high. Supposedly, he should be middle class in the society, but his appearance had given him obstructions everywhere. He knew that his current position was the highest that he could achieve, and he would never be promoted again.

His most hated thing each day was going to work, not because his job was tiring but because going to work meant he had to socialize and endure all kinds of strange looks. He had been enduring a huge amount of mental stress every single day, but he could not express any of that emotion on his face. In the countless times he woke up in the middle of the night because of that stress, he would just sit there and stare into the darkness, thinking that he might as well quit the job; why should he put himself through all that?

But every time he saw his sleeping wife beside him, he would put those thoughts away.

His wife was a beautiful pureblood. Back then, his wife had ignored her family’s opposition and married him, a hybrid. She had blessed him with two children. Even after being married for so many years, her family had never accepted him, but his wife almost never complained. For the sake of his family, Rudy did not dare quit his job; he could only let his anxiety and irritation be vented out silently during the times he puffed.

To him, life was a pool of still water, a gray silent film that played on repeat every day, only starting to have colors when he got home and saw the smiles of his wife and children. Rudy had no expectations for the future anymore. Maybe not being able to see his path ahead was good for him; a life that he could see the end of would be terrifying.

Rudy smiled self-deprecatingly. He overheard the conversation of the two people behind him who had suddenly started chatting.

"Have you heard? The DarkStar leader was captured some time ago, and the DarkStar organization has been deemed to be completely eliminated."

"It’s been half a month. Of course I’ve heard."

"Hehe, there are reports that say the DarkStar leader’s trial has ended, and he’s locked up in Rainbow Prison."

"I did not know that. Tell me more…"

Listening to the clearly deliberate conversation behind him, Rudy could only act as if he could not hear it.

Due to DarkStar’s existence, the hybrids received even more hatred. After the DarkStar organization was destroyed, purebloods had mentioned DarkStar around him more than once, on purpose or otherwise, as if it was some kind of mockery.

Rudy did not agree with DarkStar’s philosophy at all; a hybrid that yearned for peace like him even hated DarkStar’s actions. However, to the purebloods, it seemed that every hybrid admired DarkStar. DarkStar’s ending meant the failure of the hybrids, so they could put on the looks of victors and feel superior.

At this time, a projected screen appeared between the tall buildings, attracting everyone’s attention.

Serbia the Fifth appeared on the screen. He sat straight and faced the camera with a serious face, as if he had something important to announce.

The same scene appeared on every colonial planet of Godora. It was an announcement for the entire civilization.

Serbia the Fifth slowly spoke.

"Today, on behalf of the Godoran government, I’m going to announce a very important decision. In order to avoid tragedies similar to the DarkStar incident in the future, we have decided to accept help from the Purple Crystal Civilization to use an unorthodox method to solve the bloodlike discrimination problem that has affected us for a very long time…"

Serbia the Fifth read the long script that he had prepared beforehand, describing the situation as the Purple Crystal Civilization suggesting to help and him deciding to accept their help after careful consideration. He sugarcoated the terms and words used to reduce the objection of the people as much as possible.

However, all the Godorans were still petrified by this news and were all unable to speak.

Only after the news had ended for a few seconds did a deafening uproar start.

"This is too sudden. There were no signs at

all!"

"This is brainwashing!"

"Why does our perception have to be changed? Free will is inviolable! Has Serbia the Fifth lost his mind?"

"Will there be any side effects?"

"This is the Purple Crystal Civilization’s idea? Then maybe it’s reliable."

The Godorans around discussed the issue loudly and reacted in various ways, mostly with shock and disgruntlement.

Rudy did not take part in the discussion. His eyes were wide open, and his face was filled with disbelief.

At this moment, he felt that as if his heart that had been numb for a long time had finally started beating vigorously again.

He seemed to see a tint of light in his dark future.

On this day, people from every industry started to use their relationship network to inquire more about what the government meant. The people were flustered.

No one was willing to let someone else change their thoughts, even if it was a huge good deed beneficial to the collective. As expected, this caused backlash due to individual willingness. Serbia the Fifth promised subsidies, reduced taxes, and all kinds of benefits for those who accepts the ‘Discrimination Transformation’ plan; however, he did not give them the option to reject.

There was outrage, and protests appeared one after another. Serbia the Fifth’s plan had shaken the entire society, but he was determined not to change his mind.

With Purple Crystal’s interference, the internal resistance was suppressed forcefully. The government started to operate to his will.

The upper class of society was basically controlled entirely by purebloods. These people had a lot of power, and most of them were Diehards. They did not receive any information beforehand either. Although they hated Serbia the Fifth’s plan, they did not immediately stand out to oppose it but stayed calm and observed the situation.

Purple Crystal’s name helped Serbia the Fifth not receive more objections; the reputation of a Star Cluster civilization had the Godorans slightly under control. Even though Serbia the Fifth’s actions were almost like those of a dictator, many Godorans believed that this was the Purple Crystal Civilization’s decision.

Due to many factors, Serbia the Fifth was able to forcefully execute this almost insane plan.

Seeing that they could not change the government’s mind at all, the attention of all the Godorans was focused on the first test area of the ‘Discrimination Transformation’ plan announced by Serbia the Fifth. It was the Colonial Planet Gautin.

A planet with extremely low importance, filled with jobless shut-ins, was a perfect place for the test. Even if the results were not good, it would have a very limited impact on the entire civilization.

In Rainbow Prison, the DarkStar leader sat at the corner of his cell. It was pitch black, and he could only hear his own breathing in the dark.

His trial had ended. Godora and Purple Crystal had both gotten what they wanted, so he was locked up and would be spending the rest of his life in prison.

The hope that supported his belief was destroyed. It was as if the DarkStar leader had lost his spine, and his heart was numb and emotionless.

The Rainbow Prison could shatter the belief of DarkStar members. He did not know if he could hold on to his own belief in the future, but he did not care anymore.

Clank!

The narrow feeding window at the bottom of the cell door opened. A plate of food and a beam of light entered the cell.

"Recently, Serbia the Fifth announced a plan to brainwash all Godorans to eliminate discrimination for hybrids. Did your DarkStar convince him and make him betray us?"

The prison guard outside the door suddenly spoke with a sarcastic tone. He then closed the feeding window and left.

In the dark, the DarkStar leader suddenly opened his eyes. His numb eyes were filled with shock. He was absolutely confused.

Brainwashing the entire civilization?

What the hell? Could it be that we have the same belief but you’re much smarter than me?

You should be the one leading DarkStar!

Chapter 711: Discrimination Transformation Movement

Planet Gautin was the first testing area of the Discrimination Transformation plan. Be it pureblood or hybrid, all Godorans paid attention to Gautin, wanting to know how exactly Serbia the Fifth would do it.

A Purple Crystal flagship arrived at Planet Gautin and used some kind of device to send an invisible Psychic Current across the entire planet. Serbia the Fifth said that this was a secret device built with Star Cluster Grade technology that could change the thinking of Godorans over a large area. He once again promised the civilians that this device was very reliable. Actually, this was just a bluff that he had discussed with Purple Crystal to prove that this plan had Purple Crystal’s approval so that the civilians would not be as flustered.

The key person to carry out the transformation, however, was Rossellin. She displayed her ability to the fullest for the first time in front of Han Xiao. The large area Psychic Current that the Purple Crystal flagship was sending to Gautin was actually Rossellin’s Esper ability, enhanced by a device specifically designed to strengthen Psychic abilities. This made the range of her Esper ability increase many times over.

Psychics also had the ability to hypnotize and brainwash, but the accuracy and range were not as high as Rossellin’s Esper ability, (Contagious Ideology). Her Esper ability was a very gentle brainwash, completed subtly; it would not affect the personality of the target and would only give the target new ways of looking at things. This could even be explained as Rossellin showing the target a new angle of looking at the world. This Esper ability was very suitable for spreading religion and building beliefs.

The transformation lasted two days. The stay-at-homes of Gautin were initially trepidatious, but as time passed, they realized that their thinking did not change at all. They got confused and wondered if it was ineffective.

Two days later, the Purple Crystal flagship left. All the Godorans were focusing on the effect of the test, and Planet Gautin was all over the internet. Everyone was discussing it.

“Are there any Gautin residents? Come out and tell us how you feel.”

“I don’t feel any changes. Am I the only one?”

“No, I’m on Gautin too, didn’t feel any changes.”

“Did it fail?”

“Er, not sure if you guys feel the same way, but at first I thought it had no effects, but just now, I went to chat with a hybrid friend. Originally, I was a tiny bit repulsed by him, but when I saw him just now, I felt totally peaceful and calm. I even felt he looked somewhat handsome… ahem, this is anonymous. I don’t want him to know.”

“For me, it’s not exactly the same. I have a hybrid friend too. Originally, I thought he looked quite ugly, but when I had a with him earlier, although I still felt he looked ugly, that occasional disgust had disappeared.”

The people of Godora started to figure out what change the Godora residents underwent. Those that were transformed retained their own personality and even knew what changes they had gone through.

This result made the Godorans much less worried-at least their minds were not forcefully twisted.

Serbia the Fifth had been paying attention to the public reaction. He saw the effects of the test and decided to host another press conference, emphasizing on the fact that the ‘Discrimination Transformation’ plan was harmless.

At the same time, the government also secretly guided the public opinion and tried to make the people feel that accepting the hybrids was a policy that would never change. This would lead them to think that since the overall trend could not be changed, maybe changing themselves might be a good idea, it would make society a better place too.

The success of the test and the manipulation of public opinion did indeed make some civilians feel less alarmed. Some people even acknowledged the idea that accepting the transformation to not feel disgusted by these hybrids would make their daily life more peaceful and harmonious.

With the first success, Serbia the Fifth grew more confident. After observing for quite a long time and making sure that the Gautin residents certainly did not suffer any side effects, he finally stopped worrying and fully carried out the plan. The colonial planets of Godora would be accepting the transformation one after another.

Godorans called this incident the Discrimination Transformation Movement.

The pureblood Diehards had power and force. Even though the Discrimination Transformation had no side effects, they were still unwilling to accept. Hence, using their power, they started to create obstructions to Serbia the Fifth.

When the relationship network of these upper-class people started to operate, even the government operations were affected. The Diehards stirred up public opinion to smear Serbia the Fifth, saying that he was even more insane than DarkStar and that he was leading Godora to its grave, becoming a slave of a higher civilization.

Many people were convinced by these claims and became furious, claiming that the government not even asking for their opinion to change their minds was an act of not treating them as proper citizens. Serbia the Fifth’s reputation on the internet plummeted. Some even called him ‘the second generation DarkStar leader’.

However, not only was Serbia the Fifth not enraged, he was happy about it instead. This was an opportunity for him to step up and explain to the people more clearly; whether the people would believe him or not did not matter.

Of course, some conspiracists completely ignored the explanations and created even more trouble. Serbia the Fifth did not hold back against them; he sent his men to kindly invite these people to a friendly tea session so that they would stay quiet.

He did not care about those smearing accusations. In his eyes, that was just short-term damage. As soon as the plan was completed, the entire society would naturally think very highly of him, and he would become the wisest leader of Godora since the start of history.

The upper class saw that swaying public opinion was useless, so they started to secretly fund the government officials with a lot of power, hoping to impeach Serbia the Fifth and change the leader.

Sadly, ever since Godora entered the Interstellar Era, they had taken back the tons of privileges for the royalties. Furthermore, Godora was hereditary, not democratic, and Serbia the Fifth had Purple Crystal’s support. His position was extremely firm. Therefore, Serbia the Fifth sneered at the actions of the upper-class people.

Come on, you guys are so weak.

Serbia the Fifth did not want to waste time dealing with these people, so he directly invited many Diehards in the upper class and made a very firm stand. “If you people continue to cause trouble, you will have to pay the government back for all the benefits it has given you, doubled.”

The upper-class people folded. Seeing that all their plans came to nothing, they realized that they could not stop this from happening. Hence, they changed the focus of their objection into claiming that since the purebloods had to accept transformation, the hybrids had to too.

The hybrids had been oppressed for a long time; their hatred had been building up. Through research and studies, some rebellious hybrids were unhappy with the Discrimination Transformation Movement. They felt that after the purebloods discriminated against them for so many years and caused so many tragedies, wanting the hybrids to immediately forget about all that as soon as the discrimination was gone was too easy for the purebloods.

Serbia the Fifth did not ignore this. The hybrids had to accept the transformation equally.

The Godora Discrimination Transformation Movement caused a sensation in the galaxy. A tiny Star System civilization successfully occupied the head news for this period. Even the other Star Cluster civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring were paying attention out of curiosity.

A government brainwashing all their people was such a rare occurrence.

Countless galactic reporters swarmed over, so Serbia the Fifth decided to host a press conference and answered the questions of those reporters.

One day later, those renowned news outlets published their own reports. Among them, one report became extremely famous and received approval from the highest number of people.

In that report, Serbia the Fifth received a very positive description. He was praised over the top. The reporter felt that the Discrimination Transformation Movement was an extremely strong and effective medicine that was perfect for the bloodline conflict illness. Only a bold and confident leader like Serbia the Fifth would dare to execute this plan that looked completely insane. Although it had met a lot of obstructions, it was actually beneficial for the civilization’s future.

In the report, Serbia the Fifth was described as a wise, visionary, and bold leader.

The report also included interviews with many Godoran hybrids who were roaming outside the Godoran Civilization. Quite a number expressed their intention to go back to Godora. The reporter called this ‘a sign of Godora’s complete unification’. The goal that DarkStar had failed to achieve was now achieved by Serbia the Fifth of all people and achieved in a much better way.

Purple Crystal was seen as being passionate and responsible for willingly solving the internal conflict of a civilization under their ruling. Their credibility thus increased. This was an unexpected but pleasant surprise. It indirectly increased Purple Crystal’s area support from the three border Star Systems.

The report also mentioned Han Xiao, saying that Han Xiao capturing the DarkStar leader some time ago was the root of everything that came after. It made Godora and Purple Crystal closer and indirectly caused the Discrimination Transformation Movement.

Although those outsiders did not know that it was Han Xiao who planned the Discrimination Transformation Movement behind the curtains, this report did not forget about him and believed that Black Star’s contribution to this incident was just as important. Because of that, his reputation in the galaxy became more positive as well.

Han Xiao saw this report too and was quite happy about it as well.

In his previous life, no player had ever completed the [Bloodline) mission, and Godora’s bloodline conflicts had carried on. Although another Star System level terrorist organization like DarkStar never appeared again, the ever-growing internal conflict caused the hybrids to have fewer and fewer opportunities to rise higher in society. They were all lower-class citizens. This caused many talented hybrids to never be discovered and fueled the birth of many rebel organizations. Godora suffered continuously.

If not for the mission, Han Xiao would not have cared about Godora’s internal conflicts. His initial motive was just to do the mission and get the reward, but it seemed that the results generated by that were unexpectedly positive.

The Godoran government now completed what their arch-enemy had wanted to achieve. Han Xiao suddenly felt interested to see how the DarkStar leader would react to this.

Rainbow Prison was an independent galactic fortress floating in the universe. Its security was very tight.

Han Xiao had access to almost everywhere in Godora now; he could even enter Serbia the Fifth’s bedroom if he wanted, not to mention a mere prison. He requested to visit Rainbow Prison, and Godora agreed without hesitation.

The Blacklight Stealth arrived at Rainbow Prison and stopped at the dock. The warden came to welcome Han Xiao.

“It’s my honor to meet you, hero of the Golden Gal Badge, ally of Godora, Your Excellency Black Star.”

The warden was very respectful.

“I want to visit the DarkStar members inside Rainbow Prison and talk to the DarkStar leader. Thanks, warden.” Han Xiao smiled.

“Please follow me.”

The warden led the way ahead, and Han Xiao followed him into Rainbow Prison.

He passed by one cell after another, in them were all DarkStar members. Han Xiao even saw the former DarkStar officer Degulish. This guy had electromagnetic cuffs all over his body, and his face was numb and lifeless. Han Xiao knew from one look that his life here was blissful.

Finally, Han Xiao arrived at the cell with the tightest security. The DarkStar leader was right inside.

The warden opened the cell door personally and invited Han Xiao to go in, while he wisely waited outside to give the two of them space for a private conversation.

Han Xiao walked into the cell, and the door closed behind him. The room was completely dark. He summoned a Floating Guard, which acted as a light source and lit up the room.

The DarkStar leader sat in the corner. Surprisingly, he was not listless and hopeless anymore. He stared at Han Xiao with a complicated emotion in his eyes.

“It’s you.”

“Yes, it’s me; yes, I’ve come; yes, I’m here to talk to you… I’ve answered your next three questions. Now, can we talk about something else?” Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

The DarkStar leader’s words were stuck in his throat. Why do you like to stop others from talking so much?

This time, the DarkStar leader suddenly realized that he and Black Star had been enemies for so long, but this was their first proper conversation. He could not help but feel that things had changed so much.

Although it was said that the person who knows you best is your enemy, DarkStar realized that he knew almost nothing about DarkStar. He had no idea what kind of person the man that destroyed DarkStar almost all by himself was.

Chapter 712: DarkStar's End, the Leader's Sacrifice

Han Xiao was surprised as he sized up the DarkStar leader. "You look quite well."

"I've heard that the Godora government is using controversial methods to solve the bloodline conflict... and they're doing much better than I did." The DarkStar leader's tone was complicated.

"From a war prisoner's perspective, you know rather a lot of what's happening out there," Han Xiao joked.

The DarkStar leader shook his head. "Did you know, I'm going to be executed soon?"

"Hmm? Isn't your punishment indefinite imprisonment?"

"It changed, probably because of the Crimson Dynasty's request." The DarkStar leader sighed.

Han Xiao slightly nodded.

The Crimson Dynasty wanted to suppress Klent's crimes as soon as possible. Thus, they wanted to kill this important witness. Since the political deal was completed, the DarkStar leader no longer had any value. Purple Crystal and Godora did not reject the Crimson Dynasty's request. Although the DarkStar leader was a Calamity Grade Super that had some research value, on the political gambling table between civilizations, he was just a slightly bigger chip.

What made Han Xiao curious was, despite knowing that he would be executed soon, the DarkStar leader looked very calm.

"You don't hate me?" Han Xiao was curious.

"A few days ago, I did, but not now." The DarkStar leader had a complicated look in his eyes. "I was once lost. I made a deal with Klent. If I did some dirty work for them, they promised to build a home for the Godoran hybrids in the Flickering World in the future.

"When I was captured by you, I thought everything was over, but I never expected that... when I was in the deepest despair, I would see real change.

"I've been thinking these few days. DarkStar's existence made Godora realize the dangers of the bloodline conflict. Now that I've been captured, their last obstacle has gone. In order to avoid another me appearing, Godora finally decided to completely solve the bloodline conflicts. Although the method is different from mine, the Godoran government is doing it much better than I did...

"Maybe you don't believe it, but everything I've done was to change the situation that the hybrids were in. However, my identity only allowed me to use extreme methods. The future I have been dreaming of is like a blurry shadow, far and unreachable no matter what I do. You're the one that made me see that it turns out my belief wasn't unachievable. Only, I had to pay the price... that is my life.

"I don't hate you. If I wasn't captured by you, the Discrimination Transformation Movement wouldn't have happened. To use my life to build a foundation for my dream, I have no regrets. You've given meaning to my death."

The DarkStar leader's tone had a sense of relief, and he even smiled faintly.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and was unaffected. He slowly said, "Don't make yourself sound so noble. You're still a terrorist who's killed countless people."

Han Xiao would not pity a villain just because he confessed before his death. If the DarkStar leader had not been captured, he might not have been willing to give up his life even if he knew that it would change the hybrids' situation.

"I know." The DarkStar looked down.

Han Xiao touched his chin and smiled. He had a wicked idea. "However, your guess is wrong. You're not the reason that Godora made up its mind to solve the bloodline conflict. You're not as important as you think you are."

"Then why..." The DarkStar leader was confused.

"To be honest, I'm the one that convinced Serbia the Fifth to carry out the Discrimination Transformation Movement." Han Xiao raised his brows.

The DarkStar leader's eyes opened wide. He could no longer stay calm and stood right up with shock.

He did not think that Han Xiao would come all the way to bluff before someone that was about to die.

"Why are you helping me?" The DarkStar leader's lips were shaking.

Han Xiao tutted and said, "Help you? Are we close? Don't be sentimental. I have my reasons, but they have nothing to do with you."

The DarkStar leader stayed silent. The person who had captured him was Han Xiao, and the person that had completed his dream and belief was Han Xiao. His emotions were complicated and tangled up.

In the end, all the confusion and emotions became two sincere words of gratitude.

"Thank you."

Han Xiao was a little surprised. He nodded and did not say anything.

He felt that there was nothing more to talk about, so he turned around and was about to leave the cell.

This time, the DarkStar leader suddenly spoke again.

"Please wait! I have one last request, my only request."

Han Xiao turned around and asked, "What else do you want to say?"

"You've risen in just ten years," the DarkStar leader said slowly. "I've studied all your battles in the past, and I believe you have the blood of the fighter race that can absorb a part of the enemy's abilities by killing them. This is why your strength has been growing so fast."

"So?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

This was no secret, nor did he plan to hide it, so it would definitely be discovered, except no one would know that it was because of the player interface and would only think he was talented.

The DarkStar leader took a deep breath.

"Rather than being executed by Godora, I'd prefer to die in your hands. You have more rights to judge me than them. Plus... this is the only way I can pay you back," the DarkStar leader said with a relieved tone.

Han Xiao was shocked, and a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

_____________________

You have triggered a unique hidden mission [The DarkStar Leader's Last Wish]!

Mission Introduction: You have destroyed DarkStar, but you also completed DarkStar's belief. The DarkStar leader hopes to die by your hand and give you his abilities.

Mission Requirement: Kill the DarkStar leader.

Reward: 150,000,000 Experience, 1 Random Reward, 2 abilities/talents of the DarkStar leader.

_____________________

A hidden mission...

Han Xiao's eyes flickered. The mission to defeat the Germinal Organization leader also rewarded him with two abilities or talents, which he received a Molding Talent from and started his path of being a boss.

The DarkStar leader was also the boss of a major main storyline. This unique mission was a surprise of this visit and made him rather delighted.

Han Xiao took a long look at the DarkStar leader before raising his right hand. More than ten Mechanical Force lightning chains launched from his palm into the void and connected to the storage of the Blacklight Stealth at the dock, apostilizing the dozen powerful mechanical soldiers.

Energy flowed into Han Xiao's body continuously through the Mechanical Force, and his own Energy Rank grew rapidly. Psionic energy appeared in his hand like a bubble, highly compressed and giving off horrifying energy.

"I accept," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

The DarkStar leader exhaled and dissipated the tiny bit of energy in his body. Then, he slowly closed his eyes.

...

Outside the cell, the warden was walking back and forth, waiting for Han Xiao to come out.

At this time, a loud and violent explosion suddenly came from within the cell, the entire prison seemed to tremble!

Boom!

The warden was the closest to it, and he was almost deafened. His expression drastically changed, and he hastily yelled, "Your Excellency Black Star, what happened..."

While he called for Han Xiao, he opened the cell door. The moment the door opened, he saw what had happened inside, and his yell immediately stopped.

Broken limbs and pieces of flesh splattered all over the floor and the walls, like someone had exploded from within. Han Xiao had a psionic energy shield in front of him, so the splashed flesh and blood did not land on his body. A head was rolling on the floor. The warden looked at it, and it belonged to the DarkStar leader.

"Yo—You..." The warden was dumbfounded.

"He begged me to kill him. You guys were going to execute him anyway, so I might as well help you with it."

Han Xiao deactivated the shield, glanced at the warden, and left the cell, leaving the warden to stand there stunned.

The DarkStar leader was an important prisoner, so the warden did not know what to do as he looked at the gory cell. He let his deputy host Han Xiao in his place while he endured the discomfort and hastily reported this to his superiors.

The warden thought that he was going to get into big trouble, but when the superiors heard that Han Xiao was the one that did it, they had no intention of holding anyone responsible.

With Han Xiao's position in Godora now, killing a death row prisoner was not a problem at all. Furthermore, the DarkStar leader had been captured by Han Xiao in the first place, so Godora was not so pedantic as to hurt their relationship with Han Xiao for such a small matter.

It could be said that Han Xiao could almost do anything he wanted in Godora.

While being shocked by Han Xiao's influence, the warden hastily hurried back to the dock, worried that he might have made Han Xiao unhappy earlier. He barely made it and waved Han Xiao off.

...

Han Xiao activated autopilot before going to the training room. He opened the interface to look at the mission and receive the reward.

_____________________

You have completed [The DarkStar Leader's Last Wish]!

You have received 150,000,000 Experience!

You have received 1 Random Reward.

_____________________

Han Xiao nodded. His level was too high. Although 150 million was not little, it was not a lot.

As usual, he did not use the Random Reward, which he now had three of. He was extremely confident with his own luck, so he decided to stock up and do a consecutive draw after completing [Bloodline]. The Mission Completion Card was not a rare reward, so he probably would not need to touch Feidin to obtain it.

The final reward was the highlight.

_____________________

You have received reward: Two abilities/talents of the DarkStar leader.

Reminder: The DarkStar leader is a Mage, so some of the abilities have been adjusted to your class.

Randomizing... complete.

Please select two from the five options below as the reward:

[Advanced Elemental Affinity] - Talent: +80% Energy recovery speed.

[Trained Mind] - Talent: Your mind has been to a hundred secret places in secondary dimensions. +20 Psychological Resistance, +10% MYS, +5% INT.

[Mysterious Vision] - Ability: +25% MYS. Duration: 10 minutes. Cooldown: 25 minutes. Cost: 450 Energy.

[Painful Revenge] - Ability: You can stimulate your cell potential through pain and gain strength exceeding your limits. For every 3% of health you lose, you can deal melee attack damage equal to 1.5% of your health. Cost: 300 Energy.

[Luck Curse] - Ability: Using your luck as a sacrifice, you pray for the blessing of the God of Misfortune. -90% LUK, -90% LUK of the target. Duration: 3 hours. No cost. Before the curse ends, this ability cannot be used again.

_____________________

These abilities are not too bad... Han Xiao nodded.

The spells of Mages were powered by magic energy, which was not compatible with Mechanics, so most of the spells were not in the range of the randomization. Only a small portion of the abilities could be adjusted to become compatible. This way, the low-level spells of the DarkStar leader were all eliminated, and the chance of getting good abilities was higher.

The DarkStar leader was a boss-type character who had Molding Talents as well, but they would not appear as one of the options every single time. Han Xiao was not disappointed. He only glanced at the options shortly before he made his choice.

Chapter 713: Grade S Mission Reward!

[Mysterious Vision] was useless, and [Advanced Elemental Affinity] was not very useful either. Recovering mana through the health-mana cycle was much more efficient. Plus, Han Xiao would not be short of mana because of Apostilization.

[Trained Mind] was not too bad, but its percentage increase was too little. In terms of Psychological Resistance, he had [Advanced Mental Toughness]. In terms of Intelligence, he also had [Research Theory] and [Battlefield Wisdom].

Other than that, he had [One Against the World] and others. Although [Trained Mind] was not too bad, its bonus was nothing notable. In comparison, Han Xiao felt that the last two abilities were more interesting.

[Painful Revenge] was suitable given how tanky he was. It would give him the ability to basically reflect half of the damage to the enemy. It did not look a lot, but it would be quite considerable because of his recovery speed.

He had about 200,000 health points. For example, if the damage dealt to him had accumulated up to 300%, [Painful Revenge] would be triggered a hundred times, dealing about 300,000 damage, which would be quite a lot. Furthermore, his health points would increase as he leveled up, which meant that this ability had room to grow.

Han Xiao felt that this ability should be the result of adjusting Chain of Pain. Although it had its limitations due to the fact that it could only be triggered at close range, it would be very useful against those who tried to get close to him. After all, 'focus fire on myself' was rather risky.

Among Calamity Grade Supers, Han Xiao was now at the very top, so he had to prepare for the eventuality of facing a Beyond Grade A Super. By then, he would definitely get beaten up quite badly, so reflecting the damage would be very useful.

Furthermore, his close-range combat capability increased as he obtained the ability to Apostilize his machinery. Close range combat once again became one of his regular combat modes, so [Painful Revenge] would definitely be triggered.

Han Xiao had always wanted to let go of the 'Getting Beaten Style', but to his resignation, he realized that he could not escape the fate of being a tank and getting beaten up was still one of the most effective styles.

Another thing that surprised him was [Luck Curse], which he felt was the most valuable of all the rewards given in this mission.

This ability was double-edged, since both his Luck and the target's Luck would reduce by ninety percent. However, with how 'many' Luck points he had, whether it was reduced or not would not make a difference since it would not go below zero.

Han Xiao did not believe that anyone would have lower Luck than him!

He was extremely confident in this.

Han Xiao had made up his mind the minute he saw [Luck Curse]. It was basically an ability to greatly reduce the target's Luck without any side effects.

It was a perfect fit for him!

With a faint smile on his face, Han Xiao confirmed the options.

You have received [Painful Revenge]!

You have received [Luck Curse]!

Han Xiao closed his eyes to feel the new abilities for a while. Then he opened his eyes and took a deep breath with content.

The DarkStar leader gave me two decent abilities. It's indeed true that honest, loyal, and pure men like me get rewarded.

Han Xiao rubbed his hands and chuckled without any shame.

After accumulating over a very long time, he had created a very strong combat ability that could defeat just about any Calamity Grade Super. However, he did not become overconfident at all; he knew more than anyone how powerful and strong Beyond Grade As were. Normal people would never be able to reach Beyond Grade A. Every single one of them was a boss among bosses. They all had plenty of Molding Talents and bug-like abilities.

His style was far from being the most powerful among Beyond Grade As. For example, EsGod was almost almighty; Thousand Shadows' abilities were extremely mysterious; Ames' Force Field was great for both attack and defense; the Tyrant's body could penetrate Fixed Stars; plus, there was the famous Mechanic Empire. The biggest specialty of his current combat style was just being tanky and difficult to kill. It needed further development.

Now, I just have to wait till [Bloodline] is complete. Then, I will try to stock up on Mission Completion Cards. Seven years is plenty... As long as I complete the level 200 Promotion, I will be able to spend all the Experience I've accumulated through Version 2.0 and turn it all into actual strength and combat capability...

"Yesterday, under the monitoring of the Purple Crystal Civilization, Godora's Discrimination Transformation Movement was successfully completed. Serbia the Fifth has made a speech. He thinks that be it pureblood or hybrid, everyone should support Godora as a whole and should not be divided due to their blood. From now on, they shall put aside their differences, fight and work for the Godoran Civilization as one.

"Serbia The Fifth once met many obstacles during the process, and he became hated by many. Fortunately, after this process was completed, his achievement was finally recognized, and his support rate jumped up to 91.67%. The Purple Crystal Civilization thinks that in the long history of Godora, Serbia the Fifth is undoubtedly one of the wisest and bold leaders... Okay, that will be all for the Garton Star System News today. See you on the..."

Beep.

Serbia the Fifth turned off the virtual screen and looked at Han Xiao and Rossellin on the opposite of the guest table with a delighted expression.

"The plan is finally over. From the bottom of my heart, I thank the two of you for your help."

Rossellin gave a reserved smile before picking up the cup on the table and taking a sip of the specialty Godoran drink, displaying a nonchalant posture. Han Xiao watched from beside and almost wanted to give her a thumbs up—what a professional in being pretentious.

It seemed that every wrinkle on Serbia the Fifth's face was laughing. He was overjoyed. Having solved the illness that had plagued Godora for countless years, he could predict that he would definitely be written in the history and textbooks as Godora's hero—this could be said to be the biggest achievement.

After all, as the saying went, 'a great man who isn't written in textbooks isn't really a great man!'

This opportunity was gifted to him by Black Star, who was sitting in front of him, so Serbia the Fifth was full of gratitude.

"In terms of reward," Serbia the Fifth said, "we shall follow the promise we made in the first place. First, a large amount of money and resources; second, opening more resource purchasing channels; third, more resource planet harvesting rights, and we will be providing the devices and manpower; fourth, the borrowing right to the military factory to mass produce spaceships for the Black Star Army; fifth, the right to deploy our technical personals to cultivate professional talents for you; last but not least, political support."

Han Xiao listened carefully with a straight face. Those were all pre-discussed terms.

As for supplies and money, he did not care that much since he had so many resource planets now. The rights to borrow Godora's military factory and deploy their technical personnel were not bad.

The production rate of a Star System civilization was not to be underestimated; borrowing their hundreds of huge military factories across the Star System would increase the efficiency of building spaceships tremendously. Deploying technical personnel to cultivate specialized research and development talents for the Black Star Army was also beneficial in the long run.

However, compared to these rewards, the most important thing to Han Xiao was still the [Bloodline] mission that had never been completed in the previous life. This was also the first Grade S mission that he had completed!

The [Bloodline] mission on the interface was already shown as 'Completed', but Han Xiao stayed patient and did not immediately look at it. Instead, he chatted with Serbia the Fifth for a while before taking his leave with Rossellin.

After the two of them left, Serbia the Fifth stood up and looked at the bright sky outside from the window, thinking of the bright future ahead.

At the same time, Rudy felt the same as Serbia The Fifth, full of anticipation of the future.

The changes in his life were very noticeable and obvious. After the Discrimination Transformation Movement, he realized that when he walked on the streets, the looks of discrimination and alienation all disappeared. His colleagues became friendly; his wife's family became passionate and not cold anymore; his boss gave him important matters to take care of and seemed to have plans to give him bigger responsibilities.

His children were no longer quiet and alone in school and made many new friends.

Everything was becoming better.

His passion for life was reignited.

"Thank you, Serbia the Fifth. Thank you, Purple Crystal. Thank you, Black Star for capturing the DarkStar leader..."

Rudy was filled with gratitude.

Han Xiao took Rossellin to the spaceship and headed back.

After entering hyperdrive mode, just as Han Xiao was about to look at the reward, Rossellin stopped him and asked with a curious expression, "Black Star, do you really think that my brainwashing can completely change Godora's bloodline discrimination and that it will not bounce back in the future?"

"How would I know? It won't have anything to do with me even if it does."

"Yet you still trust me so much?" Rossellin tutted. "Even I don't know if this plan will work, but I feel like you're more confident than me despite not knowing the details of my Esper ability."

"I can see the future. If I say you can do it, you can do it." Han Xiao was in a hurry to complete the mission and receive the reward, so he was in no mood to chat with Rossellin. He gave her this ever-applicable excuse and hastily walked into the training room, leaving Rossellin standing there pondering.

After closing the training room door, Han Xiao quickly opened the interface and looked at the notification of the mission.

[Bloodline] Completed!

Mission Rating: B (Good)

You have received 1,250,000,000 Experience, 3 Random Rewards, +30,000 Godora Contribution Points, 10 Eternal Dungeon Crystals for [Godora's History].

You have received 1 Political Asset.

Wow, 1.25 billion Experience! That's more than seven times what I got from the DarkStar leader's last mission and almost at the reward standard of Version 5.0.

Han Xiao was surprised. This amount of Experience was not little even to him, and it even gave him three Random Rewards, which was equivalent to completing three Grade A missions with a high Mission Rating and exactly what he needed at the moment to get a Mission Completion Card.

Grade S missions all had very few clues, and their rewards were unknown before completion. Even Han Xiao had just found out about the reward of this mission. Maybe because he completed the mission using a controversial method, the Mission Rating was only Good. After all, brainwashing was not the most stable way to solve the problem. However, Han Xiao had no idea how to complete this mission the usual way, so being able to complete it was already a great surprise.

30,000 Godora Contribution Points would allow players to exchange many good equipment, but to him, it was not all that useful. Nonetheless, it was better than nothing.

Ten Eternal Dungeon Crystals were great. 'Eternal' meant that they could be used repeatedly for a limited number of times every day. The dungeon [Godora's History]'s level requirement was level sixty to one hundred and eighty, which was a very broad range. This meant that this was an enormous dungeon, and its rewards would definitely be very rich.

Han Xiao would have no use for it, but those player guilds would definitely spend huge sums to buy these Eternal Dungeon Crystals. This would basically give a guild a huge dungeon that they could enter every single day, providing their pro players continuous tests, allowing them to level up quicker and gain more resources.

Although the Dungeon Creation Right on the NPC interface could continuously create dungeons, it was not able to make any Eternal Dungeon Crystals. Furthermore, guilds would definitely want to obtain a stable way of entering dungeons for themselves. Rich people loved to buy assurance with money.

Han Xiao was more interested in the players' Experience, not money, so selling them or not did not really matter. However, using these Eternal Dungeon Crystals as high level items in the faction store would be useful in attracting players.

Han Xiao looked at the last reward—one Political Asset.

[Political Asset (1): Godoran Civilization]

You are loved by the Godorans. When trading with Godorans, you can buy at lower prices and sell at higher prices.

Godora is willing to listen to your requests. You can make suggestions to the Godoran government directly. According to the rationality of the request, there's a slight chance the Godoran Civilization will fulfill your request.

This is a symbol of political influence. Your achievements are praised in the galaxy. When interacting with certain organizations or characters, +30% Favorability gain rate.

You have valuable experience. +30% Experience gained from all sources.

Remarks: Relationship with Godora has to be at [Reverence] for the above effects to be active.

It really is this thing. I thought I was mistaken. Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Political Assets and Legendary Points had the same characteristics, but Political Assets were rarer than Legendary Points. In his previous life, he had only seen it in other people's screenshots.

He looked at the NPC interface. All of his Reward Quotas increased by sixty percent!

The effect of a Political Asset was much better than a Legendary Point!

In his previous life, Han Xiao had completed Grade S missions too, but they were either large scale missions that many were involved in or challenge missions that consisted of fighting and killing. This was his first time completing such a complicated Grade S mission like [Bloodline].

Political Assets had a lot of benefits. To Han Xiao, he felt that the most important effects were the thirty percent increase in Favorability gain rate and Experience gain. As long as he met the requirements, he would enjoy those bonuses forever.

These two effects were applicable to the players as well. Obtaining Political Assets was extremely important. It required a lot of work and time, so these two effects were somewhat making up for that. Furthermore, the long-term rewards were higher than the expenses.

If a player had one Political Asset, it meant that for the same time they spent on missions, they would gain more Experience than everyone else. Their level would always be ahead, and they would have more excess Experience to learn and level up abilities. As this continued, the difference between them and the other players would keep growing larger.

In his previous life, Han Xiao had witnessed many guilds trying everything they could to obtain Political Assets for their players.

Experience isn't Enas and has no physical form, so it can't be traded between players. This says that the bonus applies to Experience gained from all sources. Does this mean that the Experience I reap from the players will also increase by thirty percent?

Han Xiao was looking forward to finding out. Experience only existed in the interface. Since there were cash items such as Double Experience Cards and so on, him getting thirty percent bonus Experience was not impossible.

If that was indeed the case, the efficiency in him reaping leeks would see an explosive increase!

Chapter 714: Dried Experience

Closing the mission reward notification, Han Xiao looked at his stocked up Random Rewards. Including the [Bloodline] reward, he had six of them.

"Six should be plenty. I'll give it a try." Han Xiao pondered for a moment and decided to use the Random Rewards.

Luck affected the chances of getting all kinds of good rewards, but a Mission Completion Card was a rather low-value reward, so Han Xiao did not want to use the Random Reward after touching Feidin. He would have a higher chance of getting a Mission Completion Card with his own Luck.

Randomizing... complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

Please select one from the three options below:

Double Experience Card (2)

Blank Character Summon Card (1)

Large Experience Crystal (3)

Being used to not getting what he wanted on the first draw, with a calm expression, Han Xiao looked at them and chose the Blank Character Summon Card to be used the next time he saw Ames.

Randomizing... complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

Please select one from the three options below:

Energy Enhancement Aura (Cosmetic)

Random Dungeon Crystal (1)

Gene Awakening Elixir (Normal)

Han Xiao tutted. Two consecutive item type rewards but no Mission Completion Card; this was not looking too good.

These rewards are not good at all... Han Xiao touched his chin in resignation. As expected, touching Feidin or not really made a huge difference.

Luck Glow is so strong. I want it so badly.

Seeing that nothing was good, Han Xiao chose the 'Energy Enhancement Aura', a cheap aura type cosmetic. Its effect was to increase the appearance of energy attacks, making the beams look thicker and larger. It had no actual effects other than making the attacks look more intimidating and cooler.

Randomizing... complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Talent]

Please select one from the three options below:

[Golden Ratio Body]: +3% STR, +3% DEX, +3% END, +75 CHA

[Electrical Eyes]: +25 CHA, +5 LUK

3: [Sado-Masochism]: +120 MYS, -50 CHA

"What the hell are these?" Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

One of the good things about being unlucky was that he would always see weird stuff.

The second and the third choices were useless, so Han Xiao chose the [Golden Ratio Body], which was better than nothing. Han Xiao took a deep breath and started to draw the fourth Random Reward.

Randomizing... complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

Please select one from the three options below:

Mission Completion Card (1)

Small Experience Crystal (13)

Race Evolution Options Reshuffle Card Fragment (2)

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. After drawing four Random Rewards, he finally got a Mission Completion Card!

After selecting the Mission Completion Card, Han Xiao stayed patient and used the remaining two Random Rewards, which gave him 2,000,000 Experience and a common ability, [Breaking Skull], which gave +40% critical chance when attacking the enemy's head with an eight-second cooldown.

One Mission Completion Card out of six draws, not too bad. At least it solved the imminent issue.

Han Xiao breathed a sigh of relief. One was enough to complete the Promotion mission. After he completed the Promotion, his Experience would be spent up, so he would be in no hurry. He would have seven years to slowly collect more Mission Completion Cards.

Han Xiao immediately used this new Mission Completion Card.

You have used [Mission Completion Card]!

[Self Challenge] completed!

Level 200 Promotion Mission completed! Promotion successful! END Bonus increased! 1 END = 145 Health = 155 Stamina.

Han Xiao's heart trembled as if burning lava poured out from within and flowed through his entire body. He inhaled deeply and felt as if his body was melting; his cells were evolving.

The pain lasted for quite a while before disappearing. Han Xiao was gasping for air and covered in sweat, but he was very energetic as if he had just finished a physical training.

The level limit was removed. Han Xiao took a deep breath and spent all the Experience on leveling up. His level increased from level 200 to level 207.

[Apostle Mechanic] leveled up to level 12.

+240 Energy, +3 STR, +4 DEX, +5 END, +10 INT.

You have received 8 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

He finally spent all his Experience!

Experience in his interface was just a number; it would only become valuable when he turned it into his own combat capability. The Experience that he had obtained through Version 2.0 was almost all gone. Han Xiao felt the energy in his body—he was now at his peak.

I've finally spent all the Experience... Han Xiao looked at the notification and realized that his Grade Bonus had changed as well.

When achieving the Grade A standard of 10,000 Energy Rank, one would receive the Grade A bonuses. For every 10,000 Ona after that, the bonus would increase.

The original effect was: +10 END, +8 All Resistances. +10% Highest Attribute, +5% Other Attributes, +30 Free Attribute Points, and +5 Potential Points.

After the Grade Bonus upgraded, it became: +15 END, +12 All Resistances. +15% Highest Attribute, +8% Other Attributes, +80 Free Attribute Points, and +10 Potential Points.

Han Xiao spent more than half of the Free Attribute Points in Intelligence and then put forty into Endurance. Endurance was now very beneficial to him. He had spent all the Free Attribute Points in the early stages on Intelligence, so he could slow down for a while.

Furthermore, after his battle with EsGod, he was quite cautious about the attack of a Beyond Grade A, so more Endurance would definitely only do him good.

He then looked at his current attributes.

Level: 207

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Void Distorter (Human Form)

Attributes: 504 STR, 946 DEX, 1040 END, 2859 INT, 432 MYS, 214 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Points: 24

Health: 251,780

Stamina: 209,320

Energy: 28,410 [Lv.12]

[Lv.12 Energy bonus attributes: +169 STR, +239 DEX, +269 END, +336 INT, +206 MYS, +32,520 Maximum Stamina, +352% Machinery Affinity (Super Electromagnetic Sense)]

Energy Rank: 24,668

Grade: A+

Grade A Bonuses: +15 END, +12 All Resistances. +15% Highest Attribute, +8% Other Attributes, +80 Free Attribute Points, +10 Potential Points

Remark: As a Mechanic, you're among the top. As a tank, you're world-class. Are you really not considering becoming a tank?

Tsk, Machinery is the best, Han Xiao snorted internally.

In order to complete his Class Advancement, he had spent three whole years, but between his Class Advancement and Promotion, he did not take very long. This was all thanks to his accumulation earlier on.

This Promotion was not Race Evolution, so he did not undergo a tremendous change. Nonetheless, his health points grew very quickly. Compared to before the Promotion, they was had increased by twenty-five percent

Han Xiao could not imagine how tanky the Tyrant would be. Other than having extremely high defense, he would probably have millions of health points.

Level 207, one more step closer to Beyond Grade A. I've spent all the accumulated Experience. With the Experience standard of Version 2.0, I may be able to level up four to five more times. I can only wait until the players return in order to quickly level up. Now I just have to stock up on more Mission Completion Cards.

As the [Bloodline] mission ended, Han Xiao went back to the headquarters and rested for a few days. Since his holiday had yet to end, he flipped through the mission list of the Mercenary Department of the army and looked for suitable missions for him to accept.

The news that Black Star was out to do missions personally once again quickly spread across the Colton Star Cluster and brought shock to many organizations. With Han Xiao's current position, why would he ever need to personally carry out missions‽

Plus, aren't you at war? How do you have time to personally do missions‽

Is the secret war this easy for you‽

The employers across the entire Colton Star Cluster were overjoyed. With Black Star's strength, what kind of mission would he be unable to complete? For an amount of time, the Mercenary Department of the Black Star Army's business multiplied by three times—all because of Han Xiao.

Those who successfully hired Han Xiao were flattered. Despite being the employer, their attitude toward Han Xiao was like Han Xiao was their employer.

Han Xiao's method of carrying out these hiring missions could be simply described with one word—reckless!

Be it eliminating rebels, clearing beasts, or chasing galactic pirates, all he did was crush them instantly. The enemies could not even resist. Han Xiao spent more time traveling than doing the missions. It was terrifying.

Since Han Xiao was moving alone, he thought that Klent would once again send people to try assassinating him. However, after completing seven missions, he still had not even seen a trace of any assassins.

What had happened to DarkStar horrified Klent, so they were extremely cautious. Seeing that Han Xiao was alone outside, they immediately had specialized groups of people making deductions.

With Black Star's position, there's absolutely no need for him to do those hires personally.

Therefore, it's obvious that...

He's luring us to attack him!

He definitely wants to replicate what happened to the DarkStar leader and make us the scapegoat once again! This guy is evil!

Therefore, the Klentans looked at Han Xiao wandering alone with a sneer on their faces.

Humph, your intentions are too obvious; we see right through them! We will definitely not fall for it!

Furthermore, Klent had just been hit politically, so they wanted to keep a low profile for some time. Klent also could not think of anything that could threaten Han Xiao at all, so they had no intention of attacking Han Xiao for the time being.

When Han Xiao was doing missions and stocking up on Random Rewards, the various departments of the Black Star Army were developing steadily as well.

The first batch of investments for Vilna were spent in the first three months. Following Han Xiao's orders, Reynold invested another 150 million Enas.

On the Floating Dragon Island dock, one thousand battleships were parked neatly in their various models. Among them were two enormous flagships as the core of the fleet.

The spaceships of the galactic pirates were pushed to the corners of the dock. They shivered and did not dare to have any objections. This was because the exterior armor of these thousand battleships was painted with the same image—a light green Void Dragon head with a throne below it inside a ring.

This was the mark of the second Field Team of Floating Dragon!

Vilna took a few assistants to accompany Aesop and Jenny in inspecting this fleet.

"We now have a thousand Star System produced battleships and three hundred thousand galactic warriors, including 450 Grade B Supers and 240,000 Grade C Supers. The remaining are Grade D and below, mainly responsible for the management, logistics, transport, and others."

Vilna introduced the current scale of the second Floating Dragon Field Team to the two of them.

"It has only been half a year. This is great," Aesop complimented.

"It's mainly because of Black Star's help," Vilna said. "It's difficult to even make money on my own."

"How much did he spend?" Jenny asked with a frown.

"70,000,000 Enas initially and another 150,000,000 Enas a few days ago..." Vilna swallowed her saliva. Even as a Calamity Grade Super, she was still shocked by Han Xiao's generosity.

"How generous..." Jenny's brows stopped frowning, and she slightly snorted. She touched her slowly deteriorating hairline with resignation.

"The maintenance cost of these troops is about 8.5 million Enas every month," Vilna cautiously added. "Black Star is the one maintaining that right now, but in the future..."

"It's a little expensive," Jenny subconsciously replied before suddenly pausing.

She suddenly realized that she had almost never given Han Xiao any funding or maintenance fees at all. Although the Black Star Army was Floating Dragon's Field Team, they had been responsible for their own expenses and still handed over a part of their profits to her every month.

As the Black Star Army almost never requested any funding from Floating Dragon, she had not really thought about it. Only now did she realize that the Black Star Army was really independent, and they were probably passionately expanding their business to earn the maintenance fees too. Jenny shook her head and felt that she really was not a very great butler.

"Black Star built a fleet for you without caring about the cost," Aesop said. "It seems that he's made up his mind on leaving. Vilna, you must think of ways to make profits for this fleet. We will provide the maintenance fee of this team of yours in the future. We don't need the Field Team to be too large, or the cost will be too high. You can't keep accepting Black Star's help. You don't have his ability to make money, so you must learn to control your fleet's size."

"O—Okay..." Vilna hastily nodded.

Jenny, who stayed silent on the side for a while, could not help but admit, "Black Star really is a rare talent."

Aesop nodded in agreement before adding with resignation, "Sadly, he's growing too fast. Someone this talented will not serve others forever..."

Chapter 715: Seven Years

As Aesop, Vilna, and Jenny were chatting, a most familiar spaceship to all three of them came from afar. It was Han Xiao’s Blacklight Stealth.

"Why is he here?"

The three of them were surprised. They were just talking about Han Xiao, and speak of the devil…

The Blacklight Stealth squeezed into the Floating Dragon Island’s dock. The hatch opened, and Han Xiao stepped out. He looked around at the shivering galactic pirates around, curled his lips, and then looked at Aesop, Jenny, and Vilna.

"Yo, you’re all here."

"Why have you come back?" Jenny snorted.

"It’s been a long time since I last saw you, and I’ve missed you, especially that pretty hairline of yours. I missed it so much I could barely sleep at night… By the way, have you had time to sleep recently?"

Han Xiao raised his brows. After knowing Jenny for so long, he knew very clearly of how to piss her off.

"You’re such an asshole!" Being hit where it hurt, Jenny clenched her teeth, turned around, and stomped away as if the ground was Han Xiao’s face and she wanted to stomp a hole in it.

Han Xiao then looked at Vilna and said, "What were you guys doing?"

"W—We were inspecting the second Field Team…" Vilna stuttered with a slightly blushed face. Han Xiao was the one that had spent the money to build this team, and Aesop had just told her that this was a symbol of Han Xiao showing his decision of leaving. With Han Xiao suddenly appearing, she felt very uncomfortable as if she had been caught in the act.

Being extremely experienced, Aesop was not awkward at all, he changed the topic and said, "Are you looking for Ames? She doesn’t know you’re back, so she should be in the palace training. Go find her."

Han Xiao nodded. He casually patted Vilna’s head till her face was completely blushed, and then he finally walked away satisfied.

Although Vilna was a Calamity Grade, her personality was too soft, and Han Xiao could not help but tease her every time he saw her. After all, she would be his successor in the future, so he was casual when treating her.

He had just completed a mission that happened to be near the Floating Dragon Island, so he decided to make a trip there. While he was there, he was also going to use the Blank Character Summon Card on Ames.

Near the palace, Han Xiao saw Hila and Aurora, and his eyes sparkled.

Hila was wearing a tight red battle suit made of high strength nanofiber. Compared to three years ago, her body was even sexier. Her appearance and vibe had become more aligned with the Goddess of Death that she had been in his previous life, cold and indifferent.

Aurora had grown quite a bit taller, too. She was still smaller than Hila overall but not smaller at all at some places. It was clear that she had developed her vital energy Esper ability very well.

The foreheads of both of them were covered in sweat marks as they walked out of the palace. It seemed like they had just finished training Upon seeing Han Xiao, the two of them stopped simultaneously.

"Whoa, are you here to see us?" With surprise all over her face, Aurora pounced into Han Xiao’s arms and hugged him.

Hila’s eyes twitched as she slowly walked over.

"Alright, alright, they’re big enough." Han Xiao quickly pushed Aurora away by her head then sized the two of them up. "It looks like you guys have trained well under Ames."

Both sisters had Grade S Esper ability potential, so they had grown at an astonishing speed. The energy they gave off had reached Grade B, with Hila giving off stronger energy. Han Xiao speculated that Hila’s Energy Rank should be about around 6,000.

In the original storyline, she reached Calamity Grade in Version 3.0. Although she’s not increasing her strength by slaughtering countless lives, with her potential and how hard she’s working, the possibility of her reaching the Calamity Grade within the next seven years should be quite high.

Han Xiao patted Aurora’s head, paused, and said to Hila, "When you’re at Calamity Grade, come back to help me."

Given how strong Hila had been in her previous life, she would definitely be a great help when she reached Grade A. As a very powerful healer, Aurora would also be able to effectively reduce the casualties of his officers. Both of them would be fantastic additions to his army.

"Okay." Hila nodded and replied very decisively.

"I thought you would hesitate. After all, it’s safe here with Ames. Haven’t you always prioritized safety?".

With an expressionless face, Hila said, "This is something we agreed on. Plus, when I’m at Calamity Grade, I will be able to protect Aurora. Since we’re here in the universe, we can’t possibly stay in one place all the time instead of exploring the world. Furthermore, she is now capable of protecting herself to some extent."

Han Xiao looked at Hila and said, "Why do I feel like you didn’t really mean that?"

"Humph." Hila looked away.

She did not train so hard just to protect Aurora in the galaxy but also to be able to help Han Xiao as soon as possible to repay him. With her strong personality, she had to repay others for their help.

Furthermore, she would be able to see Han Xiao often if she worked for him. She could only see Han Xiao once in a very long time while training on Floating Dragon Island, so she rather missed him.

"Are you here to see Her Excellency Dragon Emperor?" Hila asked.

"Yeah."

"…She should be in the garden, go see her then." Hila looked down.

Han Xiao was just about to walk into the palace when Hila suddenly stopped him and asked, "How strong have you really become?"

She was not at Han Xiao’s level yet, and the news was mostly exaggerated, so she had been very curious about how strong Han Xiao really was.

"Hmmm, I should be able to beat a hundred thousand of you without using both of my hands." Han Xiao smiled.

Hila clenched her teeth in her mind.

She had known Han Xiao for the longest, but now she could not even see Han Xiao’s footsteps.

In the garden, Ames was floating in the air, looking up at a dim star at the edge of the sky.

Hearing the footsteps, she glanced down and slowly landed before Han Xiao. Her smooth, silky hair and her thin black dress waved with the wind.

"You’re back, Black Star." Ames smiled and complimented, "I’ve heard about you funding the second Field Team. You’ve done well."

"Everything is easy with enough money." Han Xiao chuckled as he secretly used the Blank Character Summon Card on Ames.

"Why did you come back to see me?" Ames blinked.

"Do I need a reason to come to see you?" Of course, Han Xiao was not going to say that it was because of the Blank Character Summon Card.

"You’ve become less and less cautious in front of me."

"That’s because we’re very close now, aren’t we?" Han Xiao joked.

"Is that the only reason?" Ames stared at Han Xiao’s eyes with a faint smile.

Black Star had become stronger and stronger, and his position was also growing continuously. The differences between the two of them in every regard were shrinking at a very high speed. Black Star became more casual when facing her, not as a subordinate of her anymore but more like an equal.

Ames suddenly said, "How long has it been since the last time I went to tour your territory?"

Han Xiao thought about it and said, "Quite a few years, why?"

The last time that Ames toured the Black Star Army was when Version 2.0 just started. It was then that she had taken Hila and Aurora as her students.

"It’s only been a few years, and your organization has already grown to what it is today. Black Star, how about you take me to tour your territory once again?" Ames slanted her head and gave Han Xiao a smile that he did not understand.

Han Xiao was a little surprised, but he was used to how random Ames was. He thought about it, and it seemed that there was no reason for him to reject her. He felt that it was most likely because Ames was extremely bored, so he nodded and said, "Sure. Since the boss wants to do a tour, I will accompany you. I’m on holiday anyway. Let’s go to the Black Star Army headquarters, what do you say?"

"Hmm, you decide." Ames smiled.

The two of them left immediately.

Aesop was still inspecting the troops when he saw with resignation that in the short time Han Xiao left, he had already kidnapped Ames and taken her away.

The Blacklight Stealth returned to the headquarters. The two of them alighted the spaceship, and Han Xiao took Ames to tour the various areas of the headquarters. In the process, the many Black Star Army members that passed by them all gave them strange looks.

The rumors of the two of them going separate ways never stopped. Now that they saw their captain appearing together with Ames, many felt strange. Currently, Ames was still the boss of the Black Star Army, so it looked like she was there to do an inspection.

As the two of them walked, Han Xiao explained and introduced the various areas while Ames kept quiet. Very soon, they finished touring all the areas in the headquarters and arrived at Han Xiao’s office. All the officers in the headquarters had been summoned there by Han Xiao, waiting to meet Ames in the office and be inspected.

As soon as Ames walked in the door, the Black Star Army officers all stood up and nodded, giving the Beyond Grade A their respect.

Ames looked around and saw Herlous and the others. She smiled and said, "I remember some of you. You’ve all been working with Black Star for a very long time."

"You’re Herlous, right?" Ames came before Herlous, smiled, and nodded. "I can see your potential. You should be able to reach Calamity Grade."

Herlous’ face became joyous. He had always been troubled by this, and now he felt much more relieved-he trusted the judgment of a Beyond Grade A.

Ames then came before Aroshia. Seeing that she was still cold as always, she smiled and did not say anything. She then walked up to Sylvia and patted Sylvia’s head.

"What a smart kid. I feel you have the potential to become a Calamity Grade too."

Sylvia’s eyes opened wide, and she felt a little bit weird.

She felt that Ames seemed to like guessing others’ potential, and she wondered if it was Ames’ strange habit.

Ames stopped for a while in front of every officer and spoke a few words. Every officer reacted differently. Feidin smiled gently; Harmon was lost; Reynold was solemn; Rossellin was indifferent; Karmbe, Marian, and Misecech were overjoyed.

Lastly, Ames came to Lagi and gave him a few more glances. "Didn’t expect you to be the former Forbidden Sorcerer Commander under Austin."

"Sigh, what good does that do? I’m still fired." Lagi sighed. He was used to seeing Beyond Grade As, so he was the most casual among all the officers.

Ames smiled and walked back to Han Xiao. The officers did not speak, all intimidated by Ames.

"Okay Black Star, I’ll be going back now."

"So soon?" Han Xiao was stunned. Was she not going to stay and play for a few days after going all the way there?

"I’ve seen what I wanted to see." Ames shook her head.

The rise of the Black Star Army was too quick, and observing the Black Star Army was equivalent to observing Han Xiao’s ambition. She had found the answer to what she wanted to know.

Maybe… I’m really not suitable to be his leader.

Having understood what Ames meant, Han Xiao sighed in his mind and told the officers to scatter as he took Ames back to the dock. The two of them stayed silent on the way.

"Give me a spaceship, I’ll go back myself. You don’t have to make another trip," Ames said.

"Okay." Han Xiao called the person in charge of the dock over and told him to bring a spaceship over.

As the two of them waited for the spaceship on the dock, Ames suddenly spoked without even turning her head.

"A few years ago, you told me you were going to join the secret war, but you did not seek my help-why?"

Han Xiao coughed and said, "Your position is too sensitive to take part in the secret war. I notified you, and you didn’t stop me, so I took it as you allowed it. Back then, you didn’t show any signs of wanting to take part in it, so I didn’t seek help from you."

"Why didn’t you try?"

What is that supposed to mean? Han Xiao frowned, but he could only see the back of Ames’ head.

He changed the topic and said, "A few years ago when I was ambushed by Thous… ahem, Klent, I asked for your help, but you didn’t agree to help me."

Han Xiao was talking about when he asked for Ames’ help during the third round of [Prey] and was rejected.

"If you insisted back then, I would’ve still agreed. If you insisted on asking me to join the secret war, I might not have rejected… though I don’t like to be involved in these things," Ames said with a calm tone.

Han Xiao could not see her face, so he could only speculate what she meant from her tone. "You mean that you want to take part in the secret war?"

"I’m no longer needed." Ames paused and changed the topic. "Ever since the first day I met you, I’ve never seen you stop your footsteps, why?"

Are we doing quizzes now? When did you start to speak in such a mysterious way? Han Xiao’s lips twitched. He thought for a moment and said with resignation, "It’s not time to stop. You have the choice to stop, but I don’t."

"What are you afraid of?".

Han Xiao’s eyes were slightly moved, and he did not answer.

At this time, a spaceship finally stopped in front of Ames. The hatch opened, and the gangway was lowered.

Ames stretched her body. Her clothes tightened and highlighted her cursive, beautiful waist. She sighed and softly said, "I hope you’re willing to stop one day and look at the scenery along the way. This universe has an end no matter how enormous it is, but ambition has no limits."

Then, she boarded the ship and closed the hatch, blocking herself from Han Xiao’s view, never letting him see her expression.

Han Xiao watched as the spaceship turned into a stream of light and disappeared. Then he sighed and massaged his temples.

He had a feeling that Ames had changed, and her mood had become more unpredictable.

When did she start to change? Han Xiao pondered.

The conflict between the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light affected the entire Galaxy. All the Star Fields were affected by the Crimson Tide. It was a time of chaos. Big and small wars were also happening in the various Star Clusters in the Shattered Star Ring.

The Crimson Tide swept the entire Galaxy. Comparatively, the chaos in the Shattered Star Ring was just the tip of the iceberg.

The situation of the secret war was many times more complicated compared to his previous life. More people were involved, and more ‘accidents’ happened that had never happened originally. Nonetheless, overall, the situation was still a stalemate between the Bloodshed Land and Section Zero.

War meant opportunities; no one fought wars for the sake of fighting wars. The Black Star Army was slowly expanding and benefiting.

Han Xiao was very active in the secret war and became the brightest star onstage.

Like a violent river that never stopped or flowed backward, the secret war became more and more intense in the midst of this chaos that affected the entire universe.

In the flames of war, seven years passed in this universe.

Chapter 716: New Version—Crimson Tide!

Galaxy Calendar: Year 704, 17th day of the 7th month.

In the Black Star Army headquarters…

Clank…

On the alloy walkway, a tall, curvaceous figure strode with her alloy boots making a clanking sound when coming into contact with the alloy ground. Her white-gold female armor only covered her important locations, and she wore a black nano form fitting suit on the inside.

A few warriors from the lower rungs of the Black Star Army turned into the walkway and were wearing a similar uniform to that lady. The moment they saw her approaching from afar, their expressions turned solemn, and they stood up straight to give a salute.

"Your Excellency Chief Administrative Official."

Her footsteps paused for a while, and she revealed a smile in response. Her smile was like the blooming roses and radiant sunlight. The few warriors were stunned into silence and only came back to their senses after she walked far away.

"How beautiful. She is the number one beauty of the Black Star Army indeed…"

"If only I can catch her eye."

"You must be dreaming. Her Excellency Sylvia is a Calamity Grade Super and the chief disciple of His Excellency Black Star. How could you possibly catch her eye?"

The lady who walked afar revealed a helpless expression as she heard the conversation between the two.

She was Sylvia.

In the past seven years, she had put in all her effort into training herself (struggling for survival). After a series of tempering (suffering), her latent potential was finally realized, and she had stepped into the Calamity Grade before Version 3.0!

With her strength growing, her fame grew as well. She became the Chief Administrative Official of the Black Star Army, and people finally began to acknowledge her title as Black Star’s chief disciple.

A Calamity Grade Super had a long lifespan, and Sylvia had transformed into a beauty over the past seven years. She had a tall, curvaceous figure with her long hair drifting in the wind. She was a beauty who deserved 9.5 points at the very least. Being a beauty who was both powerful and had a high status, Sylvia became the target for many males within the Black Star Army. Among all the officers, her popularity had only lost to Feidin.

Sylvia walked all the way to the rooftop of the base. This was the highest point in the Black Star headquarters, and it was surrounded by bright, twinkling stars all around. Looking up, one could see Planet Golden Gate like it was hanging down from the sky.

At this moment, there were many officers standing on the rooftop, and they all turned around to look at Sylvia. After glancing at those present, Sylvia could tell that pretty much all the important officers in the Black Star Army were present today. Vice Commander Lagi, Logistics Manager Reynold, Fleet Commander Herlous, Culture Instructor Rossellin, and so on. There were more than twenty people present with fifteen Calamity Grade Supers among them!

"Everyone is here. Have you completed what I asked you to do?"

A deep voice sounded, and when Sylvia looked toward the source of this voice, a tall figure was standing at the edge of the rooftop. He was dressed in black with his back facing the crowd. It was Han Xiao.

"Everything has been prepared according to your instructions." Sylvia nodded.

"Very good."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao turned around with a calm expression and a tinge of excitement in his eyes.

Compared to seven years ago, his appearance had not changed much, and he still looked as young as before. However, he had indeed been through plenty in the past seven years, and the wrinkles were not shown on his face but his heart. His aura had become more stable and unfathomable.

All the officers present had personally experienced Han Xiao’s change. If Han Xiao was like a ferocious lion with a tyrannical aura seven years ago, Han Xiao gave them the impression of a majestic lion at the moment. Apart from Lagi, all other officers present would be pressured by just looking him in the eye.

Today was the day for Version 3.0 to be launched. Han Xiao had waited for this day for a very long time.

It has been a full ten years… Han Xiao lamented in his heart. To the players, these ten years were nothing more than background story, but Han Xiao had personally experienced the full ten years. In order to prepare for the launch date of Version 3.0, Han Xiao had made many preparations beforehand. All his officers had arrived personally to report the progress of their preparations to him. They had only done as they were instructed but did not know the reason for it.

Compared to his previous life, Version 3.0 had quite a bit of changes.

In the past seven years, the secret war had become more and more intense. However, due to his interference, Klent was not as powerful as in his previous life, and both Section Zero and Bloodshed Land had some wins and losses. Section Zero was not on the passive side like before, and both parties were locked in an intense battle. The battlefield was no longer limited to Westwind, Kaya, and Chaida; two more Star Systems had been dragged into the war.

The secret war was one of the Main Storyline Missions in Version 3.0 within the Shattered Star Ring. Because of Han Xiao’s presence, the secret war was far more complicated than in his previous life, with many more organizations participating in it in secret. When the players returned, their first Main Storyline Mission would be the secret war that had been modified by Han Xiao!

In the past seven years, the various operations of the Black Star Army had mainly been focused on the war, mining, and employment missions. The Black Star Army had developed steadily and successfully gained firm footing in many different Star Systems. The Black Star Army was spread across the Colton Star Cluster with more than five hundred satellite bases, three hundred thousand battleships, a hundred million members, and a net worth of over a trillion!

With such a large organization, it would be a piece of cake for them to take care of a million players. Furthermore, Version 3.0 would be the time for new players to enter. With the performance that the Chinese players showed in the second Pro League, there would definitely be many new Chinese players joining the game. The Black Star Army had the capability to groom these new players.

The seven years of war had given Han Xiao a never-ending stream of experience. He was currently at level 211, and it would have been tough for the players to provide for his requirements during Version 2.0.

Thus, Version 3.0 would be a good opportunity for him to increase his strength rapidly again. Han Xiao also took the time to complete more than a hundred employment missions and had a stash of Mission Completion Cards.

Han Xiao’s preparations over the past seven years were akin to sharpening his own blade.

It could be said that he was fully prepared for the upcoming harvest!

Han Xiao took a deep breath and looked up at Planet Golden Gate. Opening the interface, he looked at the counter counting down.

Version 3.0 Activated

Fetching data… Fetching data done!

Player Forum Open.

Welcome to Galaxy Version 3.0—[Crimson Tide)!

It’s finally begun!

The players’ strength would only have a qualitative change in Version 3.0. The difference between a million Grade C Supers and a million Grade B Supers was like the difference between Heaven and Earth!

This version shall be the generation for the Black Star Army to rise!

Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled, and his lips curled up slightly. He then turned around to face the officers and waved his hands.

"Send out all our spaceships."

At the same time on Planet Golden Gate…

Because the Black Star Army headquarters had been shifted away, Base No.1, which was situated on Planet Golden Gate, had been changed to a local agency for the Black Star Army. There were not many present, and the entire place was extremely silent.

All of a sudden, the entire base was covered in white light, and the players appeared one after another. The empty base was instantly filled with people, and the silent base became bustling with activity.

"Haha! We can finally come online!"

"It’s a new version!"

"It’s already Version 3.0, and we still can’t take off our pants? Bad update!" A male player roared in rage.

"My goodness, it is already Version 3.0, and the pants stripping party still hasn’t given up?"

"We will always be around and never leave…"

"Long Sky is so cool! Hao Tian is so cool!" There were still some who were trapped in the second Pro League.

In the base, the players all chatted with each other excitedly, and the entire base was bustling like a market.

Before the update, many players had logged off in the various bases with the number of players in Base No.1 being the most. More than 100,000 players had appeared in Base No.1.

Frenzied Sword was also among the first wave of players to log on. After the Pro League ended, he took a good break. However, he was a professional player and could not afford to fall behind during the release of the new update. Thus, all the professional players all logged in at the very first moment.

Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, King Admiral, Li Ge, and the others had all logged off in Base No.1. They all gathered together and instinctively opened the interface to check any changes.

"Our attributes and skills didn’t change, but the level limit has been increased. The level limit in Version 3.0 seems to be 120," Hao Tian said.

"The faction interface is still present. Thankfully, the Black Star Army didn’t close shop." Frenzied Sword and many others heaved a sigh of relief.

As long as the Black Star Army was still around, the Faction Contribution Points that they had spent a great deal of effort to accumulate would not be wasted.

After checking their attributes on the interface, the professional players all heaved a sigh of relief. At this moment, the other players also snapped out of their initial excitement and got to work.

Having experienced the previous version refresh, the players knew what they should do. The most important thing to do after the update was to understand what had changed in the world.

Including the professional players, all the players in the base took out their communicators to see how long had gone by since the last time they logged in.

Looking at the date, everyone was immediately shocked.

"My goodness, it has been a full ten years?"

"Isn’t this a little too long? Will the NPCs from the previous version have forgotten about us?"

"Version 1.0 and 2.0 were only separated by about a year, but this was multiplied by ten times…"

"How terrifying, truly terrifying…"

"Could this be because of the Main Storyline in this version? Could it be that ten years was required to develop the Main Storyline? I remember Black Star personally revealing the existence of the Crimson Dynasty in one of Bun-Hit-Dog’s videos. Bun-Hit-Dog analyzed that Version 3.0 will very likely be related to the Crimson Dynasty. Could this be why this version is called Crimson Tide?"

It had been a full ten years since the previous version. This discovery truly shocked all the players. This was the longest time skip between versions!

Everyone discussed the changes as they looked around the base to see the changes over the past ten years.

Everyone quickly realized something strange. In the past version, this base was the headquarters of the Black Star Army and had many NPC mercenaries around all the time. However, the base was extremely silent now without a single NPC in sight. It was as though the entire base had been deserted.

"Could it be that something happened to the Black Star Army?" Someone opened up the Mercenary Alliance page and realized that the resume of the Black Star Army had disappeared.

Following which, everyone then attempted to open up the child AI program of the Black Star Army but received an ‘Insufficient authority, please sign up again’ message.

In the past ten years, Phillip had updated its child program many times, and the program in the players hands was completely useless. They had to obtain approval from the Black Star Army and submit a new application before they could use the program.

This discovery was instantly spread among the players, and everyone immediately grew nervous.

Almost all the Chinese players were in the Black Star Army, and the Black Star Army was already their own faction. The players were desperate to find out what had happened to the Black Star Army in their absence.

"Let’s go take a look first." Frenzied Sword was the most anxious, and he left the base with the other professional players behind him.

With someone in the lead, the players all swarmed out of the base and realized that there was not a single guard present.

Walking out of the base, the players realized that Base No.1 was much smaller than before as though it had been renovated. Many regions had been dismantled, and it seemed extremely desolate. Upon realizing this, Frenzied Sword and the others could not help but feel nervous.

The busy streets of Planet Golden Gate were located right outside the base, and the buildings were all covered in a warm evening sun. The street was completely filled with players, and some players had no choice but to activate their mechanical suits to fly up into the sky. They immediately got into action and searched for NPCs to find some clues.

Not too far away, there were a few Godoran pedestrians, and Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the others immediately rushed forward.

"What do you guys want?" This pedestrian looked a little frightened.

"Don’t be afraid. We only want to ask you some questions," Frenzied Sword hurriedly replied.

The pedestrian nodded with a tinge of fear and caught a glimpse of the Black Star logo on Frenzied Sword’s mechanical suit. His expression immediately changed, and he asked, "You guys are from the Black Star Army?"

Everyone’s face lit up. This person still knew about Black Star even after ten years! This meant that there was some hope!

Frenzied Sword hurriedly pointed to Base No.1 and asked, "Can I ask if that is still the headquarters of the Black Star Army?"

"You guys are from the Black Star Army. Why do you have to ask me that question?" The pedestrian had a queer look on his face but still replied honestly, "That is no longer the Black Star Army headquarters."

"Then where is the Black Star Army headquarters located?" Frenzied Sword asked.

The pedestrian pointed up toward the sky and said, "It’s up there."

In the sky?

Frenzied Sword and the others looked up doubtfully, and their faces immediately froze in place with their jaws dropping in shock.

All the players then looked up with their mouths wide open as though someone had cast a spell on them.

A gigantic metal planet floating outside the atmosphere of Planet Golden Gate appeared in their eyes!

There was no need for them to even search. They would not be able to pretend that they could not see such a gigantic planet.

Could it be that the gigantic stronghold about the size of a planet was the current headquarters of the Black Star Army?

The hundred thousand or so players were completely dumbfounded!

In Version 2.0, the Black Star Army’s headquarters had only been a single base. But after ten years, the army had a planet that was not smaller than Planet Golden Gate as their headquarters?

Just what did the Black Star Army experience over the past ten years?

Just what did they miss!

Chapter 717: Changing in a Blink

"Oh my goodness, the headquarters is actually this huge toy. How much money is it worth

"The Black Star Army could not have taken over the entire Garton Star System already, right?"

Just as the hundreds of thousands of players looked up toward the sky with dumbstruck expressions, their interfaces all vibrated as they received a notification.

Frenzied Sword recovered from his stupor, immediately opening the interface, and a look of joy appeared on his expression.

All the players who belonged to the Black Star Army had received the same faction mission.

[Ten Years): The First Link

Mission Introduction: The winds of change have blown, and the years passed quickly. Ten years have been and gone, and the situation in the universe is turbulent, with many undercurrents moving. You will participate in the tidal waves of this era. It is time for you to return to your team.

Mission Requirements: Proceed to the nearest Black Star Army satellite fortress.

Reward: 15,000 Experience, +300 Black Star Army Favorability

This is a chain mission.

Han Xiao had been watching the time for the players to come online. It was precisely he who had issued the mission for everyone to return through the faction interface. This was to allow the players to be guided to understand the new version and not allow them to run off with a head full of fog.

Because Han Xiao’s wording was formal, it was akin to a new mission for the players. In any case, any mission issued through the player interface would be a legitimate mission.

With the players having just touched on the new Version, it was the period where they were most eager to understand the changes that had happened in the galaxy. This mission was akin to a beacon in the dark, like a carrot hanging in front of a donkey, attracting their attention through creating an itch in their hearts.

"This is the guiding mission released by the new version. As long as we follow this, we will understand where the storyline has advanced. Believe me, there will not be any problems in doing so!" Bun-Hit-Dog had a firm look of confirmation.

"To actually be a storyline mission released by the Black Star Army Faction…" Frenzied Sword’s eyes lit up. "This should be a hint that the Black Star Army will play an important role in Version 3.0!"

No one would reject the guided mission for this storyline version, and the majority of the players had their own thoughts on their next course of action. They would go over to the dock to take a spaceship, which would ferry them into the sky to squeeze into that sky fortress.

Just as everyone had the thought in their heads, in the direction of the Black Star Army’s Satellite Headquarters appeared many tiny black dots the size of sesame seeds. They expanded at a rate visible to the naked eye and turned out to be a fleet with the insignia of Black Star on them. They hovered above the heads of the tens of thousands of players, the stable anti-gravity device installed in them not even raising a wind.

Those present could not help but pause in shock. At this moment, the bottom of the battleships opened, releasing traction beams toward the ground. At the same time, the cabin crew spoke through the loudspeakers, broadcasting their voices throughout the sky of the entire city.

"All members of the Black Star Army, please board the fleet. I repeat, all the members of the Black Star Army board the fleet."

All of them were spaceships that Han Xiao had specially deployed to escort the players. The players present did not imagine that the Black Star Army would actually send someone to pick them up, causing them to feel incredibly surprised.

This was Godora’s planet. To be so unbridled in the city, was the Black Star Army so powerful now?

All signs indicated that the Black Star Army was no longer the same. The players could not wait to know what had happened in the past decade.

Everyone lined up to board the spaceship, and the fleet returned right after taking in the passengers.

After boarding the ship, the players started to take action, asking the NPCs around the ship to uncover more intelligence. However, the distance from Planet Golden Gate to their headquarters was too short, not even needing half a minute to arrive there. The players who wished to gather intelligence could only dispel their thoughts.

The Black Star Army headquarters grew larger as they got closer, allowing the players to see more details of this armed satellite fortress. The ground was full of defensive measures, all kinds of weird devices, and there was even a huge thruster. Rather than calling it an armed satellite fortress, it might as well as be called a satellite battleship!

The pro players gathered together and observed through the porthole. Frenzied Sword could not help but click his tongue. "This thing looks freakishly strong. Rather than a satellite, it is more apt to call it a weapon."

"I recall that in the previous version, having tens of thousands of flagships was already extremely scary. To think that the moment this version opens, there’s something even scarier appearing. There was no such thing in the previous version, if I remember," Hao Tian mused.

"We don’t even know if this was designed by Black Star…" Maple Moon was curious.

Very quickly, the fleet reached the airport, and the tens of thousands of players streamed out, quickly occupying a large area of the dock and looking around, curiously taking in their surroundings.

201

they arrived, the players felt the lively atmosphere. There were NPCs milling about, every one of them carrying the insignia of the Black Star Army. This was far more crowded than looking at the base from the planet surface.

"Is this our new headquarters? Why are there no NPCs to welcome us?"

"What do we do next?"

Just as the players started to hesitate, their interface changed, showing the completion of the first chain mission (Ten Years). Han Xiao immediately released the second chain mission.

(Ten Years]: The Second Link

Mission Introduction: In the past decade, Galaxy has undergone huge changes. You need to review the deeds of the Black Star Army in the past decade.

Mission Requirements: Update and activate the internal procedures of Black Star Army, and watch the video lesson (History of the Black Star Army (Required)].

Reward: 25,000 Experience, +500 Black Star Army Favorability

Han Xiao had been observing the players movements from inside the base. He did not need to show himself but used the mission function to dictate the players’ movements. This would be more natural and secretive.

"This must be the backstory for the new version!"

"I told you, there’ll definitely be some notification for this version, just like in Version 2.0!"

"How convenient. I thought we’d have to look for leads ourselves."

Frenzied Sword’s eyes gleamed. He was actually thinking about what had happened between the two versions. He did not expect this guiding mission to directly publish the information they most wanted to know. How good this was!

Their mission requirement was to update their internal procedures, which was the Phillip subprogram. This was the toy installed by all members of the Black Star Army and contained the ability to check their resumes, accumulated achievements, browse the faction store, call airdrop supplies, and more.

The tens of thousands of players took out their communicators and opened their subprograms. This time, there was some response for them at last. Phillip’s virtual image turned into a 3D projection, which was suspended above the communicator.

"Coordinate detection… Coordinates confirmed. Your current position is the base of the Black Star Army. Permissions have been unfrozen. You have obtained permission to update your database. Please scan to verify, hum…"

Before the version update, Phillip’s subprogram could not support the function of stereo projection. Players could only use words to tease Phillip. However, he now had an avatar. Phillip appeared as a finger-sized boy that appeared as cute as a girl would.

Many of the female players’ eyes lit up when they saw him, and they could not help but touch Phillip with their fingers. Although there was no tactile feeling being transmitted, Phillip acted as though he had been hit and covered his little face, which was full of tears. His innocent expression seemed to convey that he was in pain because his projection had the function of virtual sensing.

Instantly, the majority of female players, including Maple Moon, were captivated by Phillip, their motherly love disastrously overflowing:

"Waa, how can something be so cute!"

"Oh no, this is the feeling of having a child!"

"He’s so cute. My heart is gonna melt…"

"So cute, how apt."

Hao Tian squeezed on Phillip’s head, causing it to explode and turn into a pile of light debris. The next moment, it reformed, and Phillip shivered in a corner of the screen. Hao Tian mused, "There’s no notification on combat information. It seems like he cannot be reared as a pet to fight."

Standing by the side, Frenzied Sword’s mouth was twitching incessantly. "Are you the Devil himself?"

The crowd teased Phillip for a while before he announced that the update was completed. The players present all then opened the subprogram. Phillip retracted back into the screen before issuing a notification.

"Permissions have been reactivated. Welcome back to the Black Star Army. Please access your academic program."

A beam of light shot out from the communicators of everyone present, forming a 3D screen as the video played. The title of the video was ‘History of the Black Star Army’, and this was exactly the academic program that they were required to watch.

Han Xiao had set up the activation program to automatically play the academic program. Not just the players, every single member of the Black Star Army had to undergo this course. This was basically a textbook used to establish the culture of Black Star Army, and the producer was Rossellin.

In his previous life, the players basically had to dig out the background of each version update by themselves, which was very inefficient. Han Xiao simply used his advantage to directly tell the players the history of the version update in this way, such that they would be able to figure out the situation earlier. This would save them a lot of trouble while improving the sense of identity the players felt, increasing their belonging to the Black Star Army.

The spirit of the players was stoked. They were trying to know what the Black Star Army had become at this point, so they quietened down, their gazes staring fixedly at their virtual screens.

"The Black Star Army was established in the Year 688 of the Galaxy Calendar and has been established for 17 years. Its original name was called the Black Star Mercenary Group, and its founder was (Black Star] Han Xiao…" Rossellin’s voice sounded, and the screen showed a silhouette of Black Star at the forefront, with the figures of his Officers behind him.

Just by looking at the opening, Bun-Hit-Dog’s eyes lit up. "This feels like a blockbuster here…"

After explaining the creation as well as the leader of the army, Rossellin’s tone changed as she immediately began to describe the process of the Black Star Army’s transformation in scale.

The picture showed a star map of the Garton Star System. On the upper left corner, there was a time indication of Year 688. This was exactly when the Black Star Mercenary Group was first established. Within the vast star map, a humble and small green dot represented the forces of the Black Star Mercenary Group at that time.

As the time on the upper left corner started to move, the tiny green dot slowly moved around, finally finding a base and beginning to expand into a small, irregularly shaped green area. This gradually expanded over time, showing the development trend of the Black Star Army.

Not only were the hundred thousand players at the headquarters watching this, but players from the other bases were also watching the video at the same time. This portion was the events that had taken place from Version 1.0 to 2.0, and to have it displayed in this manner attracted the attention of all the players.

As the green area slowly expanded in the Garton Star System, the time shown on the upper left-hand corner finally reached the mark of ten years ago, just before the version update.

The players started to pay attention. From now on, it would be the decade that they had not experienced, which was the unknown changes.

At this moment, the view on the virtual screen suddenly zoomed out tremendously, directly expanding to show the entire Colton Star Cluster. The star map was enlarged dozens or hundreds of times!

At the same time, the green area that was originally confined to the Garton Star System suddenly ballooned out to spread to more than half of the Colton Star Cluster, occupying half of it!

Everyone present was stunned silly.

Following the time skip, the sphere of influence rose sharply. If the expansion of the Black Star Army in Version 2.0 was considered that of running, then the period of ten years between the two versions was as though it was riding on a fighter jet!

The time finally arrived at Year 705. Out of the entire Colton Star Cluster, close to ninety percent was green in color.

At this moment, Rossellin’s voice sounded in the background.

"Today, the Black Star Army has completed its transformation, having branches throughout the whole Colton Star Cluster. Its business scope includes warfare, planet mining, and more. It is also the long-term ally of the Purple Crystal Civilization, the ruler of the Colton Star Cluster, with over ten other civilizations as collaborators. The Calamity Grade Supers under His Excellency have also grown to almost twenty people, with tens of thousands of battleships and hundreds of planet mining rights. The Black Star Army stands at the forefront of the organizations in the Shattered Star Ring."

Frenzied Sword and Bun-Hit-Dog stared at this commentary. They were not alone, as the players around them had the same expressions as them, full of shock and surprise!

When they originally arrived there, Frenzied Sword had already grossly inflated the power the Black Star Army had after a decade, but even he did not expect that he had still underestimated the Black Star Army! His imagination had truly limited him.

This sort of feeling was like, after falling asleep for a night, waking up and finding out that the factory in town that you worked for had turned into the world’s top five hundred companies! Overnight!

I only looked away for moment, and you had already ascended to the sky?

The curiosity of the crowd was so great that they were anxious about the deeds of the Black Star Army in the past decade. They could not help but wish to scrub the video straight to the end.

Just what exactly happened when we were not here? How did the Black Star Army leap up to become such a great influence?

Chapter 718: Defensive Measures Against Thieves

The size of the Black Star Army truly shocked the players. The video then continued to play, and the video finally began to explain what the Black Star Army had been through over the past ten years.

"Galaxy Year 695, the Crimson Dynasty expanded their territory, code name Crimson Tide. The Shattered Star Ring was thrown into chaos, and the Klent Kingdom ordered Bloodshed Land to invade the Purple Crystal Civilization. The secret war exploded, and the Black Star Army joined Purple Crystal and fought on their behalf. The war has been going on for ten years and isn't over yet. During this time, the Black Star Army has fought hundreds of battles and clashed with Bloodshed Land time and time again and forged their prestige..."

Rossellin introduced the background of the secret war and everyone was startled.

Crimson Tide? Isn't this the name of the version? It turns out that this refers to the expansion of the Crimson Dynasty. During the end of Version 2.0, Black Star revealed information about this. So, it turns out he was truly revealing information about the next version.

To think that Black Star Army would be dragged into a war between Star Cluster Civilizations. This means that the Main Storyline Mission for Version 3.0 should be related to the secret war...

Many of the players began to speculate.

If they continued along this line of thought, the expansion of the Black Star Army would definitely be related to their participation in the war. The Black Star Army should have gained wealth from the war.

However, they had only managed to guess half the truth. The next part of the video immediately triggered a huge wave of commotion.

"In this war, leader Black Star revealed the potential of becoming a Beyond Grade A Super. He suppressed all the high-level combatants of the enemy and is invincible on the battlefield. He is the most likely individual to become a Beyond Grade A Super in the entire Shattered Star Ring. The Black Star Army also became a Beyond Grade A seeded organization under his lead, with Purple Crystal and dozens of other Star System Civilizations expressing their goodwill toward him."

As the leader of the faction, Rossellin gave a detailed introduction on Black Star and described his frightening combat prowess and the influence he had in the development of the Black Star Army.

Most of the players understood that the video was trying to hint to them that the Black Star Army was only able to develop to such a level because of Black Star. If not for Han Xiao displaying the potential to become a Beyond Grade A Super, the Black Star Army would not have been able to stand out in the war.

Black Star was the one who had developed the Black Star Army to such a size in ten years!

The players all came to a realization and immediately extracted the main point.

Beyond Grade A!

After two versions, they already knew that Black Star was extremely powerful, but never had they expected him to overturn their understanding of him yet again!

A Beyond Grade A Super was already at the peak of the Galaxy to the players. Black Star was a character who came out in Version 1.0, and his storyline had run through three different versions. Currently, he had the right to become a peerless expert and would probably become an important character in Version 3.0.

Han Xiao was already one of their own to the China players, and the players could not help but erupt with excitement when they found out that their boss was such a ferocious character.

Before the update, many players were looking forward to seeing how the Black Star Army grew during Version 3.0. The outcome at this moment truly filled them with satisfaction and was out of their expectations. When they were not around, Black Star was as reliable as always and had led the Black Star Army into such a fantastic shape. He was truly awesome!

Their captain was still the best!

With such a powerful leader, their faction had a greater potential for growth, and the players grew even more passionate for the Black Star Army.

The video continued playing, and Rossellin went into detail about the various events and accomplishments of the Black Star Army over the past ten years. She weaved in the various personal accomplishments of Han Xiao. How he fought of multiple enemies alone, fought bravely to scare off the enemies, resolved numerous assassination attempts, battled EsGod, wiped out DarkStar, and so on.

The lesson introduced the entire history of the Black Star Army, and after the end of the video, many players were still hungry for more. With Bun-Hit-Dog's videos as a foundation, this video made them feel as though they were chasing after a drama series.

"This can be considered a background introduction to this new version, right?"

"Why do I feel as though this is more like an action film?"

"Black Star is awesome!"

"This is truly a growth-type faction! Our future is bright! Hahaha."

All the players discussed the video excitedly.

The changes in the Black Star Army had truly shocked them. After calming down from their initial shock, they were immediately overjoyed.

As long as the change was a positive one, the players could be at ease. The more impressive the achievements of the Black Star Army, the more at ease they would be. This was a faction which they had witnessed for a full three versions.

"Who would have thought that so much would happen when we weren't around?" Frenzied Sword could not help but lament.

Bun-Hit-Dog felt his heart ache. "What a pity. I could have made so many videos with all these resources."

The video showed them the history of the Black Star Army and allowed the players to have a better understanding of their own faction. Han Xiao had always aimed to use the accomplishments of the faction to increase the sense of belonging that the players felt to the Black Star Army, and the outcome was extremely good. A faction that had a history behind it would bring about a greater sense of belonging apart from the benefits that it could bring to the players.

Through the events over the past ten years, all the players had a basic understanding of Version 3.0. It could be said that the players adapted at the fastest possible speed to the new version through Han Xiao's guidance. This was also the outcome that Han Xiao wanted to see the most.

The second phase of the [Ten Years] mission was completed and Han Xiao released the third phase of the mission.

All the players in the Black Star Army received a new notification.

_____________________

[Ten Years]: The Third Link

Mission Introduction: You now understand the situation in the Shattered Star Ring. The Black Star Army is currently participating in the secret war. As a member of the army, you should make your choice.

Mission Requirements: Go through the necessary procedure and accept the secret war mission.

Reward: Start of the secret war storyline, +800 Black Star Army Favorability.

_____________________

"Triggering the Main Storyline Mission at the very beginning? It seems like this is the same as in Version 2.0."

They had triggered the Mutation Disaster storyline the moment they logged into the game as well. The players did not hesitate in the slightest and chose to participate in the secret war.

In his previous life, the players had to go through an exploration phase before being guided to join the secret war by the various factions. This time, Han Xiao had immediately placed the Main Storyline mission right in front of the players and saved them a great deal of trouble. The earlier the players joined the mission, the more benefits he would receive.

Originally, the method to trigger the secret war mission was to join either Bloodshed Land or Section Zero. However, Han Xiao knew about this and had thus spent the past ten years growing the Black Star Army into an important member of Section Zero. This enabled him to tie his faction together with Section Zero and allowed the players to participate in the secret war mission without joining another faction.

The rewards of Han Xiao's effort were slowly showing themselves.

The next moment, a notification popped up on the player's interface. They had triggered the Main Storyline Mission that Han Xiao had triggered ten years ago.

_____________________

You have triggered Grade S faction mission [Secret War: Section Zero]!

Mission Introduction: The Klent Kingdom has invaded the Purple Crystal Civilization, and you chose to stand on the side of the Purple Crystal Civilization.

Mission Requirements: Listen to orders and force all invaders out of the Colton Star Cluster.

At the end of the mission, your reward will be based on the rating of the mission.

_____________________

Grade S Mission!

The eyes of the players lit up. The Main Storyline Missions of the first two versions were Grade A missions, and this was the first time that they had accepted a Grade S mission.

Han Xiao had received this mission ten years earlier than the players. While the Mission Rating would only be displayed at the end of the mission, Han Xiao was certain that he had long reached the highest rating.

"This Main Storyline mission has a suffix. Does this mean that we will also be able to do this mission in the Klent faction?" Bun-Hit-Dog immediately managed to guess the truth.

In Han Xiao's previous life, the players could choose between Klent or Purple Crystal, and both factions had their own strengths. Purple Crystal was located in the Colton Star Cluster, which was also where the players were located. On top of that, they also had the geographical advantage as the defending party. On the other side, the Tyrant from Bloodshed Land was a Beyond Grade A Super, and he was also extremely attractive to the players.

The original storyline of Version 2.0 did not include the Black Star Army. Godora and DarkStar were the organizations that brought the players into the galaxy. They each hired some players and brought the players onto two different paths.

The players that were in the DarkStar faction had automatically joined Klent due to the connection between Klent and DarkStar. Because of the Tyrant's prestige, many players had chosen to join Bloodshed Land, resulting in the Section Zero faction being on the passive side.

However, Han Xiao had already changed the storyline and set a good foundation in Version 2.0. He had singlehandedly snatched almost all the Planet Aquamarine players from both Godora and DarkStar.

Currently, the Black Star Army was the most important member in Section Zero. This meant that all the players would naturally be on Purple Crystal's side!

Those who wanted to join Klent would have to give up all their investments in the Black Star Army from the past two versions. This meant that the players' cost of changing factions was extremely high. While the players did not like being forced, with the sense of belonging being cultivated in the first two versions together with his first mover advantage, the players would not feel too troubled by the lack of options.

While the Beyond Grade A Heber did indeed have some attraction to the players, the players had just watched a video that showed them that Black Star also had the potential to become a Beyond Grade A Super. The Bloodshed Land immediately lost their greatest selling point, and even if the majority of the players knew that they could switch factions, they would not do so as it was not worth it.

Thus, it would be impossible for Klent and Bloodshed Land to gain a large number of players like in Han Xiao's previous life!

The butterfly effect that Han Xiao had created in Version 2.0 was still affecting events.

However, the players were a strange breed, and there would be some who wanted to join the whistleblower club. Han Xiao had already thought of a plan to deal with them.

He had considered many different scenarios over the past ten years.

As the players discussed the Main Storyline Mission excitedly, Han Xiao no longer pretended to view the scenery and returned to the inside of the armed satellite fortress.

The first step is complete. It is now time to fertilize the crops...

Chapter 719: Fertilization

On the dock, the more than one hundred thousand players scattered. The guiding mission given by Han Xiao had ended, they decided to explore the Black Star Army headquarters and get to know the facilities here.

The players knew that this planet fortress would most likely be their base in Version 3.0.

The Black Star Army headquarters was extremely large, not cramped at all even for more than a hundred thousand people. They quickly scattered and fused into the usual Black Star Army members.

Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and a few other close professional players moved together, accompanied by Bun-Hit-Dog and Maple Moon. They walked around and observed the NPCs passing by while discussing the main storyline mission they had just received.

"The storyline of the new version is so exciting," Frenzied Sword said. "I can’t believe we are going to experience an enormous war between two Star Cluster civilizations. Those in the other Star Fields did not receive the main storyline mission as soon as they entered the game like we did; they’re still exploring."

"Well, this isn’t the first time. In every past version, the main storyline always appeared the earliest in Shattered Star Ring. This should be our specialty." Twinkle Fried Rice shrugged.

"Indeed, it was the same in Version 2.0. We knew about the main storyline as soon as we came online. The other Star Fields only got it months or even a year later." Hao Tian nodded.

"From how things are looking, it seems Black Star is going to be the main NPC in Version 3.0 once again. All the main storylines in the past three versions were related to him," Bun-Hit-Dog said while rubbing his chin.

"It’s more than three versions…" Frenzied Sword said with an excited expression. "I saw him even during the closed beta, but back then, I never guessed he would become this strong."

Bun-Hit-Dog’s eyes sparkled. "Black Star is making so many appearances. I don’t think the other Star Fields have an NPC similar to him at all. Black Star is the only NPC that has appeared in every version for the past three versions. I feel like Black Star might be the protagonist of the entire Shattered Star Ring… That’s right, this sounds like an amazing topic to talk about. The next episode of my video will definitely explode!"

Han Xiao was now extremely popular among the Chinese players. Plus, the video earlier showed his achievements in the past ten years, so this was the time when the players were most interested in him. Therefore, Bun-Hit-Dog felt like he could make use of that and use the topic of ‘Shattered Star Ring’s protagonist’ to make the next episode of his video series. He believed that it would definitely become very popular.

In the past two versions, the players had experienced many interesting storylines in Galaxy and witnessed all kinds of NPCs. Quite a number of those NPCs were also widely liked by the players, but Black Star was the only one that the players had the deepest impression of. Even the players in the other Star Fields knew his name. Currently, Han Xiao was the most famous NPC and also the NPC that the players wanted to see the most.

In the eyes of many players, creating articles, videos, or anything related to Black Star was a business opportunity.

‘Black Star Series’ was the video series that had made Bun-Hit-Dog famous. It was one of the must-watch videos for the new players, and it was still ongoing.

Due to the fame brought by this series, Bun-Hit-Dog was most passionate about building Han Xiao’s image. However, due to how famous Black Star was, there were also other video creators that did the same and made videos about the Black Star Army.

Nonetheless, Bun-Hit-Dog had captured the market as early as back in Version 1.0, so he was the most ‘authentic’ in the eyes of the players.

It could be said that Bun-Hit-Dog’s videos contributed greatly to how much the players liked the Black Star Army. As members of the Black Star Army, seeing that the faction was growing under their influence and hard work, and that it was made into a kind of drama series, it gave them a very strong immersive experience.

Video creators such as Bun-Hit-Dog used NPCs’ fame to benefit themselves, but they did not know that Han Xiao was also using them.

The group chatted for a while and returned to the main topic of the main storyline of the new version—this was what the professional players were interested in.

"By the way, with our strength, we shouldn’t be able to influence the result of this galactic war, right?" Frenzied Sword said.

Maple Moon nodded and said seriously, "Hmm. I just checked. The representatives of the secret war are the Bloodshed Land and Section Zero, which the Black Star Army is a part of. The leader of the Bloodshed Land is called Heber, one of the Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring. As for Section Zero, their organization is also extremely large. With both sides being so strong, the people involved in the war are most likely in the billions. Even if all the players take part, I don’t think the result of the war will be affected much, if at

all…"

Hao Tian pondered and analyzed, "If that’s the case, the secret war is just the major background of the new version. The main areas we will be acting in should be the smaller battlefields within the war."

"I hope they aren’t just more cut scenes…" Twinkle Fried Rice smiled bitterly.

"That might not be the case…" Seeing that the others turned to look at him, Frenzied Sword continued to explain. "Think about it, for the past three versions, our level limit has been increasing. The scale of the storyline has been increasing too, from a planet, to a Star System, to a Star Cluster. However, the combat capability standard in the Galaxy has a stable system. For example, Grade Cs are basic galactic warriors, so Grade Bs are the mid-tier combatants. This system will not change because of the version updates, while our Grades will keep increasing. This means that our position in the Galaxy and our influence on the storyline will keep growing as the version keeps updating!

"Now that the level limit is 120, the first batch of players should all be able to reach Grade B. According to this theory, our importance in the new version will definitely exceed the previous two versions. Hence, I think that we will be able to take part in the storyline of Galaxy more actively in Version 3.0, and there will definitely be new ways of playing this game."

The others contemplated for a while. Damn, this guy does kind of make sense.

Bun-Hit-Dog’s eyes sparkled. "Can I cop… quote what you just said?"

"Please, act like a human being." Twinkle Fried Rice was speechless.

"By the way, although we triggered the main storyline, how are we going to take part in the war? Do we listen to the army’s arrangements or take on missions on our own?"

At this point, Frenzied Sword and the others suddenly realized that the Black Star Army members around all suddenly gathered in the same direction. Their communicators also vibrated. It was a notification from Phillip to tell all the members in the headquarters to head to the square—there was going to be an announcement.

Frenzied Sword and the others went to the square with the crowd. The place was now filled with people. The other players had arrived as well and were waiting with the other Black Star Army members.

The floor in front of the crowd curved up and turned into a stage. Projections appeared above the square and displayed the image of the stage so that the people far away could see.

More than twenty high-level army officers appeared on the stage. Many were familiar faces to the players.

"It’s been ten years, but the officers from Version 2.0 are all still here. That’s nice."

"There seem to be quite a few new officers as well."

"Oh, is that beauty Sylvia?"

"Oh no, is this excitement I feel?"

"Humph, so what if that’s a beauty? I’m an educated person. Us Dragon Emperor Lickers will never betray our faith!"

Seeing the familiar NPCs from the last version, many players felt nostalgic. Out of habit, they threw detections at the officers. Other than getting to know the names of these officers, the rest of the information was all question marks, and every one of the officers was shown as ‘Fatally Dangerous’.

Now, the players finally had a clearer image of how strong the Black Star Army was.

Hum!

The space in the middle of the stage rippled. A person appeared out of thin air and walked out of the void. It was Han Xiao.

More than a hundred thousand players finally saw what Han Xiao looked like after ten years. He was still wearing the familiar clothing but taller and more level-headed.

Frenzied Sword and the others realized that admiration appeared on the faces of many of the Black Star Army members around.

From this detail, they were clearer on Han Xiao’s position in the hearts of his subordinates. Bun-Hit-Dog quickly started recording to collect materials.

Including the players, countless people in the square were staring at Han Xiao. He cleared his throat, and his voice spread across the entire square through machines.

"In half a month, we will work with the large group of Section Zero to launch a large-scale counterattack against the Bloodshed Land. Many people will be recruited to take part. Other than the warriors that have already been enlisted, the army will be accepting the enlistment requests of the rest of the members as well. Other than the returns paid by the Purple Crystal Civilization, the army will provide additional subsidies for those who take part in the war according to their position. The details are on the announcement board of the internal army system…"

As a mercenary group, the members would just split the reward given by the employer. Now that the Black Star Army had completed its transition into a private armed force, it had to pay salaries to the official members like the military. Taking part in a war was extremely risky, so additional subsidies were required as well.

Luckily, Black Star Army was more than able to afford those expenses even with its current size.

"So that’s how we’re going to take part in the war. We’ll have to request it in the army," Frenzied Sword said.

"The Rating of the main storyline mission can only be increased by taking part in the war, but we can choose not to. So, this isn’t a compulsory storyline mission."

The players started to discuss the topic, and the square became noisy.

This time, Han Xiao looked around, chuckled in his mind, and continued.

"All those who are taking part in the war will enjoy fifty percent off when purchasing the various products of the army. In half a month’s time, all those taking part shall gather in the headquarters and board the fleet to head to the battlefield. If you have any questions, you can ask the artificial intelligence program of the army."

The crowd was stunned.

Fifty percent off?

Fifty percent for all the faction products

What?

That’s amazing!

Chapter 720: Players, I'm Gonna Earn Till I Explode!

The players were ecstatic and could not wait to open the faction store interface.

Compared to Version 2.0, the faction store’s product categories had increased by hundreds of times, and various equipment, materials, and items were all available. Because the Black Star Army had collaborated with many different financial groups, Han Xiao had managed to negotiate with the leaders of the various financial groups to open their purchase channels to his faction members.

In this manner, as long as an object was not too rare, the faction store would definitely be selling it. This led to a significant increase in the logistics capabilities of the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao had also collected a huge number of blueprint drawings in the past few years and vigorously developed the backend logistics division. With the support of his strong economic strength, he had established countless factories and assembly lines for the logistics department and even trained up a group of professionals. Currently, the capability of the Black Star Army to produce independently was very strong, already having stored tens of thousands of machines and equipment, including rare high-end equipment such as orange and pink equipment.

All the materials and equipment would be supplied to the members of the faction. As long as they had money, they would be able to arm themselves to the teeth.

The standard issued armor of the Black Star Army had also undergone many changes through the past seven years. It had integrated a variety of intermediate-level armor technology, further strengthening it to be better armor. It had been mass produced for the middle to lower ranked members, named ‘Black Star Army’s Mark 7 Individual Soldier Armor’. It could transform into specialized modes for attack, defense, reconnaissance, and more.

The armor of the majority of players had fallen behind in times. Compared to the current Mark 7 armor, it looked more like a trinket than actual armor.

Looking at the list of items the faction store offered, the desires of the players started to burn. This was especially true for Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the other professional players who did not lack money.

If they participated in the battle, all the good items, including orange equipment, would be on fifty percent off!

This opportunity, once gone, would never come back!

The players had amassed a large sum during Version 2.0, and having come across this sale with great difficulty, where they would finally upgrade their equipment, the idea of diligently saving up was simply thrown out the window.

What was the purpose of saving? To be able to spend it all when the opportune time came!

When one could bear it no longer, there was no need to endure!

Without hesitation, the players on scene immediately applied for the military operation through Phillip.

With the fast processing speed of Phillip, it quickly completed the request of all the players present, sending out the mission that Han Xiao had long prepared to them.

(Faction War Mission: Black Star’s Counterattack]

Mission Introduction: Section Zero has prepared a large-scale counterattack military operation. As a glorious Black Star Warrior, you have chosen to participate in this campaign.

Mission Requirements: Follow the Black Star Army’s fleet, and obey orders to participate in the battle.

Reward: +500 Black Star Army Favorability, activate the follow-up mission of the secret war.

The players present only took a glance at the interface notification before turning their attention back to the Faction store. Indeed, everything present was reduced by half.

The players were all overjoyed and could not wait to dance around merrily.

Han Xiao had released this mission in order to guide the players as he had no control over the activation of main storylines. Thus, he used the reward section to let players understand that they would start the following mission of the secret war main storyline. This was to give players peace of mind, allowing them to improve their participation during the battle and reducing the number of slackers.

In the past, Section Zero had also assigned players to participate in the battle. This time, he had taken in so many players, so the labor had to be done by himself.

This large-scale military operation had not been proposed suddenly as Han Xiao knew that the players would return during this time. Two months prior, he had already begun preparations for this large-scale counterattack operation. He had waited until now to bring players with him to join in this secret war together.

While the players had accumulated a lot of experience and money in Version 2.0, Han Xiao’s upgrades now required a sky-high price. The experience they had saved up was just not enough, and he had to fatten them up once more, or else the Mission Completion Cards he had saved up would be useless.

As soon as this version opened, Han Xiao could not wait to guide the players over to the war missions. This was to allow them to accumulate as much experience as possible; only by increasing the players’ spending power and letting them become rich could he then earn even more. He had always been an advocate for mutual benefits and being well-off comprehensively.

Putting it in another way, the leeks that he had planted were not ripe yet. He still had to give it his all to fertilize them.

Han Xiao also knew well that with every new version, raising their levels to the upper limit would be the players’ first choice. As such, their desire to spend would be lowered. Han Xiao needed to stimulate demand and make players willing to take out their wallets for consumption.

The fifty percent discount for the war participants was just one of his measures to stimulate the demand in the players.

The large number of players formed a turbulent human wave as they left the square, going straight toward the logistics department. Meanwhile, every one of them was browsing the store, looking for their favorite equipment or items.

"One set of the standard issued armor, and I’ll take the skin for it as well!"

"Jackpot, jackpot! This time, we hit the motherload!"

"Never expected this sort of benefit from the beginning of the version. This is to improve our combat capability, allowing us to protect ourselves in the war mission. The head really loves us!"

The hundred thousand or so players nearly burst the logistics department at the seams when they all rushed in to order equipment.

In addition to the single players wantonly buying, a few of the guilds began to organize their manpower, calling friends to crowdfund their items.

"Such opportunities are rare. Hurry and get more money. We can buy better things with these!"

The Guild of Gods Head Jupiter showed an expression of glee, prepared to utilize the funds of his guild to buy a few sets of mining spaceships and equipment. In the future, Guild of Gods would be able to mine their own resources, receiving a steady stream of profits.

Professional players like Frenzied Sword, however, preferred the high quality equipment and went to find their respective club’s guild to raise money, buying orange equipment crazily.

The players present looked as though they had all consumed aphrodisiacs, their desire for consumption skyrocketing to extreme levels. Wave after wave of purchases were made, and on their hands were big and small bags, all containing new equipment. Although their wallets were emptied, everybody had a smile on their face.

Having saved fifty percent of what they were supposed to pay, they were so happy!

At the same time, Han Xiao returned to his office, checking the revenue data of the army.

"In just half an hour, I’ve earned 2.7 billion Enas," Han Xiao murmured to himself. Even with the current huge assets of the Black Star Army, this sum was no small amount. If averaged out, an individual player had spent close to 20,000 Enas. While all the goods were on a fifty percent sale, his total profit after deducting the costs was still hundreds of millions of Enas.

With the current productivity and warehouse capacity of the Black Star Army, meeting the demands of all the players was simply a piece of cake.

Han Xiao did not play his strategy of raising the price first before slashing it; he indeed placed all his goods at a fifty percent discount this time. However, because he had already mastered the Technology specialization, the profits after discount was still immensely high!

The players were also not stupid and would definitely remember the prices of goods in the previous version. Furthermore, what Han Xiao was lacking now was not money, so he had no need to destroy the goodwill between him and the players for just this paltry sum. It would be better to allow the players to feel some substantial benefits.

His goal was not to obtain this pot of money but rather to stimulate the consumers’ desire for consumption, emptying the players’ wallets before using this long-term discount activity to make players generate money quickly. Thus, they would work harder to participate in the war. Through this, their experience would fill up and empty out for him, then rinse and repeat… Continuously draining the players wallets would keep their fighting spirit up!

A mature leek would know how to engage in self-fertilization!

"Now that the players have spent all their money, I guess we can start soon…" Han Xiao’s eyes narrowed as the corners of his mouth curled up.

In fact, emptying the players’ wallet was just the prelude prepared by Han Xiao. The real harvest had just begun!

In the Logistics Department, the amount of equipment left in the deposit did not even hit triple digits. As the players put on their new equipment, they felt content at how rewarding the buying spree was. Their desire to spend money was not yet over, however, and they opened the faction store to browse if there was anything else that they could take advantage of.

Looking at the sky-high prices even after discounting for the top-tier equipment, the players were moved, but they could not afford it even with the discount. Thus, they could only look away in resignation. It was at this time that someone found out the faction store stocked a lot more Profession Knowledge compared to the previous Version.

As they closely scrutinized it, the players received a huge shock.

The faction store actually contained the Basic and Advanced Knowledge of the various Psychic, Mechanic, Esper, Psychic, and Magic Professions!

There were even a few Professions that had High-End Knowledge!

Everyone present clearly remembered that in Version 2.0, the Black Star Army did not have a complete copy of all knowledge for the five major professions.

In fact, the Basic and Advanced Knowledge for each Profession could easily be gathered as long as one had money. With the current financial power of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao had gathered all the various lower-tier Profession Knowledge in the past seven years and even bought over a few high-end knowledges.

Having reached this level, the Black Star Army members under Han Xiao were numerous, with people of all different Professions. Buying this many different types of Knowledges was so that he could conveniently groom more warriors.

However, in the eyes of the players, this had extraordinary significance. In order to obtain profession knowledge, players in the various Star Fields had to increase favorability of the various profession mentors as well as the favorability of the faction they were in, and this was troublesome.

However, in the Black Star Army, they were able to master the profession knowledge of the classes, which signified that they did not need to find a mentor, and this would save them a lot of time and energy. This was an advantage that players from the other Star Fields did not have!

The most surprising thing was that, not only did the amount of Profession Knowledge increase, they actually did not require money!

Learning knowledge in the previous versions required money. However, this time, in the faction store, knowledge only required one’s Faction Contribution Points as well as experience!

Although the experience cost of learning a Knowledge remained, the required Faction Contribution Points had halved!

"They actually made Knowledge free of charge?"

"This doesn’t make sense. Why is it that Profession Knowledge does not require money now? Won’t it be a loss for us since we bought it last version using money?"

"Wait, I’ve discovered the reason!"

If a problem could not be solved, they could ask Phillip. Some of the players took the initiative to open the subprogram and ask, and they quickly got the answer.

Due to the scale of expansion for the Black Star Army, training camps had been established in various places. In order to train up members of the army on a large scale, the exchange pattern for Knowledge had thus been altered. Members of the army could apply for the Knowledge so long as they had enough contributions instead.

This system not only applied to the players but also to NPCs. This was equivalent to the induction training for the Black Star Army.

The crowd was astonished and realized even more about the great cause of the Black Star Army. This Star Cluster level Organization was indeed miles apart from its past, with high generosity and a proper system in place.

"So, we also receive the same welfare?" Other than a portion of people feeling depressed that they had spent the money in vain, the rest were all overjoyed.

"So, does that mean that we all need not pay whenever we wish to learn Knowledge next time, just use our Contribution Points!"

"Damn, this is too good!"

"It’s indeed a Faction for growth. The treatment is awesome!"

The majority of players were relieved, and they could feel the practical benefits of the development that the Black Star Army had undergone in the past decade.

When comparing faction benefits, the Black Star Army had left the rest in the dust!

How blissful!

"Just now, the three consecutive chain missions awarded us quite a bit of contribution points, enough to buy a few of the Knowledges. My Basic Knowledge is not complete yet."

"Hehe, I’m out of money, but learning Knowledge does not require money!"

"The faction contribution points are even at a fifty percent discount. This benefit is really too good, too profitable!"

With the mentality of ‘since I can take advantage, I might as well do it’, the group of players immediately used up all the experience points that they had saved to obtain all the various Knowledges.

Following the buying of the Knowledge, the dry experience bank of Han Xiao started to fill up once more.

"Finally…"

Han Xiao let out a deep breath, feeling relieved.

This was what he needed the most!

He had abolished the monetary price for Knowledge to gain a large amount of the players’ experience. However, because the system also took into account NPCs, Han Xiao had thus made it into a system of contribution points for Knowledge.

For his normal members, experience was an intangible object, so if there was no requirement in terms of contribution points, it would be equivalent to giving it away, which would result in serious problems. This was his bottom line for maintaining the system of the faction.

In order to allow players to fork out the experience to purchase the Knowledges, Han Xiao had utilized the three guiding missions earlier to send the players a wave of contribution points. Following which, he had then used the ploy of halving prices to incite the players’ desires, emptying their purses.

After they had finished spending, the players would definitely want to take advantage of the system with the fifty percent off. At this time, they would then discover that Knowledge did not require money, and with their contribution point prices halved, a portion of the players would use their experience to learn various Knowledges. The reason it was only a portion was because knowledge could be learned at any point in time, but Han Xiao wanted to harvest some player experience in this short amount of time.

After being deprived for a decade, he could bear it no longer!

After considering that it was necessary to maintain the value of the contribution of the camp as a secondary currency and that it could not trigger ‘inflation’ in the process, Han Xiao did not give out too many contribution points to the players… or else he would have just thrown the players a motherload of contribution points, to the extent that they would reach the [Reverence) relationship, allowing them to learn all the knowledge they wanted. Not only would he empty their purses, he would also empty their experience bars, robbing them of both resources!

It’s better to harvest slowly. I’ll save some experience for them, allowing them to rise to Grade B. I cannot just pull my leeks out from the roots…

Han Xiao was acutely aware that he could not pull out the seedlings to make it look like they were growing

Watching his experience counter skyrocket, he licked his lips, a moved expression on his face.

It had been ten years. Finally, he could fill up his experience slot, this bottomless pit!

Chapter 721: The World Doesn't Lack 'Smart People'

Through the forums and internal message system within the army, the players who were in the other bases also received news about the discount they could get if they participated in the war.

Around ten days later, more than a million players gathered at the headquarters of the army and chose to participate in the war.

A portion of the players fell for Han Xiao’s marketing strategy and surrendered their entire wallet to him. In just half a month, they provided the Black Star Army with a few hundred million in pure profit.

However, most of the players still placed their focus on leveling up. For example, all the professional players focused fully on leveling up during the start of the version, and the number of players who chose to learn new knowledge were the minority.

Han Xiao did not feel discouraged. When the players became fat with experience and had some extra experience points, they would definitely purchase the various knowledge from the army; it was only a matter of time before their experience became his. Just the profit from this half a month was more than the total that he had earned over the past seven years.

The players happily enjoyed their new equipment while Han Xiao happily counted his money.

In just half a month, Han Xiao increased his level to 217, and he was only three levels away from level 220.

After this round of harvesting, he had pretty much emptied all the savings of the players, and they needed some time to recover.

The players’ savings are still too little. At the end of the previous version, many of the players went to participate in the preliminary round of the Pro League for fun and used all their experience points leveling up their skills. It is best I feed them until they are fat first.

In the lounge of the conference room, a group of officers were playing cards and creating a loud commotion. Han Xiao sat on the sofa alone and began thinking of his future plans.

After this battle, I should be able to gather enough experience to reach the next promotion mission. The gap to becoming a Beyond Grade A Super is becoming narrower.

While it would not be that easy for him to become a Beyond Grade A Super, Han Xiao was satisfied with his current progress. The other Beyond Grade A seeds still could not find a way to break into the Beyond Grade A realm and were stuck at a bottleneck. On the contrary, his growth was only reliant on his leveling speed, and he did not have any real bottlenecks.

Furthermore, he still had a stash of Mission Completion Cards. As long as he had sufficient experience, his growth would be smooth.

Just as Han Xiao was thinking, a loud cheer could be heard from the side.

Lagi had a look of resignation on his face as he made his classic pessimistic remark. He then stood up to leave his seat. On the other side of the table, Reynold sat down with his back straight and a calm expression on his face. He nodded slightly as though to say, Thank you for letting me win.

"Not bad, our Logistics Manager won five games in a row."

"Tsk, I lost 50,000 Enas. I should’ve bet on Reynold instead."

"Our vice commander was completely thrashed. His skills are just too lousy."

"The logical thinking process of a Mechanic is truly amazing… but why is His Excellency Black Star so terrible at playing cards?"

Sylvia turned around and said to Han Xiao, "Teacher! Someone is talking bad about you!"

Han Xiao snapped back to reality and walked toward Sylvia with his hands behind his back. Standing behind Sylvia, he bent down slightly and placed his chin on Sylvia’s head. His gaze then swept past all the officers with an expression that said, Let me see who is talking bad about me.

Because the majority of the officers had participated in the battle a few days ago, almost all the core members of the army were present in headquarters. Han Xiao had held a short meeting before this, and after the meeting, everyone had gone to the lounge to play cards and opened a betting station.

Han Xiao was not interested in participating in any activity that relied on luck.

Reynold was originally studying a blueprint by the side, but after Sylvia lost a few games in a row, she insisted on dragging Reynold into the game to vent some anger for her.

While Reynold did not like wasting time on entertainment activities such as Wayne Cards, he would occasionally be invited to join a game or two and thus had his own deck.

Playing Wayne Cards seemed to be a part of all the officers’ resumes.

While all the officers had powerful combat capabilities, they usually did not manage administrative matters. When they were not deployed, they also had hobbies like an ordinary individual.

Since he had decided to play, Reynold naturally treated every game seriously. He had a powerful logical reasoning skill, and he had always been good at playing cards. He won five games in a row and did not even show his sister Rossellin any mercy.

Reynold collected his cards and looked around expressionlessly. "Who else?"

"Teacher, why not you play a round too," Sylvia then said with a cheeky smile.

"I bet that Black Star will lose," Harmon said honestly. "It is a sure win bet."

"Not bad." Han Xiao snorted. "I will beat whoever dares to win against me to death. Who wants to play?"

"No no no."

Everyone waved their hands immediately. You’re the boss. You’re the strongest. Of course, we won’t dare to play.

Reynold knocked on the table lightly and said, "If no one is playing with me, I shall take my leave."

Right at this moment, Herlous stepped forward and sat opposite Reynold. Let me take you on.

"I shall let you understand the true meaning of skill."

"It should be the true meaning of luck, right?" Reynold replied expressionlessly.

Herlous snorted. "Humph, luck is a type of skill too."

"It’s over. Reynold’s victory streak shall end here."

"Reynold, take care of this b\*stard."

Everyone cheered on excitedly.

After seven years of hard work, Herlous had finally stepped into the doors of a Calamity Grade Super. His talent was truly higher than his peers, and he lived up to the name of being a protagonist character. It was as though he had become a Grade A Super just by playing cards.

Among all the officers, Herlous enjoyed playing Wayne Cards the most. Because all his victories usually come from a lucky draw, together with the fact that Feidin did not like to play cards, Herlous had some prestige in the Wayne Card world of the Black Star Army.

Even the players knew that he would never reject an opponent, and even they could find Herlous to play cards against. There were even corresponding missions, and they could obtain experience points if they beat Herlous, even getting the chance to obtain a rare card from him.

After a few lines of trash talk, Herlous started his game with Reynold. Both of them were using a Black Star Army deck.

Five years ago, the Wayne Cards had been refreshed, and despite being a subsidiary of Floating Dragon, the Black Star Army had more Wayne Cards than Floating Dragon. Han Xiao’s card was strengthened greatly with plenty of special effects and high HP. His card had already become a rare card.

Not too long later, Herlous got a few lucky draws in a row. Despite Reynold’s skills being superior, he was still on the losing end.

A thought suddenly sprung up in Han Xiao’s head, and he gave Herlous a (Luck Curse).

"Humph, you are dead." Herlous drew with confidence, but after glancing at his card, his face froze up.

Wayne Cards were pretty much determined by luck, and Herlous’ Luck attribute was still higher than his after being reduced by ninety percent. But in front of Reynold, he could only lose miserably after a few terrible draws, and Reynold easily turned the tables.

"Eh? Your luck finally isn’t working?"

"Haha, you can also have such a day."

Herlous’ face darkened, and he quibbled, "What do you lot know? This is a strategic retreat. I will turn the tables in a while."

Everyone around burst into laughter, and the entire room was filled with energy.

Han Xiao did not join in the fun and returned to the sofa to check the forums.

It had been less than half a month since the release of Version 3.0, and the players from the other Star Fields were still in the exploratory phase. The news that had been released by Han Xiao had become a clue for the other players who were searching for the Main Storyline Missions in the various Star Fields.

This time, the Main Storyline Mission in the Shattered Star Ring was the first to appear again, and the players from the other Star Fields were all extremely jealous. As such, the forum of the Shattered Star Ring was the liveliest, with players from many other Star Fields coming to leave their comments.

Coincidentally, Bun-Hit-Dog’s new video was also released, and it discussed how the Black Star Army was a hidden Main Storyline Mission that spanned across three different versions. A huge wave of discussion was created, and both Han Xiao and the Black Star Army became the hottest topic in the past half a month.

Han Xiao briefly looked through the post, and it was mainly describing his importance and past events. Bun-Hit-Dog helped to boost his fame, which was never a bad thing.

The event that made Han Xiao the happiest was that Galaxy Times introduced the benefits of the Black Star Army according to the players’ information.

Version 3.0 would bring about a new wave of players joining the game, and the introduction from Galaxy Times would sway many into choosing the Shattered Star Ring as their starting point. This would directly result in a large increase in the number of players.

Knowledge can only be learned once, and these new players represent a new market. Apart from Planet Aquamarine, there are a few other novice planets in the Shattered Star Ring. I need to find some time to construct a Black Star Army base on those planets and bring those players into the army.

Apart from the players who started off with him from Version 1.0, it was time for Han Xiao to increase the size of his crops.

The players from the other Star Fields also represent a huge market. It is a pity that the distance between Star Fields is too large. The Black Star Army still isn’t able to leave the Shattered Star Ring, and there isn’t any hope of capturing those markets for now.

Han Xiao shook his head silently. He had always been eyeing the players from the other Star Fields, but because of the distance, he had not been able to include them in his plans.

While casually glancing at the posts, one of the posts caught his eye.

The title of the post was ‘The True Strategy of the Secret War’.

What is this true strategy? Why don’t I know about it?

Han Xiao clicked on the post, and the owner of the post was someone called Summer Night Flower. The content of the post made Han Xiao raise his brows in response.

"… there are actually two factions that we can choose from in the secret war, and everyone should already know about this. However, we all belong to the Black Star Army and automatically belong to the Purple Crystal faction. Since that’s the case, why can we still choose the Klent faction? I think that a hint is hidden behind this.

"This hint is: Joining Klent will bring us more benefits than staying in the Black Star Army!

"This is the true strategy of the Main Storyline Mission!

"I am not spouting nonsense. Firstly, I’ve investigated the events that have happened over the past ten years. Bloodshed Land have had the upper hand from the beginning of the war, and they still have the advantage. They are invading more and more territories, and it seems like Klent has a much larger chance of victory.

"By looking back at the example of the Germinal Organization and Mutation Disaster, I have concluded that the Main Storyline Missions are out of our league, and players aren’t able to affect the direction of the storyline.

"The secret war is fought between two Star Cluster Civilizations, and I don’t think that we will be able to affect the outcome of the war.

"In other words, Klent will be the final victor of the war!

"While we will be able to receive benefits from staying in the Black Star Army, we will fail the Main Storyline Mission, which will result in a lower Mission Rating. If we join Klent, even if we skip the missions, our Mission Rating will be increased.

"Second, there aren’t many players joining Klent at the moment, and the competition is low. This means that we will have a greater chance of obtaining more resources. The Black Star Army has over a million players, and with so many people fighting for resources and missions, we will have to expend more energy to receive reward.

"Third, the connection to future versions. Klent’s backer is the Crimson Dynasty, which is one of the three great Universal Civilizations. The future versions will probably revolve around the Universal Civilizations, and joining Klent will open a door for us that leads to the Universal Civilizations.

"Regardless of how powerful the Black Star Army becomes, it will be impossible for them to exceed a Universal Civilization.

"Thus, we will only be able to enjoy short-term benefits if we join the Black Star Army and will end up losing more opportunities. Perhaps the benefits of the Black Star Army are no more than a trap. Only an intelligent individual will be able to see through it and join Klent!"

After reading the post, Han Xiao had a strange feeling

He recognized this player called Summer Night Flower. In his previous life, Summer Night Flower was a famous player who triggered a hidden storyline. He enjoyed analyzing storylines, and he had some fame.

If Han Xiao was being honest with himself, Summer Night Flower’s analysis truly seemed extremely logical.

However, Summer Night Flower was wrong from the very beginning. This was something that Han Xiao had purposely created, and there was no hidden hint or anything.

If someone really believed this post and chose to join Klent, the outcome would truly be terrible for them.

Han Xiao had a look of resignation on his face.

Even if you wanted to come up with a hypothesis, you should at least get your facts straight.

Hopefully no one ends up being fooled…

Chapter 722: Going to War

Han Xiao committed Summer Night Flower’s name to memory before throwing this matter to the back of his mind.

This was something that would definitely happen. Players were explorers after all; there would be some who wanted to seek something fresh. Since this could not be avoided, Han Xiao could only let nature take its course.

Only the crops that went through wind and rain would be truly precious.

After browsing through the forums for a while, Han Xiao suddenly felt the sofa tremble slightly, and someone sat down beside him. Turning around to look, it turned out to be Reynold.

"Not playing cards anymore?"

"Lagi dragged Feidin over. What’s the damn point of playing?" Reynold replied expressionlessly.

Han Xiao then chuckled before casually saying, "You must let me know if you have any requests."

"No."

"Think about it carefully again. Don’t need to worry about troubling me. You must let me know if you have any problems…"

Reynold had a strange look on his face. "Why do you ask me this question every month or

so?"

"It’s just me showing concern for my subordinates…" Han Xiao let out a dry cough. In order to obtain Reynold’s Perfect Mechanical Sense, Han Xiao showed concern to Reynold every now and then in an attempt to trigger a mission.

However, ever since Han Xiao saved Rossellin, not a single mission had appeared from Reynold again. Just when would he be able to finally obtain the Perfect Mechanical Sense talent?

Should I get some people to kidnap Rossellin so that Reynold will seek my help to save her?

"Your Excellency Black Star, how long do you think this war will last?" Reynold suddenly asked.

Han Xiao thought for a moment before saying, "If you were to ask for my opinion, a war represents opportunity, and the longer the war, the better. However, this war can only be considered ordinary when compared to the other galactic wars, which last hundreds of years. As long as the Crimson Dynasty finishes their negotiations with the Federation of Light, Klent will retreat. According to some intel that I received, the Universal Civilizations will probably finish their negotiations in a few

years."

Reynold shook his head. "Looking at the current situation, Klent has completed almost half of their plan. When the Crimson Dynasty has fulfilled their wish, they will help Klent redraw the territorial borders of the Seoul Star Cluster and include the few Star Clusters conquered by Bloodshed Land in the territory of their Seoul Star Cluster. If Purple Crystal doesn’t find a backer, they won’t get any help for sure."

"That’s right. An independent civilization will have to endure all this," Han Xiao replied. He had some thoughts of his own but did not feel that it was necessary to let Reynold know about them. After pausing for a while, he continued, "However, even after the end of the secret war, the Crimson Tide won’t disappear quickly. It is just like how a rock being thrown into still waters won’t only create a splash but ripples as well.

"There are numerous civilizations in the galaxy, and they all have their own desires for more, which is like extremely combustible firewood. The Crimson Tide is like a spark to light up their dormant desires. The moment their desires are ignited, they won’t be extinguished easily.

"Purple Crystal also know that they cannot let Bloodshed Land occupy so many Star Systems. The purpose of this battle is to organize a large-scale retaliation, clear out all the strongholds that Bloodshed Land have in the Kant Star System, and snatch back control of the entire Star System. This is the largest military operation that Purple Crystal has launched since the start of the war, and they are sending out almost all their forces."

In two days’ time, the Black Star Army would be officially deployed to meet up with the other members of Section Zero and head toward the Kant Star System.

This time, he was prepared to give the players a chance to show off their abilities and give all the dirty work to the players. More importantly, he wanted to groom the players and make them perform more war missions so that his crops could grow up healthily.

Since the players would not die, if they did not go to hell, who would?

Furthermore, the overall gaming experience would be better if the game was more dangerous. If the players did not experience some deaths, they would not be motivated at all.

Summer Night Flower had his eyes fixed on the forums, paying attention to the replies to his posts. Disagreements formed the majority of the replies, and his expression became ugly as he saw them.

He had only managed to create this post after some deep thought, and Summer Night Flower had felt extremely delighted at that moment. The way he saw it, he would definitely be able to knock many of the players awake and lead them in the right direction, gaining their praise in the process.

However, the reaction to the post was completely contrary to his expectations, and most of the players sided with the Black Star Army. Most of the replies were extremely sarcastic and said that his post was completely worthless and no more than a blind guess. This made Summer Night Flower extremely infuriated.

"These people do not know how to think at all!"

As Summer Night Flower saw more and more sarcastic replies, his mood became terrible, and he decided not to read the replies anymore.

Summer Night Flower edited his post and added, "All of you will know who is right and who is wrong when the truth verifies my thoughts. At that time, it will be too late for all of you to regret!"

At the same time, another player called ‘Hate the Heavens’ also saw Summer Night Flower’s post.

Hate the Heavens had always felt that he was extremely good at spotting hidden storylines that no one knew about. He was also an avid reader of the post by Galaxy Chronicles and had even set up a small guild for players who enjoyed digging up hidden storylines.

When he saw the post, Hate the Heavens immediately felt that Summer Night Flower must be right.

The Main Storyline would not give them a meaningless faction, so there must be a hidden storyline in Klent!

Hate the Heavens made his decision and sent a link to Summer Night Flower’s post to all the members in his guild.

"All of you look at this post. I think that it is extremely logical, and I plan to join the Klent faction."

The guild immediately broke out into commotion.

"You must consider this matter carefully Guild Leader! You will be screwed if your guess is wrong!"

"I think that it makes sense. Guild Leader, count me in. This trip will definitely be interesting."

"Guild Leader, how are you planning to join them? I don’t think we have a path to join them, right?"

"I searched for some information, and there is a news report of Bloodshed Land hiring soldiers in Colton," Hate the Heavens replied. "I think that there will be a chance to join the enemy if we go to the frontline stronghold of the enemy alone. We can make use of this opportunity to change factions."

"This can be considered betrayal, right? We won’t be able to return to the army again in future," another person added.

"So what if we can’t return? Bloodshed Land is a large faction, and it may not be any worse than the Black Star Army. Furthermore, we may have the chance to come in contact with the Crimson Dynasty in the future," Hate the Heavens replied indifferently.

ren

"All of these are guesses. Guesses can be

wrong."

"I feel that it can’t be wrong." Hate the Heavens shook his head. "Besides, with so many players being in the Black Star Army faction, we will know about any developments in the army. However, no one has triggered the hidden storyline in the Klent faction, and I want to play a storyline that no one knows about…"

"But the benefits of the Black Star Army are so

good…"

"Haha, I am not a professional player. Why do I need to be so powerful?" Hate the Heavens replied with loud laughter.

He was a player who craved satisfaction, and the allure of a fresh storyline was far greater than benefits. Among the players, there were plenty who felt the same.

Summer Night Flower’s post did have some effect. Apart from those who replied with sarcasm, there were some who began considering his words and grew curious about the Klent faction.

There were a small portion of players who were like Hate the Heavens and sought a fresh storyline, but the majority were gambling on the benefits that the Klent faction could bring to them.

Two days passed in the blink of an eye.

It was the day to go out for battle, and all the manpower had been gathered up. A large fleet was awaiting orders in the military dock of the headquarters.

More than a million players formed a special fleet and waited on-board the battleships with excitement.

They were no longer strangers to these large-scale missions, but most of them still felt excited whenever they participated in a mission that involved more than a million players.

As a faction that had gathered all the players together, such missions gave them a sense of belonging, and they felt as though they had a mission on their shoulders.

All the members participating in the battle waited in their respective battleships with Lagi’s face being displayed on the screen of all the battleships. He was currently briefing all the participants of the mission. This should have been the job of the faction leader, but Han Xiao felt that Lagi was a demonic talent when it came to boosting the morale of the troops and thus allowed him to take this job.

As such, everyone had no choice but to listen to Lagi’s monotonic voice.

"We will all die eventually, and the difference is only whether we die today or tomorrow…"

-20 Morale.

"Regardless of whether we are powerful or weak, we cannot avoid death. Being alive is only a process of rotting away slowly. Everything you do is meaningless to the universe, including this battle. Regardless of victory or defeat, it has nothing to do with all of you…"

-40 Morale.

"However, even if we know that the outcome cannot be changed, we will still continue to work hard. Even if we know that life is more important than everything else, there will be some who take risks. Even if we know that we are no more than a small chess piece in the war who will be reduced to dust by the various weapons, we are still willing to fight… Why is this?"

The morale slowly rose back up.

"It’s because of money!"

The morale instantly went back to zero!

"We will only be able to enjoy life with money. We will not have to bend our backs to others if we have money. We will be able to take care of all our problems easily with money! We are warriors, and fighting is the way for us to earn money. Do you lack money? Then pick up your weapon and slaughter the enemy. A war is the best opportunity for us to earn money. Every single enemy has a price on their head, and your earnings shall be determined by the number of enemies you kill!"

A special effect has been triggered: +80 Morale.

Any righteous slogan would only make the members of the army sneer in disdain. After all, the secret war was a battle of benefits between Klent and Purple Crystal. They had nothing to do with the war but chose to participate in it for money. As such, the best way to stir the army would be to tell them the truth and let them know how much money their enemy was worth.

All the players looked at each other with dumbfounded expressions on their faces. They had thought that they would be listening to an inspiring speech but never expected it to be such a pragmatic one.

Black Star, you have changed.

But we like it!

Han Xiao stifled his laughter and hurriedly kicked Lagi away, who wanted to add something. If he allowed Lagi to speak freely without following the script, the morale of the army would definitely vanish.

Han Xiao coughed dryly and added, "Set off."

Boom!

The next moment, the surface of the Black Star Army’s satellite headquarters opened, and a large catapult rail was revealed. Thousands of battleships took off from the catapult rail and formed neat rows outside the atmosphere of the headquarters.

The fleet entered hyperdrive at the same moment and transformed into rays of light disappearing into the universe.

If the pedestrians on Planet Golden Gate stopped what they were doing and looked up, they would be able to see thousands of shooting-star-like objects disappearing into the horizon.

On Planet Heber, the Bloodshed Land headquarters…

"Your Excellency Tyrant, intelligence from the frontlines reported Section Zero sending out all of their forces. Their target is the Kant Star System, and Black Star has personally set off," Jorde reported to Heber respectfully. "I have arranged for the forces from other Star Systems to reinforce them."

"Mhm." Heber’s soft murmur indicated that he had heard the report before asking, "Has Black Star grown up yet?"

Jorde hurriedly replied, "It has been a full seven years, and Black Star’s strength has not changed up until now."

Talking about this, Jorde could not help but heave a sigh of relief. Back then, Black Star’s fame was peerless, and it was as though he could become a Beyond Grade A Super anytime. However, seven years had gone by, and Black Star had not achieved a breakthrough. His fame was no longer as high as before, and some organizations no longer paid close attention to him.

Every Beyond Grade A seed was a genius, but they would always become ordinary after a brief commotion. It turned out that Black Star was no different from the other Beyond Grade A seeds.

Heber shook his head with a tinge of disappointment.

He had been waiting for Han Xiao to grow up and wanted to kill Han Xiao after he became a Beyond Grade A Super. Only then would he have a battle record of killing a Beyond Grade A Super to allow his prestige to increase another level.

Seven years ago, news of Klent working together with EsGod had soured relationships between Bloodshed Land and Klent. However, both parties were allies and fought for their own benefits. Thus, this little conflict did not affect the plan for Bloodshed Land to fight on behalf of Klent.

"I overestimated him." Heber felt that it was a pity. With his status, there would not be any benefits for him killing a Beyond Grade A seed.

Jorde could not help but ask, "Your Excellency Tyrant, Black Star has not shown any progress over the past seven years. Will he suddenly achieve a breakthrough and become a Beyond Grade A Super?"

Heber looked at him and slowly explained, "Before the appearance of the Primordial Ones, Calamity Grade Supers were the most powerful beings in the universe. This went on for many years, and many generations of geniuses weren’t able to touch the door frame of becoming a Beyond Grade A Super. The barrier to becoming a Beyond Grade A Super won’t be broken so easily. Compared to talent, luck seems to be more important. After all, one will become an entirely new organism after becoming a Beyond Grade A Super…"

This was not the first time that Jorde had heard that a Beyond Grade A Super was a completely new organism. Just where did the huge chasm between the Calamity Grade and Beyond Grade A come from?

However, Tyrant did not wish to tell him, and Jorde could only suppress the curiosity in his heart. "Does Black Star have a chance to become a Beyond Grade A Super?"

"Hmm, perhaps after a few decades of exploration," Heber said with a deep voice. "However, Klent’s plan will be completed in a few years’ time, and the war will be over soon At that time, Black Star will die by hand, so he won’t have the opportunity to live that long."

Heber’s patience was limited, and he would only give Black Star until the end of the war to become a Beyond Grade A Super.

After the war ended, there would not be anything to restrict a Beyond Grade A Super from taking action. At that time, even if Black Star was only at the Calamity Grade, he would personally kill Black Star. Black Star had to pay the price for killing his officers.

Chapter 723: Money Is the Most Terrifying Weapon

In the Kant Star System, a gigantic fleet was currently hovering around a space filled with nothingness. The size of this fleet was comparable to the elite forces of Klent or Purple Crystal. Two large flagships that were a few dozen kilometers long were located at the core of the fleet with the military technology of Purple Crystal being built into it. Its exterior was covered in a dark purple prism crystal, looking as though it was an artificially carved purple diamond. Energy veins that flickered with a bluish-gold color ran through the crystal, and these energy veins transmitted psionic energy to the entire ship like the veins of a human body. These veins granted the flagship an extremely powerful defense and also gave it the ability to shoot out compressed psionic blasts from any corner of the vessel.

It was a Star Diamond Grade Flagship, Purple Crystal’s flagship model. With the Gemini Star as the furnace, a special mineral from the Purple Crystal Civilization called ‘Dark Stream Crystal’ was used to forge this super flagship. It was made from military warehouse no. 3 of the Purple Crystal Civilization and was a war machine for Section Zero.

Every time he saw these two gigantic flagships, Han Xiao would drool over them. This flagship was the epitome of Purple Crystal’s technological skill, but it was a pity that it was not for sale. Furthermore, Purple Crystal’s technological skills leaned toward crystal magic and inscription magi, which was not compatible with him.

After a long distance hyperdrive, Han Xiao brought the Black Star Army fleet to the gathering point. There were already millions of battleships awaiting their orders, and they were the fleets of the various members from Section Zero. After ten years of war, Purple Crystal invested a large amount of resources and used their military factories to support Section Zero. As such, the fleet of every Section Zero member had grown greatly.

The flagship of the Black Star Army was a spherical satellite base. Han Xiao gave the flagship a name befitting its appearance, Model Marble. This was an armed satellite fortress that Han Xiao had personally modified. Its size was smaller and had a higher mobility and combat capability. It had the more stable dark energy furnace as its core, and its cost was within a reasonable range. According to Han Xiao’s estimation, it should be comparable to an ordinary flagship model of a Galactic Civilization.

The blueprint of this flagship came from a Bloodshed Land armed satellite fortress. Han Xiao created multiple versions of the fortress and completely embraced the idea of copying and plagiarism. After all, Han Xiao had chosen the path of Virtual Technology, so he was not able to gamble for the blueprints of gigantic machinery. Thus, making a copy of an existing machine was much easier to him.

Psionic energy was still far too dangerous, so Han Xiao only dared make use of psionic energy when forging high-grade weapons. When forging such a large fortress, Han Xiao had chosen to use a more stable source of energy. Dark energy existed all around the universe, and it belonged to the category of [Abnormal State Energy).

All the leaders of the participating organizations were gathered into a Star Diamond Grade Flagship called ‘Everlasting’ for a meeting. As the leader of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao naturally needed to attend the meeting. He was currently in a conference room that had more than a hundred individuals present listening to the commander from Purple Crystal nagging endlessly.

A map of the various Bloodshed Land strongholds in the Kant Star System was displayed on the holographic screen, and every Hyperdrive Base Station was connected to three to fourteen different planets. An efficient reinforcement system was formed, and Bloodshed Land had a total of eleven strongholds in the Kant Star System. They formed a fan-like formation with the first Bloodshed Land stronghold near the border as the core.

The enemy’s fan-shaped territory could be split into three different layers: six weaker strongholds at the outer rim, four strongholds to slow down the enemy in the middle, and the bridgehead, which was the very first stronghold of Bloodshed Land in the Star System. The objective of this large-scale invasion was to purge all the enemies from outside to inside.

"According to our intelligence, Bloodshed Land has found out about our operation and raised their level of defense. We will be facing a head on battle…"

Han Xiao did not pay too much attention to the meeting. He had already obtained all this intelligence from Ralph and was currently looking around at the people around him to kill time.

Of the many leaders present, the most powerful few were the leaders of the Arc Light Organization, Hero Group, New Phylen Rebels, and so on. They had once been the trump card force of Section Zero, but their position had been replaced with the Black Star Army.

At this moment, the commander said, "Bloodshed Land mobilized some reinforcements, and Hadavy will be joining this battle. Your Excellency Black Star, we will need to rely on you on our side."

Han Xiao nodded in response, and the other leaders nodded to him in response.

He was the most powerful individual in Section Zero and would always deal with the most powerful enemy. Among all the high-level combatants, all the organizations there relied on him to deal with the most troublesome enemy. This was also the reason for the Black Star Army’s status in Section Zero.

"According to the intelligence, Hadavy and his reinforcements will be guarding the innermost bridgehead. They are currently constructing various large-scale defensive measures and plan to use their strongholds on the outer rim to slow down our progress…"

"Can’t we attack the enemy’s bridgehead directly?" one of the leaders asked.

The commander replied with a deep voice, "The border of the Kant Star System is connected to Kaya, and Bloodshed Land’s stronghold is located right behind the bridgehead of Kant. If we attack the bridgehead directly, we will have to face enemies from both the Kaya Star System and the other strongholds located in the Kant Star System. Thus, we will face less pressure if we choose to attack from the outside.

"Because of the lack of time, we have to uproot all the strongholds located on the outer rim as quickly as possible. The enemy forces located on the outer rim are the weakest, and we have an absolute advantage in terms of strength. We will split our forces into six and attack six different strongholds at once. The forces shall be split as follows…"

Han Xiao realized that the Black Star Army was assigned to lead a few different organizations to attack a weaker stronghold. An idea then came to his mind.

"I have a suggestion."

"Please speak," the commander said with a respectful tone.

Han Xiao pointed at the star map and said, "The smallest stronghold is only connected to three different planets, and it would be too troublesome to send an entire fleet over. Leave them to the Black Star Army. I will uproot them completely."

The commander hesitated for a moment before nodding. "Alright then, I shall withdraw those forces."

He had plenty of trust in Han Xiao’s strength. However, a mere three planets without a single Calamity Grade Super could be easily taken care of by Black Star alone. The enemy did not arrange for any experts in the outer rim, and it was truly a waste of resources to send a powerhouse like Black Star.

"Then the reward…"

"Don’t worry, you will definitely be satisfied." The commander nodded. Purple Crystal definitely would not be stingy if the Black Star Army took on an extra mission.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "I don’t need too much. I just want 7,000 tons of Dark Stream Crystal and 2,000 tons of string alloy."

am

Rare materials could be used to create plenty of elite mechanical soldiers, and compared to money, Han Xiao preferred to receive his payment in materials.

"I will report this to my higher ups." The commander’s lips contorted slightly.

Returning to the Black Star flagship, Han Xiao called the fleet commander, Herlous, over and indicated his intention to split up his forces.

Lagi would lead the majority of their forces and join the main fleet while Han Xiao would lead a small bunch to attack the smallest stronghold.

"You want to lead them?" Herlous asked with doubt. "You can destroy the three planets single handedly, right?"

"I plan to bring Marian, Sylvia, and a portion of the undying force. I mainly want to train them." Han Xiao shrugged.

"Alright then." Herlous nodded.

"I also have something else to add. For the undying troops that I don’t take with me, I want you to send them to the most dangerous part of the battlefield. I want you to throw all the jobs with risks over to them."

Herlous rubbed his head and said, "I understand. I’ll have them follow Harmon."

After giving some instructions to Herlous, Han Xiao then issued a mission to the players through the interface. He indicated that the army would be split into two, and he would be taking 300,000 players with him.

Through the faction interface, the 300,000 spots were filled up in less than three minutes. Han Xiao then mobilized more than a hundred battleships and took Sylvia, Marian, and the 300,000 excited players to their destination.

Han Xiao’s objective of this operation was to fatten the players up and allow them to earn as much experience as possible. Thus, he was willing to participate in more operations.

Apart from the Main Storyline Mission, Han Xiao was prepared to use up the daily Faction Reward Quota to give the players experience.

On planet number K-00156 was one of the Bloodshed Land strongholds in the Kant Star System. This was a new stronghold that had not been completely overhauled. Grayish metal covered the surface of the planet, and more than a thousand battleships were patrolling the atmosphere of the planet to keep it safe.

Over a hundred rays of light suddenly sliced through the dark space and exited hyperdrive. They exited hyperdrive not too far away from planet K-00156, and Han Xiao led his forces over without stopping.

300,000 players looked at the planet through the windows of the battleships excitedly.

"This is our target, right?"

"Is it finally going to begin? I can’t hold back my excitement any longer."

"Have you guys triggered the war mission? My mission is to destroy this planet’s stronghold. Are all of your missions the same?"

All the players obtained a subsidiary mission through the Main Storyline Mission that required them to destroy the stronghold on planet K-00156.

Frenzied Sword and a portion of the professional players took part in this mission as well. Maple Moon also followed along, and there was not even a need to mention Bun-Hit-Dog; he would follow Black Star wherever he went.

Right at this moment, an orange alert light went off in all the battleships, and Phillip’s voice sounded.

"All forces, proceed to the charge cabin and prepare to launch. Check the durability of the armor and life support system of the charge cabin. We will be entering the atmosphere of planet K-00156. We will land on the surface. Kill all enemies who fight back and destroy the base on the surface of the planet. I repeat. All forces…"

All the players heard the order and entered the charge cabins with their comrades. However, Maple Moon looked outside the window with hesitation on her face.

The Defense Team of planet K-00156 had already detected the approaching troops and were currently about to surround them. The enemy had over a thousand battleships, a full ten times their size. They were like sheep being surrounded by wolves, and it would be impossible for them to break out from the enemy’s encirclement. How were they supposed to be launched onto the planet?

Maple Moon was much more observant toward such details.

"What are you waiting for? Let’s go." By the side, Bun-Hit-Dog pushed her along, and Frenzied Sword also began to rush her.

"Wait." Maple Moon took out her communicator and summoned Phillip. "The enemy battleships are about to surround us. How are we going to deal with them? If our battleships are destroyed, all of us will be sucked into the universe."

"This isn’t something for you to worry about," Phillip replied mechanically. "The enemy fleet will not cause us any trouble, hum…"

Maple Moon wanted to continue asking, but Bun-Hit-Dog who was beside her suddenly let out a gasp. "Look outside, Black Star has met the enemy force alone!"

As the people in the surroundings heard that, they all stopped moving and looked outside the window curiously. Maple Moon also looked up, and Frenzied Sword ran back to look outside the window.

Han Xiao exited the battleship alone and faced thousands of enemy battleships.

The enemy had also locked onto him and opened fire immediately.

All the players in the spaceships could not help but grow anxious. In the previous version, Black Star had not displayed an overwhelming prowess in the universe. While they knew that Black Star would definitely have become stronger in the new version, this was the first time witnessing Black Star take action in this version. None of them were clear about Black Star’s strength.

This was the firepower of over a thousand battleships!

Would he be able to block them?

Just when everyone was feeling nervous, Han Xiao’s hands turned into claws, and as though he treated the space around him as a piece of cloth, he tugged down on it firmly. The space around him contorted, and the endless wave of cannon fire was immediately dispersed in every other direction, flying past his body.

Shortly after, ripples could be seen in the space around him, and his army boxes appeared behind him in an orderly formation.

Frenzied Sword did a quick count of the number of Army Boxes, and there were 121!

The next moment, all the Army Boxes were opened up, and as though Pandora’s box was opened, a never ending wave of black machines swarmed out. Millions of energy blasts were launched, and the energy blasts swallowed half of the enemy fleet.

Hundreds of enemy battleships were immediately torn apart by the energy blasts and reduced to fireworks in the dark universe.

In a single instant, half of the enemy fleet was wiped out!

Even though this frightening wave of machinery was charging toward the enemy, the players on-board the spaceships could not help but take in a deep breath.

In the past seven years, Han Xiao did not have much experience to level up and thus focused his attention on his mechanical army. Currently, the size of his mechanical army was already in the millions, and he had forged a new artificial intelligence to deal with the calculations in battle. Phillip would then focus completely on being a butler.

"Alert, detecting a large energy spike! Alert! Alert!" An alarm went off in the spaceship.

All of a sudden, the surface of planet K-00156 began to tremble with a huge energy wave being released. The window of the spaceship adjusted itself automatically, and the view on the window seemed to be zoomed out. A large Anti Air Railgun that was used to deal with enemy flagships appeared from the surface of planet K-00156, and a brilliant purple light began charging up in the barrel of the railgun.

Han Xiao’s attention was also attracted by the railgun, and he threw out a compressed orb, which rapidly opened to become an Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon. An even more frightening energy reaction emanated from the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon, and an ice blue pillar of light shot out from the barrel of the cannon, accurately striking the Anti Air Railgun on the surface of the planet.

Everyone aboard the spaceships could clearly see the outcome of this shot. A large ice crater was left behind on the surface of the planet with frost covering the surroundings of the railgun. Tens of kilometers of land was covered in frost, and the frost was still spreading.

While they could not hear the commotion from that attack, all the players felt a chill run down their spine.

If this attack landed on an ordinary colonial planet… perhaps a single cannon would be able to destroy an entire city.

Just when everyone was still in a daze, Han Xiao suddenly weaved through the enemy vessels and appeared beside the enemy’s flagship. He immediately activated Machinery Apostilization, and the eyes of his mechanical suit lit up with a bright blue color. This was an indication of the energy within his body being extremely abundant.

Han Xiao placed his palm on the electromagnetic shield, and through the psionic energy being emanated by his body, the electromagnetic shield was dyed blue in color. With a few flashes, it shattered like a piece of glass, and Han Xiao proceeded unobstructed to the outer armor of the flagship. His hands turned into claws, and he embedded them deep within the armor of the flagship.

A never-ending flow of psionic energy infiltrated the enemy flagship through his ten fingers. With Han Xiao’s palm as the center, the psionic energy spread out to the exterior armor of the flagship like energy veins.

The entire flagship lit up like shattered porcelain pieces, and when the light became blinding, the entire flagship exploded with bright blue flames. The flames rapidly consumed the oxygen within the flagship and were extinguished in an instant.

At the same time, Han Xiao’s mechanical army had already destroyed the entire enemy fleet and returned to the Army Boxes like birds returning to their nest. Only the remains of destroyed battleships were left floating about in space.

The battle had ended in less than five minutes. For an expert of his realm, as long as there were no Supers of the same level to restrict him, destroying an entire fleet was a piece of cake to him.

The sound of Phillip’s cheers could then be heard in the spaceships.

"His Excellency Black Star has cleared all obstacles. All forces prepare to launch in three minutes. I repeat. His Excellency…’

All the players could not help but gulp in shock.

Was this the world of the powerful?

Too awesome!

Chapter 724: Fertilizer

Fighting an entire fleet with the strength of an individual. All the players were completely entranced by the sight before them.

The last time they had witnessed Han Xiao taking action, he did not have such overwhelming strength. It seemed like many things had changed greatly over the past ten years…

Frenzied Sword had a strange feeling in his heart. It was as though he had been through many good and bad times with Han Xiao.

Bun-Hit-Dog’s eyes lit up, and he immediately interviewed Frenzied Sword. "Hey, didn’t you say that our strength would slowly be unlocked with the release of new versions? Does this mean that we will be able to destroy fleets in future? This is too interesting!"

"We should be able to…" Frenzied Sword was not too sure. He felt that as long as the level of strength in the galaxy did not change, their growth in strength would influence the way NPCs viewed them. With this game’s world being extremely open and free to possibilities, perhaps they would truly be able to attain a strength that could rival Black Star.

Maple Moon looked as though she was deep in thought by the side. She felt that the effect of the players leveling up should not be limited to an increase in their PVP abilities.

This small interlude did not affect the progress of the spaceships. The hundred or so spaceships approached planet K-00156, and the AI system began the countdown for their launch.

Under Phillip’s pestering, all 300,000 players boarded the launch pods and were ready for launch.

One after another, the space chargers shot out from the spaceships, and all the players took out their weapons while awaiting touchdown. Even the Espers and Pugilists would also have firearms as weapons.

Maple Moon frowned and suddenly thought about something.

"Since Black Star destroyed the enemy’s fleet, why do we still have to be sent down to the planet? Can’t we just shoot at them from outside the atmosphere?"

Everyone was stunned for a moment, but before they had the time to react, the launch pods trembled, and everyone felt their bodies becoming weightless.

Boom!

Han Xiao floated beside the fleet and looked down on the planet from above. The numerous space pods were like burning meteors raining down on the planet.

Han Xiao then zoomed in on the surface of the planet. An endless stream of players exited the launch pods and flooded the planet like a huge wave. This stronghold had many different bases with the sergeants of the Bloodshed Land leading their troops out to fight off the players. The strongest enemy fighter was only at Grade B, and under the fearless assault of the players, the enemy was forced back slowly.

"Not bad. I should be able to earn a large amount of experience this time." Han Xiao did not have any intention of helping and sat cross legged outside the atmosphere to watch the battle.

Han Xiao had volunteered to attack the smallest Bloodshed Land stronghold so that the Hyperdrive Base Station and the three planets that it was connected to would become the player’s fertilizer.

Apart from the war and faction mission, all the Bloodshed Land warriors on the surface of the planet were also like walking bags of experience. As long as they were killed, the players would be able to gain plenty of experience.

With his level, getting rid of these useless soldiers would only give him one experience point. On the other hand, the players’ levels were low, and thus, they would receive plenty of bonus experience from killing the enemies. Han Xiao would then harvest the experience points from the players, and a beautiful production line would be formed. It was just like the principal of feeding a chicken to lay an egg.

The strength of the players is growing, and they will slowly walk up to a larger stage and display their prominence in the various organizations.

In his previous life, as the players’ strength increased and they began to roam the galaxy, many powerful galactic organizations paid close attention to the players. In the later versions during his previous life, the players had received a resounding nickname.

Cancer of the Universe!

Han Xiao had always felt that the nickname was extremely cool and fitting.

The players were still far from that standard. Only when the first few waves of players became Grade B would it be the time for the players to rise.

As the farmer who was prepared to let the name of his crops shine far and wide, Han Xiao knew that his responsibility was heavy.

"Your Excellency Black Star, are we going to help?"

Just when Han Xiao was deep in thought, Marian who was clad in heavy armor flew to Han Xiao’s side and asked if they should reinforce the ground troops.

He was one of the three Calamity Grade Supers who had joined the Black Star Army seven years ago. He was a powerful Mechanical Pugilist who did not talk much, with his focus being set on raising his strength. He could still be considered loyal and had gained Han Xiao’s trust over time.

"It isn’t necessary. I am training the soldiers, and both of you have something else to do." Han Xiao waved his hands.

Marian nodded in reply.

"With this planet being attacked, the Hyperdrive Base Station will definitely send reinforcements very quickly. I want the both of you to attack the Hyperdrive Base Station before the reinforcements arrive. I want you to then send me over to the two other planets through the wormhole of the Hyperdrive Base Station. I will destroy their flying equipment before sending our forces over to clear up their nests," Han Xiao said.

He wanted to turn the ground troops on the three strongholds into lambs waiting to be slaughtered. He would destroy all their methods to escape and trap them all on the planet. Not a single person would be allowed to escape, and they would all become fertilizers for his crops.

Han Xiao wanted to add something on but suddenly detected fluctuations in space. With a chuckle, he said, "My prediction is spot on indeed. Both of you prepare yourselves. Someone is here to seek death."

The moment his voice sounded, a whirlpool-like wormhole opened outside the atmosphere of planet K-00156 and spat out battleship after battleship.

Without saying a word, Sylvia revved up the output of her mechanical suit and transformed into a beam of light. She nimbly avoided all the incoming laser beams and charged straight into the wormhole.

Marian followed closely behind her, but his performance was far more boorish. He activated dozens of shields and charged straight into the wormhole while tanking all the cannon fire. Along the way, he had even crashed straight through two small assault ships.

Both of them were Mechanical Pugilists, and their mechanical suits had personally been fine-tuned by Han Xiao. Together with their Calamity Grade strength, they were more than sufficient to take care of a Hyperdrive Base Station without any high-level combatants. Furthermore, both of their mechanical suits were equipped with Phillip’s child program and could extend the range of his virtual intrusion. When both of them arrived, he would be able to assist them from afar in infiltrating the base.

The reinforcing battleships appeared without ending with their guns blazing. Han Xiao remained cross legged, and his new and improved eleventh generation Watcher Instrument defended him automatically. A total of 361 bluish-gold orbs floated around him to form a thick psionic shield that deflected all the enemies’ attacks.

"Let me play with you guys for a bit since I am not pushed for time."

Han Xiao chuckled. With a single thought, a terrifying amount of data assaulted the artificial intelligence system of the battleships. In the blink of an eye, the firewalls of these battleships were completely riddled with holes, and their calculation modules became unstable.

After multiple Class Advancements, his Virtual Technology skill had already entered a new realm, and his speed was completely different from the past. Furthermore, he had obtained a new Cutting-Edge Knowledge, (Quantum Network Matrix), from Purple Crystal, which multiplied the amount of data he could send. His infiltration technique went through a revolutionary change, and Han Xiao was currently capable of directly connecting to a quantum network.

As long as the enemy was within range, he would be able to generate a storm of data with a single thought, and his infiltration ability was extremely powerful. This was the flagship skill of a Virtual Mechanic.

Han Xiao had already grown to be extremely powerful in all areas. Although he had yet to reach Beyond Grade A, he could already be considered a powerhouse in the galaxy.

A Virtual Mechanic was a huge killing machine in a galactic battle. Even if Han Xiao did not make use of his mechanical army, he would be able to easily deal with a small fleet. As he infiltrated the enemy ships to throw the enemy into a mess, Han Xiao sent out his elite mechanical army to board the enemy ships and kill all their crew. Since he was not in a hurry, Han Xiao decided to minimize the destruction and capture all these battleships.

Han Xiao had plenty of strength to spare and diverted part of his attention to the players.

On planet K-00156, one of the bases was currently a bitter battlefield.

Boom boom boom!

Frenzied Sword’s large caliber rifle punctured a hole in the body of a Thousand Beast Soldier. The corpse of the soldier fell toward him, and Frenzied Sword kicked it away before raising his arm to activate a shield. A series of gun fire immediately rained down on his shield, and Frenzied Sword began to calculate the durability of his shield. He then charged forward into the midst of an enemy five-man team. Whipping out his electromagnetic whip and helix blade, he killed the five-man team after a short battle.

Taking in a deep breath, he looked around his surroundings. They were currently in the Hub Center of the base, and the main hall was currently a messy battlefield. Both parties exchanged fire with dead soldiers lying all around the hall. The players transformed into white light after reviving and did not leave any corpse behind. Thus, the situation looked like a one-sided massacre as though a swarm of locusts had just swept by.

The players formed small parties and worked together. Their screams could be heard amid the cannon fire.

"Pull the enemies, back row output damage!"

"Hang in there, main tank. Inject yourself with life sustaining hormones. Second and third tanks, prepare to switch out!"

"Mechanics, quickly set up your artillery towers!"

"Hahaha, we’re rich! A single Thousand Beast Soldier actually gives us so much experience. What the f\*ck? Who is the one who stole this daddy’s kill!"

The Esper class players unleashed their various skills, and all the different kinds of energy blasts bombarded the enemy into retreat. The players had the numerical advantage with their individual combat abilities reaching an acceptable standard. They were all Grade C at least with an extremely small portion of them having reached Grade B with their accumulated experience from the previous version. They still had their biggest trump card: reviving!

With such an army, there was no need to bother sending scouts, sneak attacks, ambushes, or any complicated combat maneuvers. They just needed to use human wave tactics.

Frenzied Sword charged past the defensive line and entered the walkway of the base. Although the mission only required them to occupy the base, Frenzied Sword was extremely experienced and knew that killing the base commander would definitely raise his mission rating. Thus, he ignored all the other soldiers and searched for the base commander.

There were definitely other players who had the same thought as him, and Frenzied Sword did not dare delay.

At the same time, the base commander was currently watching the situation of the battle from the surveillance equipment in the base. He knew that their defeat was imminent, and his legs could not help but tremble.

"This is Black Star Army’s immortal troops!"

The commander’s voice trembled with fear gripping his heart. Everyone from Bloodshed Land had looked through Black Star Army’s information before and knew that the immortal troops were the true hidden trump card of the Black Star Army. After disappearing for a full ten years, they had made their appearance again!

Hopelessness filled his heart, and he witnessed the most frightening aspect of the immortal troops from the screen. They were all extremely bloodthirsty and would never leave anyone alive. In a short while, the entire base would be soaked in blood, and all their spaceships had already been destroyed by Black Star. They no longer had any chance to escape.

"Where are the reinforcements?" The base commander still held on to the last bit of hope in his heart.

"We tried to contact them seventeen times, but we did not receive any response. We lost all contact with the reinforcements, and they were probably…" The intelligence staff had a face full of fear.

The base commander fell into complete despair. They no longer had a way out and could only wait for their deaths to arrive.

"Why don’t we surr…"

Boom!

Before he could even finish, the door was suddenly blasted open, and Frenzied Sword appeared from the large cloud of dust. Without any hesitation, he switched to a close ranged weapon and waved his axe around to slaughter anyone in sight.

"Wait a moment. I am the commander of this stronghold. I surrender!"

The approaching axe had truly frightened the base commander out of his wits, and he hurriedly knelt down to beg for mercy.

The axe stopped ten centimeters away from the commander’s head, and the base commander felt his entire body turning soft. Frenzied Sword then looked at him with doubt.

"You are the commander?".

"I am!"

"You’re surrendering?"

"That’s right! That’s right!"

Frenzied Sword paused for a while before suddenly letting out a battle cry and swinging his axe down mercilessly to cleave the commander before him in two.

His axe was instantly stained with bright blue blood, and Frenzied Sword shook his head.

"What’s the point of keeping you if your surrender doesn’t trigger a mission? Eh? Killing a commander actually gives so much experience!"

Frenzied Sword had a bright smile on his face as he left the room, leaving behind a dismembered corpse and bloodstains all over the walls.

At the same time in the interior of the Hyperdrive Base Station, a long sword was being dragged by a slender hand. Reddish-gold bolts of energy could be seen coursing through the body of the sword, and the tip of the sword created a deep scar on the surface of the alloy floor.

This was an alloy walkway with Bloodshed Land soldiers both in front and behind. They were trying their best to push back the beautiful lady in the middle, but all of their firepower was easily blocked by the protective shield of her mechanical suit.

Sylvia completely ignored the army that was surrounding her and looked at Marian, who was currently destroying the enemy ships outside. He was smashing his body through all the spaceships and having the time of his life.

"Hurry up and take down the base. Don’t keep Teacher waiting too long," Sylvia muttered under her breath. Holding onto the sword with both her hands, her body began spinning.

Marian, who was currently fighting the enemy spaceships in space, could clearly see a reddish-gold circle burst forth from the interior of the Hyperdrive Base Station, cutting the entire base in two and slicing off a fifth of the base cleanly.

"Why are you even more violent than me? You’d better not destroy the base. We still need to use it later," Marian said helplessly.

Outside the atmosphere of K-00156, Han Xiao floated in space and waited silently. Over half of the enemy battleships had already been captured by him.

Right at this moment, a wormhole channel opened again with the other side of the channel being the second planet. The remaining defending battleships were clustered together as though they were screaming out, AHH! Don’t come near me!

A bright smile could be seen on Han Xiao’s face.

Not a single bag of the three fertilizers could be missed.

"Sylvia succeeded so quickly. It seems like I taught her well."

Chapter 725: Hidden Scheme

Because Sylvia had managed to seize the enemy’s Hyperdrive Base Station, Han Xiao quickly utilized the wormhole of the enemy side to attack the last two planetary strongholds.

With the fall of their Hyperdrive Base Station, the remaining two strongholds knew that their troops were not a match and wanted to retreat. However, Han Xiao was too fast for them, and the enemy did not even have the time to move their supplies before they were attacked. The second planet’s fleet was completely annihilated, while the fleet for the third planet left their troops on the surface, choosing to turn tail and run instead.

Having lost their means of transportation, the ground troops of the two strongholds turned into trapped beasts and could only watch as the airdrop capsules rained down on them, as the screaming immortal players rushed out like a tsunami, bringing with them blood and slaughter.

Small and new strongholds like these would not have many strong Supers, which was suitable for the players’ standards. Once in a while, there would be a Grade B Super, which could be regarded as a Boss monster. In general, clearing the stronghold went smoothly.

It did not take Han Xiao very long to wash the three strongholds with blood, using the 300,000 players. No one from the enemy side lived, the players taking all their heads. In addition to the reward provided by the battle war mission as well as the faction reward, the players obtained a huge sum of experience, leaving them satisfied.

The rest of the personnel in the Hyperdrive Base Station were also cleaned up by Han Xiao, and only the logistics department were left behind to take the supplies left behind on the battlefield.

This base station could be considered to have been successfully thrashed. Han Xiao then contacted Herlous, enquiring about the status of the Black Star Army with the objective of checking on the status of the players there.

The Black Star Army, under the leadership of Herlous and Lagi, had attacked a stronger base station. The millions of players were scattered around, attacking the six planet strongholds as they conducted ground battles through airdrops. The team with the most people was led by Harmon.

Han Xiao brought up the battlefield imagery, revealing an expanse of a desolate battlefield. Harmon was rushing at the front, full of energy and his fur bristling around his burly body as he concentrated fire on one of the enemy’s ground vehicles. He wielded his war hammer, killing one enemy after another. At his position, the tens of thousands of beast soldiers hung around him, weaving in and out with affecting his battle.

A large number of players were also cooperating with him to fight, but because Harmon’s burning spirit always resulted in him running to the area where gunfire was the most concentrated, the players behind him also received the most damage.

While Harmon’s behavior frazzled the players, following behind him was a good way to get kills. This was enjoyable yet mind numbing.

However, the treatment of the majority of these players was not as good as how Han Xiao treated his 300,000. After all, they did not have that many people reserved to kill, so their final gains would not be as lucrative. However, based on the current level of all the players, the reward could still be counted as generous.

"There are a few more battles coming up. It should be enough to allow everyone to level up a few times."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

Version 3.0 had begun less than half a month earlier, and excluding those who progressed quickly to reach Grade B, the average players’ level was around 93. The moment they reached level 100 and underwent their promotion to Grade B, the combat capability of the player teams would change qualitatively.

In the beginning of the Version, due to the increase in mission rewards, the players would be able to progress swifter as well. It should not be too difficult to reach level 100 in the short term.

Sylvia and Marian returned after accomplishing their task, and Han Xiao praised them for their efficiency.

It went without saying for Marian, who was always hardworking and reliable. As for Sylvia, after ten grueling years of training, she had finally turned into a powerful assistant that Han Xiao was looking for, able to hold her own.

"This is all thanks to the hard work put in by you, Teacher." In the cockpit, Sylvia let out a happy smile upon hearing Han Xiao’s praise.

She could still remember herself being blinded from the truth ten over years ago, and she had even tried to attack Han Xiao. But in the end, Han Xiao had led her down the correct path.

Sylvia was full of gratitude toward Han Xiao. While the ten-year child labor contract had long ended, she did not mention it at all. If it was not for Han Xiao’s guidance in those ten or so years, she did not know which galaxy she would still be lingering in, and she could not imagine how bad her life might have been.

Rather than saying that it was a slavery contract, Sylvia now felt that it was more of Han Xiao using it as an excuse to lead her down the right path. After being around him for over ten years, she looked up to Han Xiao like her adoptive father, and she did not wish to leave him right after being groomed properly.

"Continue working hard. You still have room for growth." Han Xiao nodded.

Because Sylvia had just broken through to the Calamity Grade, her strength was still on the weak side. However, with a full set of orange equipment from Han Xiao, she could unleash a higher level of strength. She herself also had the potential to grow even stronger.

Han Xiao let the entire team rest for a while before setting out to find the rest of the army to convene. Because there were a lot of people on Lagi’s side, he was reassured and did not rush to meet up with them.

When everyone rejoined, the battle had already ended, and they had also succeeded in destroying the base station. Everyone was now busy cleaning up the battlefield.

Intelligence reports continuously flowed in. The six stronghold bases of the Bloodshed Land within the Kant Star System had been completely cleared, and only some fish had managed to escape the net, falling back to the four base stations in their second layer.

Section Zero consolidated the entire team before aggressively advancing.

The next ten days showed that the speed of advancement for the team had slowed down. The base station systems of the enemy’s second layer were far more defensive compared to those in the periphery, and from time to time, they even received reinforcements from the rear, holding back the progress of Section Zero, albeit barely.

The fighting had continued unabated for the past half month, and players had gotten plenty of opportunities. They had adapted to the battle mission modes and rushed to the dangerous front lines, gaining a lot.

Cold-blooded, this was the impression that the player army left on the other members of Section Zero.

They did not accept surrender. Even enemies that showed no resistance would be killed, without a single one left alive.

All parties knew that Black Star commanded a unit of immortals, and they had finally resurfaced after a decade. Their role in this war was very obvious, making many of the forces quite envious.

Because the Black Star Army was growing ever stronger, many of the organizations had also gone to study the data of the immortals unit. According to their performance, it was projected by most organizations that these groups were a sort of Space Wonder derived from the Universe. While they were immortals, they would require a certain amount of energy to resurrect each time, and the number of resurrections was also finite in a certain time span.

While having hundreds of thousands of low-levelled Supers was not considered a lot in an interstellar war, the good point was that they would be continuously recycled. Every enemy died was one enemy less, but they would forever have a zero casualty rate, which was even better than the well-known special forces troops of the Universe, the Demon Lake, and Mechanic Empires.

In the eyes of the other organization, this group of immortals was the true trump card of the Black Star Army. Their abilities could be considered above the Thousand Beast Soldiers on the battlefield.

With the current status of the Black Star Army, they were naturally entitled to have their own special forces. Although many of the organizations were envious, they did not plan to provoke Black Star just for the immortals. Besides, apart from Han Xiao, no one else was aware that the players could still grow.

Han Xiao continued to lead his side, but he did not launch any more attacks personally for the next half a month. However, he alone could cause a thousand soldiers to retreat, causing the high-level combatants of the enemy to turtle up and not show themselves. This was all caused by Han Xiao’s fierce reputation of the many people he had killed in the past ten years. There were just too many Grade A Supers, and his name was a deterrence, causing ordinary Calamity Grades to not dare to face him.

In this battle, the only opponent worthy of him was Hadavy.

This Beyond Grade A seed was too difficult to fight against. Han Xiao had clashed against Hadavy thirteen times in the seven years, and while the battle results were all victories, Hadavy had good brains and was always able to run faster than anyone when the situation turned bad. Han Xiao had been unable to capture him up till this point and finally understood the feelings of his enemies.

Han Xiao estimated that he would only have an eighty percent chance of causing Hadavy to retreat this time. However, he did not mind that at all and was instead quite relaxed.

With the return of the players, his own level was already skyrocketing. When the time came, it would be easier for him to get rid of Hadavy. Thus, he was not worried at all.

Since the leader was lazing around, Lagi, as the high-level combatant, was sent out to lead the Black Star Army instead. Right now, Lagi was already firmly seated in the position of Vice Leader and was also a first-rate character in the eyes of the public. He could be considered the Captain of all the Mages in the Army.

While his pessimism was truly whack, Lagi’s battle prowess could not be denied. This former Forbidden Sorcerer commander lived up to his name, with vast mana and throwing around Forbidden spells like hurling garbage. His actual combat power placed him in the top ten of Section Zero.

After spending more than ten days breaking through the two base stations at the second layer, the personnel in the last two base stations took the initiative to retreat, all of them returning to their final base station at the core.

Originally, Bloodshed Land wanted to use the other base stations to stall for time and take advantage of the opportunity to arrange defense facilities. However, the offensive of Section Zero was too fierce, causing them to be unable to delay at all. They simply decided to save their fleet and assemble their forces, preparing for a final fight against Section Zero.

The last enemy base station on the Kant Star System was where all the retreating fleets had assembled. Together with a large amount of reinforcements, their military strength looked extremely robust. Section Zero formulated the corresponding tactics to deal with them, passing over the command to Han Xiao to contain the enemy’s advanced combatants, as well as to repel Hadavy.

The moment they started fighting, Han Xiao would not have time to care about the players any longer and thus arranged for his officers to brief the players properly.

At the same time, the officers of the last base station in the Kant Star System all gathered for a meeting, discussing on how to deal with the attack of Section Zero.

As a relay commander, Jorde also participated in the meeting through a virtual projection.

"We have a total of fourteen planetary bases as well as a transition base station. Whether the enemy sends a division or launches a total attack, there is a way to deal with it. While our fleets are much weaker, as long as we can endure for three days, the next batch of reinforcements will be able to arrive, and they will bring a teleportation gate with them."

"It is impossible for Section Zero to keep such a huge number of troops assembled all the time. Furthermore, our comrades in the other galaxies can also use this opportunity to further expand. The longer this is delayed, the more beneficial it is for us."

"There’s no need to fight to the death. We can always return to Kaya and wait for the Section Zero troops to disperse before we break through their blockade once again and return to Kant."

Everyone present expressed their opinions and their recommendations toward Jorde, as he was the final decision maker.

After listening to everyone, Jorde nodded and replied, "We have a plan for the general direction, but it is inevitable that we will have to fight. Now that the enemy has seized the initiative, the countermeasures we are laying out might be useless, but the tactics will still need to be adapted to the movement of the enemies. What we need to consider the most right now is how to resist the enemy’s attack. Let’s not talk about Section Zero’s soldiers, since they far outstrip you all in quantity. In terms of advanced combatants, no one can fight against Black Star, so we’re at a great disadvantage."

Hearing that, Hadavy spoke in a deep voice. "I’ll hold him back."

"He has already pushed you back tens of times, proving that you are unable to handle him yourself. There have been many cases of you retreating early, leaving those combatants that were helping you up sh\*t creek. At least fifteen Grade A Supers have died because of you," Jorde replied rudely. Sometimes, he even wondered if Hadavy was sent by the other side. Every time that he moved, the casualty rate would definitely be higher.

Hadavy was speechless and could not refute his unscrupulous betrayal of teammates, so he could only snort in dissatisfaction.

Jorde had a solemn expression as he continued. "This time, I’ll hand the rights to the weapon specially designed to curb Black Star over to you. This can only be used once, so you’d better make use of the opportunity."

Touching the contents of his pocket, Hadavy looked a little hesitant.

A few days earlier, a squad belonging to Jorde had been sent over, delivering a weird object to him. They had said that this was a special one-time consumable weapon created to deal with Black Star, which could damage him severely. They had told him to utilize it when facing Black Star.

While Hadavy did not understand the specific function of the weapon, it was definitely used as a hidden scheme. Hadavy had gone to work for the Bloodshed Land specially to fight against Han Xiao. He wished to use a proper confrontation to stimulate his potential, so he was reluctant to utilize underhanded methods against Black Star.

"Do you understand? If there’s an opportunity, you must use it immediately!" Jorde stressed.

"This is not the style of the Tyrant." Hadavy was a little dissatisfied.

"But this is my order!" Jorde snapped. He respected the demeanor of the Tyrant, but there had to be someone to deal with the dirty work. This special weapon had taken him much effort to obtain, and he did not even tell Heber about it.

Hadavy deliberated for a time before finally reluctantly agreeing to use it. However, he secretly planned to never take it out.

Anyway, he was only there to fight. Whoever won the war was not of any concern to him. He was not a subordinate under Bloodshed Land, and Jorde could not punish him even if he failed. At worst, he could just stop working for them.

Chapter 726: Psyker

Bloodshed Land and Section Zero had been fighting each other for ten years already and were extremely familiar with each other. The upcoming battle would be another exchange between both parties, and they all made their respective preparations.

The main force of Section Zero did not delay and very quickly launched an all-out assault on the final few strongholds in the Kant Star System.

Ten or so planets burned with the flames of war.

The Black Star Army fleet worked together with the other members of Section Zero to attack a few different planets. Currently, the players could not play a huge role in a galactic battle, and Han Xiao sent the players to be the vanguard force of a land assault. He placed them in the most treacherous location of the battlefield. Despite the frontlines being the most dangerous location on the battlefield, it also allowed them to gather as many kills as possible. Furthermore, their fearlessness also served the purpose of breaking through the enemy defense lines.

As for Han Xiao himself, he was situated at the core of the battlefield and followed the main troops to attack the Hyperdrive Base Station.

Their troops had the absolute advantage this time, and he did not have to infiltrate the enemy force alone. He only needed to guard the Star Diamond Grade Flagship. He watched as his allied troops slowly destroyed the enemy defense line and advanced.

In the command room from the flagship, the walls of the spaceship seemed to have been made from transparent crystals, and one could clearly view the explosions and cannon fire outside the spaceship.

A scaled projection of the entire battlefield could be seen floating in the middle of the command room, and the commander of the battle as well as his advisors were monitoring changes in the battlefield.

Han Xiao stood by the side and watched the battle.

He was not the commander of this operation, but as the most powerful fighter around, he was also a member of the core team. He guarded the command room personally and was ready to set off at any moment.

The commander and the others were currently analyzing the battlefield while Han Xiao listened by the side.

"The enemy withdrew a portion of their fleet from the other strongholds to guard their base. They are putting up a strong resistance, and we may need a long time to break through the thick defenses of the enemy.

"However, there is also a piece of good news. Because the enemy withdrew a portion of their forces from the other strongholds to guard the base, the defenses of their other strongholds have been weakened, and our forces attacking the other strongholds have the upper hand at the moment."

Han Xiao nodded. The Hyperdrive Base Station was connected to all the strongholds and was like the heart that sent blood to the other organs. Most importantly, the moment the Hyperdrive Base Station fell, the entire defense line would also collapse.

Because his side had an advantage in the number of troops with their main force attacking the Hyperdrive Base Station, the enemy had no choice but to withdraw their forces from the other strongholds to guard the Hyperdrive Base Station. This way, it would be much easier for them to clear out the enemy strongholds.

Section Zero’s objective was to wipe out the fleets protecting the strongholds. The moment the Hyperdrive Base Station fell, the fleets of the various strongholds would definitely retreat to preserve their strength.

Thus, while the intention of their forces seemed to be an all-out assault to capture the enemy base, they were actually trying to tie down the enemy forces to allow their allies to destroy more enemy strongholds.

Han Xiao’s gaze swept past the various regions of the battlefield to find Hadavy’s location. His only job that day was to defeat Hadavy.

Han Xiao could not help but stroke his chin after realizing that Hadavy was nowhere to be found. "Isn’t he prepared to take action? Did he appear on the other battlefields?"

Perhaps Hadavy would avoid him and make use of the Hyperdrive Base Station. He could choose to reinforce the other strongholds through the wormhole since the other fleets would not have a high-level combatant capable of stopping him.

However, Han Xiao was not too worried. If Hadavy avoided him, it meant that the enemy troops would not have a high-level combatant capable of stopping him. At that time, he would be able to take action to push the enemy forces back and force Hadavy to return.

"The other divisions haven’t discovered any traces of him." The commander shook his head. "He is still in the base. As long as he doesn’t appear, you do not need to take action. We aren’t the ones feeling anxious."

Han Xiao nodded and opened the forums to pass the time.

The players were currently carrying out their various battlefield missions, and the forum was filled with screenshots of the battle. The players took screenshots of different enemies, bosses, and their spoils of war.

There were some players who also made live streams of the war. For example, the professional players from the various clubs did a live stream of the war in order to attract fans.

Participating in a large-scale war truly excited many of them. There was no fun without any challenges. After briefly looking through the forums, Han Xiao concluded that most players felt a sense of satisfaction from this battle.

Compared to the players from the other Star Fields who were still searching for clues regarding the Main Storyline mission, the Black Star Army had already began receiving benefits from the Main Storyline mission.

After browsing the forums for a while, the commander’s anxious voice snapped Han Xiao back to reality.

"Hadavy has appeared!"

Han Xiao’s eyes sparkled, and he closed the forums. Hadavy’s figure appeared within the assault battleships of the Black Star Army, and he was currently destroying battleship after battleship. Lagi had already gone forward to stop him, and both parties had begun fighting.

"Your Excellency Black Star, please fight him off," the commander said with a heavy tone.

Lagi and Hadavy were currently facing each other amid the chaotic battlefield. Lagi’s staff flickered with various colors, and colorful magic spells smashed down onto Hadavy like a waterfall.

Hadavy was a close-combat main tank while Lagi was a long range damage dealer. The battle between them would naturally be one chasing while the other fled.

The battlefield between the two shifted every second, and the energy waves from their battle were like shining stars on the radar. All the battleships near them were affected by their battle.

They easily traversed over ten thousand kilometers during their short exchange, and their battle went from one corner of the battlefield to another. Hadavy grasped the right opportunity and hugged Lagi’s body. Their figures then crashed into a Section Zero battleship, and both of their bodies tumbled into the inside of the battleship. They got up instantly with their gazes locked on each other.

An ear-piercing alarm sounded from the inside of the battleship, and the defensive measures of the ship were activated fully. Various miniature floating guards, mobile artillery towers, and mechanical soldiers flooded over from the various walkways. The defensive squad of the battleship also charged over without hesitation.

The sound of mechanical activity and cluttered footsteps could be heard from the walkway behind Hadavy. Without even looking back, Hadavy threw out a punch backward.

A powerful force compressed the air within the battleship and sent it out with a powerful shockwave. As though a violent storm had blown past, the entire walkway behind him was torn to shreds, and all the guards were wiped out in an instant.

Hadavy retracted his fists and lamented as he looked at Lagi. "You truly live up to the reputation of being the vice commander of the Black Star Army. I can feel a great sense of danger from your magic, and you are definitely one of the top five mages that I have seen in my live."

"Sigh, I should have chosen to become a Psychic instead back then. What’s the point of being a Mage? I can’t kill you, and it still takes so much effort." Lagi let out a sigh and lowered his staff.

As Hadavy saw that Lagi did not intend to attack him, he asked with a face full of doubt, "Are you going to admit defeat?"

Lagi shook his head and replied, "I can’t kill you, and you can’t kill me. Since Black Star will be coming in a while, we might as well just wait here and save our strength."

Hadavy had a strange look on his face. You obviously just want to avoid work!

Right at this moment, Han Xiao appeared from the large hole in the battleship. Seeing the two of them getting along peacefully, Han Xiao was stunned.

Without waiting for Han Xiao to say anything, Lagi said, "I shall hand things over to you."

Lagi then cast a teleportation spell and disappeared without a trace.

Han Xiao was truly helpless in the face of Lagi’s laziness, and he turned around to look at Hadavy.

"You again. Why did you have to join Bloodshed Land and create trouble for me? Since you like being beaten up by me so much, you might as well let me catch you and beat you up three times a day."

"You will only face me with killing intent if I am your enemy. Only then will the battle between us be meaningful!" The moment Hadavy saw Han Xiao, his battle intent began to burn, and he charged forward toward Han Xiao.

Han Xiao had already activated his Machinery Apostilization talent, which gave him a boost of almost a thousand attribute points. He avoided Hadavy’s charge and grabbed onto Hadavy’s arm to throw him out. A new hole was immediately created in the battleship.

Han Xiao then sent out a psionic blast and sent Hadavy flying further away before summoning his mechanical army.

A cold voice sounded in Han Xiao’s helmet.

"War system Sparta awaiting orders!"

This was an artificial intelligence created specially to control the mechanical army, and Han Xiao had named it Sparta. This name sounded as though it was made for war.

Han Xiao gave out an order for Sparta to control the mechanical army to assist him in battle. A dark cloud of mechanical soldiers then chased after Hadavy to block him.

After fighting him so many times, Han Xiao was extremely familiar with Hadavy’s abilities. Because it was extremely difficult to kill Hadavy, the focus of the mechanical army was on control

Hadavy and the mechanical army were engaged in an intense battle, and Han Xiao harassed Hadavy by the side. At the same time, he casually destroyed a few battleships nearby and harassed Hadavy through voice chat.

"Stop fighting. You can’t win anyway."

"When are you planning to run? I will give you a chance to escape beforehand."

"Let’s make a deal. Why don’t you stand there and allow me to fire at you a few times to vent my anger? I will face you in hand to hand combat next time. How about that?"

"Heh, how much is Bloodshed Land paying you? I will give you double if you come and work for me."

Hadavy’s face turned darker and darker before he finally exploded. "Shut up! Focus on fighting me!"

He enjoyed facing powerful opponents to stimulate his potential and felt that he would only receive benefits from a treacherous battle that forced him to the edge.

Just when Han Xiao was prepared to continue, Jorde’s stern voice suddenly sounded in the communication channel. He and Hadavy heard everything that Han Xiao had said.

"Hadavy, use the weapon I handed over to you immediately."

Weapon?

The enemy may have prepared some special method to deal with me.

Han Xiao immediately became alert and tightened the attack of his mechanical army. At the same time, he closely monitored all of Hadavy’s actions.

However, it was as though Hadavy did not hear anything, and he continued to fight the mechanical army.

"Did you hear me?" Jorde bellowed. "Are you going to defy orders?"

Hadavy pretended that he had not heard anything

Jorde’s voice then turned cold. "I knew that you wouldn’t listen to me."

Hadavy suddenly had a bad premonition, and the ‘special weapon’ on his body suddenly reacted. This was a Secret Message Bead that suddenly unlocked itself automatically. A faint palm-sized ball of white light then floated out from the bead and hovered beside Hadavy.

"What is that?"

Both Han Xiao and Hadavy were taken aback.

Before the two of them could even think, the ball of white light disappeared and appeared above Han Xiao. Han Xiao had already made preparations and immediately reacted.

Void Travel!

The space around him seemed to have been frozen, and Han Xiao rapidly avoided the ball of white light. This ball of white light seemed extremely eerie, and it was best to stay as far away from it as possible.

The next moment, the ball of white light shot toward Han Xiao and could actually move in the Void Dimension as well!

Han Xiao was startled and tried his best to avoid it, but the ball of white light chased after him tightly.

Han Xiao hurriedly deactivated his Void Travel and activated a short-ranged hyperdrive to exit the battlefield. However, the white light appeared before him yet again as though it was a homing skill that would definitely hit him.

This thing can’t be avoided… Han Xiao’s gaze became solemn, and he shot at the ball of light. However, the ball of light seemed to have no physical form, and the laser beam went right through it.

Since he could not avoid it, Han Xiao activated a few psionic shield layers and welcomed the ball of light instead.

However, the many layers of shield could not even touch the ball of light, and it went straight through the shields and struck Han Xiao’s body. It then disappeared right after.

Han Xiao touched his body, and he did not seem to be injured at all.

"Just what is… urgh!"

He suddenly felt an intense pain in his head, and a notification popped up on his interface.

You have been struck with Psyker’s (Psychic Parasitic Toxin). You have received 14,860 mental damage!

You have gained the (Schizophrenia) status. Duration unknown.

You have gained the [Poisoned Soul) status. Duration unknown.

You have gained the [Sensory Misdirection) status. Duration unknown.

You have gained the [Parasitic Mind) status. Duration unknown.

You have gained the [Mild Hallucination] status. Duration unknown.

Han Xiao gritted his teeth as he stared at the notifications on the interface.

The thing that shocked him the most was the attacker.

Psyker.

He was the only beyond Grade A Super in the Shattered Star Ring that Han Xiao had not met!

Psychic!

"Why would it be him?"

Chapter 727: Psychic Toxin

There were four Beyond Grade A Supers that everyone knew about. For (Tyrant] Heber, (Dragon Emperor] Ames, [Magus] Austin, Han Xiao had met or even communicated with the three of them at some point. But for the final Beyond Grade A, the (Star Pupil] Psyker, he had never even seen the guy.

Psyker’s territory was located at the very edge of the Shattered Star Ring. Han Xiao had once attended a party of overlords, but only Psyker did not show up.

Psyker was born in a Star System level Civilization and was the Supreme Leader of that very Civilization. He had led his tribe and compatriots to develop silently in their own territory.

Could it be that this guy has also sided with the Crimson Dynasty?

Inside his Mechanical suit, Han Xiao’s expression was dark.

In Version 3.0 of his previous life, Psyker did not get involved in this secret war. He could only attribute this current situation to his influence on the events in this life.

While he had never seen Psyker, Han Xiao could still remember his data.

Psyker was not a humanoid creature. It was said that he had achieved atavism, and his genes could be traced to one of the deities in the Arcane Church. He possessed a high spiritual talent and possessed the abilities of Psychic Activation as well as Psychic Realization.

The attack that he had taken was only a Psychic attack from Psyker that was stored by some means and not from the main body, so the damage was not high. The headache inducing part was the array of negative statuses with an unknown duration.

Han Xiao himself was unsure if this sneak attack was intended by Psyker or if the enemy had managed to obtain the item from certain channels, with Psyker being unaware.

After these thoughts flashed through Han Xiao’s mind, he suddenly found that he no longer had any energy to continue thinking. The negative statuses had begun to play their role, and his brain was suddenly filled with chatter, as though there were countless people murmuring within his head.

His vision began to overlap, as though mirrors were placed in random positions all around the place, giving birth to illusions. A sense of weakness began to appear from the depths of his spirit, as though he was suffering from mental exhaustion but unable to fall asleep.

Now that the guys from Bloodshed Land know that any Calamity Grade cannot threaten me, they’ve started to use Beyond Grade A attacks against me…

Strongly suppressing the chaos in his mind, Han Xiao gritted his teeth and waved his hand, and his Mechanical army acted according to the established order, strengthening their offense against Hadavy. At the same time, they rushed like a huge mechanical wave toward the battlefield, smashing apart enemy warships and speeding up their advance.

Han Xiao did not care about the command to delay the battle any longer and prepared to rush down to take over the Hyperdrive Base Station as soon as possible and end the battle so that he could return and take care of this negative state.

Hadavy was a little stunned. The white light before was a Psychic attack, and without any outward appearance of any damage done, he did not know if Han Xiao had suffered any sort of attack at all.

Even a Beyond Grade A seed such as him could not tell, let alone everyone else on the battlefield. Only Han Xiao himself knew what exactly had happened to him.

"Jorde, what sort of thing was that?"

Hadavy’s expression was ugly. He hated using underhanded methods the most.

"This is a secret." Jorde was dissatisfied with Hadavy and could not be bothered to explain further. Besides, Hadavy was only a cooperative partner, not loyal to Bloodshed Land. He did not take Hadavy as someone whom he could trust.

Hadavy suppressed his flames of anger, and while dealing with the concentrated firepower of the Mechanical army, he observed Han Xiao before saying, "He seems to be unaffected. What sort of damage did that white light do?"

Jorde only coldly laughed, not deigning to reply.

After exchanging blows for a decade, the intelligence collected by Bloodshed Land on Han Xiao was not little at all. Compared with his strong physical vitality, Black Star was considered weak to mental attacks. This could not be concealed, and most forces had guessed that. However, Han Xiao was only considered relatively weak in this regard; it was not his Achilles’ heel. Because his life force was so strong, ordinary Grade A Psychics or Mages were unable to exchange blows with him.

However, if the attacker was a Beyond Grade A psychic, then things would be different.

The attack was derived from Psyker’s psychic toxin, which was something that Jorde had spent a lot of effort to obtain. His inspiration came from the EsGod doppelganger that DarkStar had summoned seven years ago, with the purpose of weakening Han Xiao.

This was because the Tyrant was initially hoping for Han Xiao to reach the Beyond A Grade so that he could make an appearance and kill him to improve his reputation. Thus, Jorde had taken Heber’s orders as his life, not utilizing this toxin whilst waiting for him to improve.

However, not long ago, the Tyrant had personally accessed the situation and told him that it was almost impossible for Black Star to have a breakthrough in the next two to three years to become a Beyond Grade A Super. The Tyrant’s plans had fallen through, and thus, Jorde thought that there was no need to let Black Star go, contrary to Heber’s intentions.

Since Black Star was unable to advance, the Tyrant would have no way to interfere in the war based on the rules set, so Jorde decided to use Psyker’s psychic toxin to weaken Black Star and reduce his strength, removing the pressure of an advanced combatant.

This mentality was equivalent to originally thinking of holding a stock with great potential, yet suddenly seeing the growth of the stock stagnate or even begin to plummet and deciding to quickly sell the stock to cut his losses.

Psyker’s toxin was extremely insidious, and no hint of the source could be seen. Jorde estimated that Black Star would probably not even know of Psyker’s name.

"Your mission is already complete. Find a chance to retreat." Jorde regained his composure, throwing out this sentence before cutting the communication.

He was very satisfied with the results this time.

Hadavy remained silent. Only he was left in the call, and he no longer asked nor grumbled about what Black Star was inflicted with. He was suddenly enveloped with a sense of loneliness and resignation.

Hadavy weaved left and right in the battlefield, utilizing the Bloodshed Land’s fleet as a protective shield as well as his indestructible body, forcefully extricating himself from the siege of the mechanical army. He then stole a spaceship and quickly fled using hyperdrive.

Han Xiao had long been accustomed to his escapes, and knowing that he could not give chase with his current strength, he recalled the Mechanical army and turned back to deal with the other enemy Calamity Grades.

The Everlasting had also entered the battlefield, its crystals emitting psionic annihilation beams continuously destroying and annihilating all the spaceships passing by its crosshairs, leaving a line of blank space on the battlefield.

Faced with the unstoppable advancement of Section Zero, the Bloodshed Land changed its strategy, no longer resisting desperately. They began to withdraw whilst fighting, and seeing that the Hyperdrive Base Station was about to fall to the enemy, they decisively blew it up, cutting off their links to their various planetary bases and preventing Section Zero from reaching them.

After losing the fast wormhole passage, the rest of the planetary bases also became independent, and the fleets from each planet started to evacuate, abandoning the Kant Star System to preserve their strength.

It did not take long for all the troops from Bloodshed Land to evacuate. Section Zero had achieved a massive success in their counterattack, expelling all enemy forces in the Kant Star System.

Bloodshed Land’s number of Star Systems reduced from five to four, which also meant that the situation in the Kant Star System was not stable. If it was the West Wind, Kaya, or Chaida Star Systems, which had been occupied for a long time, it would not be so easy to repel them. Even so, this was a great victory, and Section Zero’s morale was boosted. The Purple Crystal Civilization was also overjoyed when they received this intelligence.

The rewards for the players’ missions were also settled, and the victory result improved their mission evaluations and increased the total reward.

On a random planet that had been occupied by Section Zero, black smoke rolled, and the ground was filled with burnt corpses. Groups of soldiers combed through the battlefield to collect any loot.

There were many players in the battlefield cleaning teams, picking up loot as though they were picking up trash.

"Our harvest this time is not bad. If we convert all this broken equipment into materials, we should be able to sell them for one or two thousand Enas."

Frenzied Sword picked up a high-tech mechanical war hammer, throwing it into the loot box as he spoke with a happy expression.

The Rivervale team was in the area collecting war loot and idly chatting in twos or threes.

The Vice Team Leader, Evil Sword, picked up a broken blaster, pursing his lips before tossing it aside, as he casually asked, "Leader, how much experience do you have now?"

"Let me see…" Frenzied Sword glanced at his interface. "I’m almost ready to advance."

Because the professional players had to take part in the Pro League at the end of Version 2.0, they did not save up much experience. Thus, at the beginning of the version, their levels were not the highest, and a majority of them had not reached the level 100 mark to undergo their promotion.

"You’re levelling up very quickly!" Evil Sword was envious. "I’m still lacking quite a bit."

"I killed more enemies than you and got a higher mission rating, so of course, you haven’t leveled up as quickly as me." Frenzied Sword smirked.

Evil Sword twisted his mouth. "Forget it, I won’t rush to promote together with you. I’d rather spend my experience on learning more High-End Knowledge. I’ll suppress my grade for the time being."

"Why would you want to suppress your grade? You can probably promote to Grade B right after you reach level 100."

"Who knows? Maybe there will be an experience penalty for killing Grade Cs after reaching Grade B. Anyways, with you as our guinea pig, it’s better for me to just wait for a while." Evil Sword grinned.

"Up to you, you wimp. After all, you’ll need to promote sooner or later." Frenzied Sword rolled his eyes in response.

On the other side of the battlefield, Hate the Heavens was also sweeping the battlefield with a few of his friends, idly chatting.

"This battle is finally over. After this, we’ll find some time to proceed toward another Star System to participate in another war mission," Hate the Heavens suggested.

While they were involved in a war, there was no chance to defect to the enemy camp. Now that the war mission had ended, they were free to move around, and Hate the Heavens had decided to take the opportunity to move by themselves.

"But the fifty-percent discount seems to be ongoing. I feel that we should enjoy the last wave of benefits before we change to another faction. We should first return to the Black Star Army headquarters, spend all of our benefits, and then join Bloodshed Land," one of them said.

Hate the Heavens nodded in response. "That works too."

"It’s just that our main storyline will have to first be removed and changed to the Klent faction main storyline," one of them said regretfully.

"There’s no way around it." Hate the Heavens shook his head. "But we at least managed to obtain the reward from this campaign. We should not be considered to have lost out. Compared to the hidden storyline of the Klent faction, this sort of loss is nothing."

Everyone else nodded in agreement.

At the same time, in yet another stronghold, Summer Night Flower was considering the same problem.

"After this mission ends, there should be people who go and join Klent. At that time, I’ll be able to prove my hypothesis, that the Klent faction is the best choice." Summer Night Flower sighed to himself. He believed in his conjecture and was full of expectations toward changing factions.

The majority of the forces were cleaning up the battlefield, so Han Xiao allowed Herlous and the other officers to deal with that while he closed himself up inside the training room.

In the room, Han Xiao’s face was pale, and his eyes closed as he tried to gather strength to sense his body’s condition. It was only after a long time that he reopened his eyes, his expression grave.

The problem was quite thorny.

[Poisoned Soul] would keep him in a permanent status of Mental Weakness that reduced all his attributes by twenty percent. In addition, his stamina and energy would fall fifteen percent faster than normal, meaning that he would require more effort to use the same skill.

[Sensory Misdirection) reduced his hit rate, critical rate, and evasion.

[Mild Hallucination] targeted his mental state, constantly harassing it with weird voices, making it difficult for him to maintain a calm and rational state.

The (Schizophrenia) status was the most dangerous, as it produced a sub-personality within him. It was linked with the [Parasitic Mind) status, where the mental toxins would parasitize his spirit, consuming part of the energy he used each time to nourish the weaker sub-personality. This would strengthen it, to the point that it would compete with the main personality for control of the body.

If the control over his body was robbed, his interface would show that he had entered the [Chaos] status and would run rampant, not recognizing friend or foe.

However, Han Xiao knew that the actual effect would be more complicated, not as simple as stopping at the (Chaos] status.

Psyker… sigh, I really hate this Psychic…

Han Xiao rubbed his temples while frowning. Right now, the sub personality was still weak, and he could not detect its presence. However, every time he moved to attack, the sub personality would also grow in strength.

Could it be that the objective of Bloodshed Land is to restrict my movements, making me afraid to fight?

Han Xiao helplessly shook his head. Toward a psychic attack made by a Beyond Grade A Psychic, even if he was prepared for it, the attack would still land.

It seemed as though he had to let go of whatever he had currently and think of an idea to resolve his negative statuses…

Han Xiao sighed.

The duration of the negative status is not written. Thus, I can assume that it will not go away on its own. How should I go about resolving this?

Enduring the mental fatigue, Han Xiao thought silently.

The easiest method would be to request His Majesty Psyker for aid. However, he was unsure whether Psyker was a friend or foe and would not throw himself into their grasp for nothing.

The second method would be to ask Austin for help. This plan could be considered.

The information on the interface was not comprehensive enough, and Han Xiao wished to examine the nature of the toxin in detail. However, he was more suited for dealing with material items and was unable to sense his mental state. Thus, he could only invite Lagi and Feidin over.

"You were hit by the sneak attack from a Beyond Grade A Psychic?"

When Feidin and Lagi came into the room and heard the explanation from Han Xiao, both of them jumped in shock.

Han Xiao rubbed his eyebrows and sighed. "It was impossible to avoid, and I didn’t expect to encounter Psyker either. Feidin, please check and see how bad my situation is."

Feidin turned solemn and stretched out his hands, pressing behind Han Xiao’s ears as he closed his eyes. His mental power began to seep into Han Xiao’s brain.

Han Xiao could feel Feidin’s mental energy seep in like tentacles.

Hum!

Suddenly, the vision in front of his eyes turned illusory, and it displayed the vision in his mental state, as shared by Feidin.

His mental territory was a blank world. Both him and Feidin existed in the form of spiritual bodies and light particles, overlooking the entire area.

About ten percent of the area was filled with purplish black mist. From time to time, it attempted to condense into a human figure but met failure.

"This is the psychic toxin that has taken root and parasitized your mental territory." Feidin’s tone was grave. "Not only will it continue to absorb your strength and expand by itself, the moment it reaches approximately thirty percent of your territory, the sub personality will be born, and it will begin to fight with you for control over the body."

Han Xiao’s expression was ugly. "Can you clear all the psychic toxins?"

Feidin helplessly shook his head in return. "This is a psychic power belonging to a Beyond Grade A Super. Its power is tyrannical and hard to remove. Even my own psychic strength will be swallowed by it and turned into its nutrients. Sorry…"

At this time, Lagi’s spiritual body also squeezed in, appearing beside the two. One look at the scene, and he patted Han Xiao’s shoulder immediately.

"You have no hope left. Just hand the position of Army Commander to me. I’ll continue your work."

"Thanks a lot, man," Han Xiao replied sarcastically.